This is the story of Bridget and Annie,
who share a flat in London,
and the boys next door,
Nick and his friend Hector from Argentina.
Annie and Hector are dating
and Bridget and Nick were dating,
but that's history.
Now all Nick wants is a job,
a babe or a motorbike.
He's not fussy.
Stand by for Extra.
Oh, darling, no. I'll die without you.
He's Robert. He ran away with Jenny.
Oh, no!
That's why she can't marry Lionel.
-  That is so sad.
-  I know.
But doesn't Jenny know
that Lionel is her brother?
She had a car accident.
She can't remember.
That is terrible!
Quick, quick, quick, quick!
Go on! Kick it! Kick it!
Football! Hi, boys.
-  Hi, Bridget.
-  I need your help.
-  Sure. What is it?
I'm going to buy
a new computer for work.
I know everything about computers.
Great!
I need one with a lot of gigabytes,
good RAM memory,
all the software compatibility
and the top processor.
Maybe this one?
No, this one hasn't got what she wants.
And you understand what she wants?
Yeah. You don't?
-  Of course I do.
-  Well, so do I.
So? Have you decided which one?
Who's going to pay for it?
It's for work, so they'll pay for it.
-  This one, then.
-  This one is the most expensive.
It's a nice colour.
Well...
It has everything you want.
Do you think more SDI sockets,
or the analogue input?
Forget it. I'll order it now.
Come on, come on!
What are you doing out here?
Waiting for my examination results.
Your results are arriving today?
What have you done to Teddy?
Brad Pitt is much more handsome
than Teddy.
Where is it?
Bill, bill, nothing, nothing, bill...
It's not my examination results.
It's from the landlady.
It says we are too noisy.
Noisy?
She's written to the wrong apartment.
We're never noisy.
My new computer's here!
Well, Nick? Open it.
-  Why me?
-  Nails.
Anything else?
Well, it's a very big box.
What's that?
I think it's the instructions.
Great. Have fun.
Wait! Where are you going?
Shopping.
You'd better have finished
when I get back.
Better have finished what?
Installing the computer.
You do know everything about computers,
don't you?
No problem.
The instructions are all in English.
Look... Hector, here's a Spanish version.
Yes...
Right, let's do it.
Or don't you know how to do it?
I could do it with my eyes closed!
Well, instructions are for girls!
Oh, yeah!
I am the man!
Yeah, but I did all the work.
You? I did it.
I am the computer king.
-  Yeah?
-  Yeah.
-  You think you can beat me?
-  I already did.
Computers are easy.
How about a real challenge?
Whatever challenge you like.
Right...
Man Olympics. Challenge One.
Who can put the most marshmallows
in his mouth?
-  Marsh...
-  ..mallows.
-  Look. One.
-  One.
-  Two.
-  Three.
-  Four.
I'm going to buy a new computer for work.
No, this one hasn't got what she wants.
And you understand what she wants?
Come on, come on!
Where is it?
How about a real challenge?
-  One.
Well, instructions are for girls!
What's that? Love letters?
No, I've got all the letters
delivered to this building.
You've got the neighbours' letters?
I'm sure my examination results are here.
Where are the boys?
They've installed my computer!
I think so.
-  Is that normal?
-  Bridget!
Nick? Hector?
What are you doing?
Man Olympics. Challenge Two.
What kind of a challenge?
Who can go the longest without...you know...
Falling down? Sneezing? Jumping?
No, no. Without going...
Without doing...
You want to spend a penny?
Spend a penny?
I don't want to go shopping!
No, no, no. She means...
Stop thinking about your challenge
and follow me.
Maybe I've passed!
Maybe I've failed!
You're not going anywhere until it works.
-  Oh, no!
-  Here, let me try.
-  You think you can do better?
-  I know I can do better.
I know a way from my country.
-  Really?
-  Really.
My father taught me.
Yes, we have that way in England too.
-  Hi, guys.
-  Hi.
Oh, no! What happened?
-  It was like that before.
-  It was not like that before.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
Man Olympics. Challenge Three.
Hi. I need a man.
No, you idiot!
I need a man
to fix the computer I bought.
Tomorrow? Good.
And I'd like him
to be tall, dark, handsome...
Great, thanks. Bye.
At last, a real man.
Hi, I need a man.
It was like that before.
-  It was not like that before.
-  Sorry.
It's Nick's phone.
You have 23 new messages.
Message one...
Hi, bro.
I've got all my friends to call you.
I hear you and Bridget are history.
That's great news.
I didn't like her anyway.
Message two...
Hi, Nick. Izzie here.
Melanie asked me to give you a call.
I hear you and Bridget are history.
Hello. What?
Nicky Wick- wick is not here.
Is that Emma?
Nick's told me all about you.
Yeah. You and your moustache.
Nick!
Mr Postman?
Man Olympics. Challenge Five.
Tug- of- war to see who is the strongest.
They had a tug- of- war here?
Yes. They are so stupid!
-  Who won?
-  I won.
What's wrong?
I want my examination results.
-  Where's the post?
-  Calm down.
-  The postman!
-  The computer man!
Well, hello there.
Come in!
But...
I know what you're going to say.
-  But...
-  It was like that when I bought it.
So what do you think?
It looks broken.
-  Well, can you repair it?
-  No.
-  You can't repair it?
-  You don't know how to?
-  No.
Well, how can you be a repairman, then?
I'm not.
-  You're not a repairman?
-  No.
Well, what are you, then?
I deliver special letters.
My letter!
Annie Taylor?
-  Yes!
-  This is for you.
Man Olympics. New challenge.
First one to get...
Annie's letter!
It's mine!
I can't look! You read it.
Pass!
Computer problem, miss?
I can fix anything.
My hero!
Thank goodness you're here.
How did he do that?
-  Peter?
-  Annie?
-  It is you!
-  Yes.
He's Peter, an old friend.
It was so clever of you
to fix the computer.
Good- looking and intelligent.
A rare combination.
Right!
That's it!
Man Olympics!
New challenge.
What challenge?
Let's see who the real men are.
Hector and me, or you two.
-  OK.
-  What's the challenge?
-  Let us decide.
-  Yes, we'll decide.
Next time in Extra...
Annie gets a new job.
So does Hector.
And why does Nick
become a beauty queen?