This is the story of Bridget and Annie,
who share a flat in London,
and the boys next door,
Nick and his friend Hector from Argentina.
Hector and Annie love each other.
Nick loves babes and motorbikes
and Bridget loves make- up,
mirrors and chocolate.
Stand by for Extra.
It's time for Can You Live Without...?
And here's someone
you just can't live without.
It's Marty!
But what Sharon doesn't realise
is we've got a camera in the bathroom.
That's disgusting.
She must know that we can see her.
I think it is quite clever.
And what are Paul and Mandy doing
in the living room?
They're kissing. They're kissing.
They're not kissing. They're whispering.
What? Do you call this whispering?
Let's think of another name for it.
Paul and Mandy said they could live
without kissing for 24 hours.
And look, they've failed.
Paul and Mandy lose points for that.
We caught them kissing.
See you after the break.
Can You Live Without...?
is sponsored by Clouds Toilet Tissue.
Well, I couldn't live
without kissing Hector for 24 hours.
Why don't you try?
Hector, I wish you'd stop chewing gum.
-  I'm not chewing.
-  Yes, you are. You're always chewing.
No...
I bet you couldn't stop
chewing gum for 24 hours.
Well, yes, I could.
And, anyway, you suck your thumb.
I do not.
Well, only when I'm stressed.
-  I've had an idea!
-  Oh, no!
We could be contestants
on Can You Live Without...?
We could do it. It's just 24 hours
of giving up our favourite things.
It would be easy.
Think of the prize money.
And Marty Ross presents it.
He would come to my apartment again.
-  Oh, no!
-  Oh, Marty.
He's got such good taste.
And this is fantastic. Original.
What happened to Marty?
He said he needed time away from me
to really appreciate me.
-  So he dumped you, then.
-  He did not!
Anyway, Bridget,
are you feeling persuasive?
Of course.
I'm always feeling persuasive.
Well, it's time to persuade Marty
that we want to go on
Can You Live Without...?
And then Marty can make it happen.
I'll try.
Mr Ross to Studio B, please.
-  Hello, Marty.
-  Hello...
-  Bridget!
-  Bridget?
Bridget, Eunice's researcher.
We had dinner last month.
That Bridget. What do you want?
I've got something to say.
Well, I'm not the father.
-  No! Nothing like that.
-  Well, what is it, then?
My friends and I want to be contestants
on Can You Live Without...?
I wish I could help you, but it's not
my decision, it's the producer's.
Now, I must go.
-  You can't help me? That's a shame.
-  Yes, it is.
Because I'd hate for the newspapers
to see this.
Or this.
Where did you get them?
Don't you remember?
I'm Eunice's researcher.
I research.
I wish I could help you,
but it's not my decision,
it's the newspapers'.
All right, all right.
I'll see what I can do.
It's time to persuade Marty
that we want to go on
Can You Live Without...?
Hector, I wish you'd stop chewing gum.
Because I'd hate for the newspapers
to see this.
Or this.
We could do it. It's just 24 hours
of giving up our favourite things.
It's time for Can You Live Without...?
And here's someone
you just can't live without.
It's Marty!
Hello, darlings.
Do you want to spend
the next 24 hours with me?
-  Yeah!
-  Correct answer!
Yes, let's see what the people
who live here...can live without.
But it looks like
they live without anything anyway.
Well, let's meet the contestants.
You first, pretty lady. What's your name?
You already know my name, Marty.
We have a pretty joker here.
Don't get smart, sweetie.
This is my show, photo or no photo.
-  Bridget.
-  Good luck, Bridget.
-  And who do we have here?
-  Hello.
My name is Annie
and I'm Hector's girlfriend...
and I love Charley, my dog.
So, which one could you live without?
Enough said!
And this is Hector.
So, Hector,
Annie loves her dog more than you.
Mind you, Hector does sound
like a dog's name, doesn't it?
Here, Hector! Here, boy!
Don't bite!
And, last of all and least of all...
it's...
Hello? Is anybody there?
I know, you're a fish.
Hi. I'm Nick.
Hi, Nick. And what do you like?
Bananas!
Baboons. You like baboons!
You are a baboon.
You're a small baboon.
No, it's not baboons.
You like babes!
Sorry, this is Nick and he likes babes.
Well, let's get on with it.
As usual, each of these contestants
has picked one thing
that their flatmates
cannot live without for 24 hours.
Bridget...
You must live without chocolate...
mirrors...and make- up.
Annie, you must live without...
touching Hector, sucking your thumb...
and, most of all,
you must live without Charley.
Hector, you must live without...
touching Annie and chewing gum.
Nick, you must live without...
talking about babes
or talking about motorbikes.
And all of you must live without
television, magazines and music.
24 hours of living without starts now.
Come on, Charley.
You're coming with me.
Don't forget -  I'll be watching.
No television!
No touching.
If you touch, we lose points
and we won't win a big prize.
No make- up. What must I look like?
And no mirrors!
Look at that guy.
He looks like a monkey at the zoo.
So how will they do? Top points
could mean a holiday in the Caribbean.
But if they fail, they lose points
and their prize holiday could be this.
Of course, we might give them one or two
temptations to make interesting television.
Join me after the break.
You must live without touching Hector.
Nick, you must live
without talking about babes
or talking about motorbikes.
24 hours of living without starts now.
I think it's going to rain.
-  Do you?
-  I agree.
Manchester United are doing well.
-  Are they?
-  I agree.
I think it's going to rain.
Weather and football -
is that all you can talk about?
Well, yesterday I met this really cute b...
Don't say it! Do not talk
about babes or motorbikes.
Careful!
Bridget, no mirrors. You lose ten points.
But it's not a mirror, it's a kettle.
Don't argue!
You lose another ten points.
Well, it's all quiet now.
What about some temptation?
Hector, what is in your mouth?
Nothing.
-  Are you chewing gum, Hector?
-  No.
No, he's not. He's chewing this.
Open.
That was from the Red Sea.
It cost a lot of money.
I could kill for some chocolate.
This should be fun!
'Bridget.
'I love the show, love from...
'Orlando Bloom.'
Orlando Bloom...watching me!
I hope you didn't hear me say that.
What do I look like?
What are you doing, Annie?
I'm talking to Charley.
Annie, you must live without Charley.
You lose ten points.
What?
Hector...
- Don't move!
-  What is it?
It's OK, just don't move.
I'm not going anywhere.
What Hector doesn't know is that
we've put that spider on his jumper.
This is wonderful TV
Think, think!
One minute.
That's better.
Now, we'll just
brush this little fellow off.
Don't touch it!
It's OK.
I'm sure it's not poisonous.
How do you know?
Anyway, if you touch me,
we will lose points.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
OK.
Now...stay still.
Don't move!
Hang on a minute!
Hector, this is a toy.
I knew that.
Hector, you were so funny.
Marty has played a trick on us.
Yeah, very funny.
Who's a cross boy?
Things are getting really hot now
and they've still got over 12 hours to go.
You know, Hector,
I really think we can do this.
We can win that holiday.
Hello, Annie.
Bridget, what are you doing in there?
I'm...just reading the electricity meter.
Come here.
Why are you wearing dark glasses?
I don't want Orlando to see me
without make- up.
Bridget! Is that chocolate?
No.
But they're from Orlando!
No chocolate, Bridget.
You lose 100 points.
Nick has entered the building!
Nick!
Yes! Annie and Hector touched.
They lose 200 points.
-  What?
-  It was an accident.
And best of all, Nick,
you can't live without motorbikes.
So you lose 500 points.
No, no, no, no!
You said no talking about motorbikes,
actually, big nose!
Yeah, Marty.
So thanks for the present.
You can keep your holiday.
What? You can't do that.
Baby, fancy a ride?
Yeah!
Hector, this is for Marty.
Or should I say...Martina?
So, Marty, if you want the bike,
come and get it.
Sorry, Marty, we can live without you.
Goodbye.
And, Marty, I think your audience
will love this picture of you.
Oh, no!
Come on, Annie.
We have lots of catching up to do.
Hector, catch me!
Next time in Extra...
Nick plays Santa while Hector
and Annie play under the mistletoe.
and Annie plays under the mistletoe.