This is the story of Bridget and Annie,
who share a flat in London,
and the boys next door, Nick,
and his friend Hector fro Argentina.
Hector and Annie are in love.
Bridget likes to party and party.
And Nick will do anything
to earn some money.
Stand by for Extra.
I love this time of year.
Sleigh bells, mince pies,
presents under the tree!
What? Easter?
No, silly! Christmas!
I'm going to show you what
a traditional English Christmas is like.
Starting with...mistletoe.
Mistle-toe?
It's an English tradition.
When you stand under it,
you can kiss someone.
But I am not under any mistletoe.
You are now.
Oh, you poor things!
You're stuck together again.
Don't worry, I can help!
There, panic over!
- Right, I'm off.
- What?
Another television party?
Not a party, three more parties.
And that's just tonight.
But you've been to a Christmas
party every night for two weeks.
I know.
It's so difficult being so popular.
First, there's a champagne party
at the Savoy,
then at nine o'clock
I'll get a taxi to the Ritz
and get changed on the way...
What? In the taxi?
Naturally.
And then at 1 1 :30
I'll get a taxi to Annabel's.
Annabel - who is she?
Annabel's - the night club.
Will you change your clothes
in the taxi again?
And there I hope
I Will meet a young, handsome man.
An early Christmas present!
I hate Christmas!
Did you have a bad day
at the grotto, dear?
- Nick, is that snow?
- No.
Well, what,s that on your beard then?
I was holding this baby...
when suddenly...
- Christmas!
- But children Love Christmas.
- Is the money good?
- Yeah.
Well, stop complaining then!
Hector and I are going to have
a lovely Christmas, aren't we?
Christmas is all about
parties and presents!
So, Bridget, have you got your
Christmas stocking ready?
She's taking her stockings off
in the taxi!
Don't wait up.
What is a Christmas stocking?
On Christmas Eve,
you hang up your Christmas stocking
and a big, Jolly Father Christmas comes
and fills it up with presents!
Who put that sleigh there?
My sleigh! I forgot!
Mind my leq.
Right, right...
Whoa! Not too fast!
I feel terrible!
- Poor Bridget. Are you in pain?
- No.
But what about the parties?
I can,t go like this!
I could take you dancing!
Christmas is cancelled!
- Is that it?
- Yeah, crackers are great!
So, what else
do you have at Christmas?
Turkey, Christmas pudding, mince pies.
Mince pies. How do you make them?
It's just pastry and mincemeat.
- Mincemeat?
- Yeah, it's traditional
It's sultanas, raisins and spices.
It's mince...
- Meat.
- Yeah.
Listen to this.
What do you get
if you cross a chicken with a clock?
- I don't know.
- An alarm cluck!
An alarm cluck!
I don't get it.
One a cluck, two a cluck...
A clock?
Mistle-toe?
It's an English tradition.
When you stand under it,
you can kiss someone.
I was holding this baby...
when suddenly...
It's so difficult being so popular.
My sleigh! I forgot!
Mince pies!
First, the pastry!
And now the minced meat
from the best butcher!
They smell good, don't they, Charley?
Well, I've finished
all my Christmas shopping.
Oh, madam!
Refreshment? Mince pie?
Mince pies? Hector, you are clever.
I followed the re-ceep.
- Pee.
- Mince pee?
No, no, no. Re-ci-pe.
Re-ci-pe.
Good choice, madam. Merry Christmas!
Something wrong?
Delicious...Delicious.
You know, Hector,
Christmas is all about sharing.
Would you like some, Charley?
It's Saint Nicholas!
What happened to your beard?
One Christmas candle,
one small child...
Mince pies, yummy!
With best mince from the best butcher.
Hector. What did you put in the pies?
Minced meat - from the best butcher.
This is mincemeat.
This is minced meat.
Isn't it the same thing?
- Not quite.
- Delicious!
I've got an idea!
Let's make this a special Christmas,
just for Bridget.
Night-night.
Hey, Bridget.
- Do you want to come carol singing?
- Who is Carol?
Carols are Christmas songs.
You knock on people's doors
and sing to them for money.
- Let's do it!
- For charity!
For poor little children.
Some children have no Christmas.
Just like me.
And your job as Santa Claus
is so important.
You help children
to believe in Christmas!
Yes, you're right, Annie, I do.
My job is important!
I help children to believe!
Right, let's go!
I'll go, only if we can sing Abba songs.
And that Will make you happy?
Here, have a mince pie.
All right.
Away in a manger...
Dog in a manger more like! Good night!
Silent night...
I wish you were - all night!
We Three Kings of Orient are
One on a scooter, one in a car...
Get Iost!
Merrlly on high...
Get 'em, Gnasher!
Come all ye faithful
Joyful and tri...
Hi, Annie. I like the tree.
Thank you. It's nearly finished.
Please, use these. My decorations.
Oh, sweet, Hector.
- Are they from Argentina?
- No.
Oxford Street.
- Aren't they great?
- Great.
Hi, Nick.
How was your Iast day as Santa Claus?
Great! Such nice children.
One of them
let me play with his binoculars!
Really?
And I've just finished
my Christmas shopping.
- But the shops are shut now.
- No.
The petrol station was open.
Look I've bought my mum this.
A map of Watford.
- But your mum doesn't live in Watford.
- I know.
She might go there one day, though.
I bought shampoo for my sister.
Car shampoo.
Yeah. And aftershave for my dad.
I like the tree...but I Love these!
I've got some too.
It was the Iast day of the grotto today,
so they were throwing these away.
Can you believe it!
No!
Perfect.
Well, it might make Bridget Iaugh.
Why?
I know. If Bridget can't go to her parties,
let's have a party here!
- When?
- Oh, I don't know.
In about 15 minutes?
Look at the Christmas tree!
I know. It makes me want to cry too.
What's the point of having Christmas
if I can't go to my Christmas parties?!
Now Christmas just makes me cry!
Bridget, cheer up.
Tomorrow is Christmas Day.
Have you got your stocking?
Yes.
And I've got mine!
What are you hoping for? A motorbike?
Yes! Why not?
The only thing
that Will make this Christmas worse
is if you invited all my friends round
for a surprise party to cheer me up.
Surprise!
And now the minced meat,
from the best butcher!
They smell good, don't they, Charley?
We Three Kings of Orient are
One on a scooter, one in a car...
Good night!
Joyful and tri...
Surprise!
Hang on, I,m coming!
- Merry Christmas!
- Hello, Bernard. Merry Christmas.
I'm sorry,
we had a little party Iast night.
I'm here for dinner.
Isn't it a bit early?
Ten o'clock, time for a sherry.
- Bernard, where's your mother?
- At church.
Well, I'll just go and get dressed.
To Bernard, Love from Annie.
Sherry. Thanks, Annie.
Nearly finished this one.
To Bridget, Love from Annie.
A flea collar? I haven,t got fleas!
I'm sorry, Bridget, wrong label.
It was meant for Charley.
Is she sure it was meant for Charley?
To Bridget, from Hector.
Thank you, Hector. You shouldn't have.
What To Wear At Christmas Parties.
I bought it before you...
I've got a little something for you, Nick.
Gorilla -
because you are the original man.
It smells like a gorilla.
Well, you should know.
I wonder what this could be.
Merry Christmas, sugar plum.
Merry Christmas, snuggly-puppykins.
One heart, forever.
This Will stop it!
Bridget, nothing Will stop
my Love for Hector.
Well...
I just called to say Merry Christmas!
Hector.
Bridget, what has happened to you?
- I had an accident.
- Oh, what a pity!
You've missed some fabulous parties -
especially at the Beckhams'.
Elton John is a very naughty boy!
Still, never mind,
there is always next year.
OK, must dash.
Off to a top restaurant for lunch.
- Eunice?
- Yes?
Before you go, have a mince pie. Nick?
I shouldn't...but it's Christmas.
It's true, there is a Santa!
And she's a woman! Wait for me!
I want to tell you
what I really want for Christmas!
- Can you smell something?
- Yeah.
Is something burning?
I forgot - the turkey!
Water, water! We need water!
Not on me! On the turkey!
Move! Move!
There. The fire is out.
Anyone for turkey?!
Shall we just have pudding?
No mince pies, thanks.
I have another surprise for you.
Another English Christmas tradition.
Chocolate log. One slice or two?
Next time in Extra...
Nick wants to join the SAS,
Bridget and Annie
train the boys for action
and why is Hector home so late?
Hello, Hector!