goodbye mr. Hollywood by John Escott
chapter one mystery girl it all began on
a beautiful spring morning in a village
called Whistler in Canada a pretty
little village in the mountains of
British Columbia there was a cafe in the
village with tables outside and at one
of these tables SAT a young man he
finished his breakfast drank his coffee
looked up into the blue sky and felt the
warm Sun on his face Nick lortz was a
happy man the waiter came up to his
table more coffee he asked yeah great
said Nick he gave the waiter his coffee
cup the waiter looked at the camera on
the table on vacation he said where are
you from San Francisco Nick said he
laughed but I'm not on vacation I'm
working I'm a travel writer and I'm
doing a book on mountains in North
America I've got some great pictures of
your mountain the two men looked up but
Whistler mountain behind the village it
looked very beautiful in the morning sun
do you travel a lot then asked the
waiter all the time Nick said I write
books and I write for travel magazines i
right about everything different
countries towns villages
rivers mountains people the waiter
looked over Nick's head there's a girl
across the street he said do you know
her Nick turned his head and looked no I
don't well she knows you I think the
waiter said she's watching you very
carefully he gave nick a smile have a
nice day he went away back into the cafe
Nick looked at the girl across the
street she was about 25 and she was very
pretty she is watching me Nick thought
then the girl turned and looked in one
of the shop windows after a second or
two she looked back at Nick again Nick
watched her she looks worried he thought
what she doing is she waiting for
somebody suddenly the girl smiled then
she walked across the street came up to
nick's table and sat down she put her
bag down on the table the bag was half
open hi I'm Jen she said do you remember
me we met at a party in Toronto hi Jan
said Nick he smiled I'm Nick but we
didn't meet at a party in Toronto I
don't go to parties very often and never
in Toronto Oh
the girl said but she didn't get up or
move away have some coffee said Nick the
story about the party in Toronto wasn't
true but it was a beautiful morning and
she was a pretty girl maybe it was a
party in Montreal or New York the girl
laughed okay maybe it was and yes I'd
love some coffee when she had her coffee
Nick asked what are you doing in
Whistler or do you live here oh no she
said I'm just uh just traveling through
and what are you doing here I'm a travel
writer Nick said and I'm writing a book
about famous mountains that's
interesting she said but her face was
worried not interested and she looked
across the road again a man with very
short white hair walked across the road
he was about 60 years old and he was
tall and thin the girl watched him are
you waiting for someone asked Nick no
she said quickly then she asked where
are you going next Nick to Vancouver for
three or four days he said when are you
going she asked later this morning he
said there was a letter in the top of
the girls half open bag Nick could see
some of
writing and he read it because he saw
the word Vancouver and we can meet at
the empress hotel victoria vancouver
island on friday afternoon so she's
going to vancouver to he thought
suddenly the girl said do you like
movies movies yes I love movies he said
why I know a man and he he loves movies
and going to the cinema she said slowly
people call him mr. Hollywood she smiled
at Nick can i call you mr. Hollywood to
Nick laughed okay he said and what can I
call you she smiled again call me
mystery girl she said that's a good name
for you said Nick just then the man with
white hair came into the café he did
not look at Nick or the girl but he sat
at a table near them he asked the waiter
for some breakfast then he began to read
a magazine the girl looked the man then
quickly looked away again do you know
him Nick asked her no she said she
finished her coffee quickly and got up I
must go now she said Nick stood up to
nice too
he began but the girl suddenly took his
face between her hands and kissed him on
the mouth drive carefully mr. Hollywood
goodbye she said with a big beautiful
smile then she turned and walked quickly
away Nick sat down again and watched her
she walked down the road and into a big
hotel now what thought Nick was that all
about the man with white hair watched
Nick and waited after four or five
minutes Nick finished his coffee took
his books and his camera and left the
cafe his car was just outside the girls
hotel and he walked slowly along the
street to it the man with white hair
waited a second then quickly followed
Nick from a window high up in the hotel
the girl looked down into the road she
saw Nick and the man with white hair
about 50 yards behind him Nick got into
his car and the man with white hair
walked quickly to a red car across the
street five seconds later Nick drove
away in his blue car and the red car
began to follow him when the girls saw
this she smiled then went to put some
things in her travel bag
chapter 2 a hand in the back that
evening in his hotel room in Vancouver
Nick could not stop thinking about the
girl in the Whistler cafe why did she
come and sit with him she didn't know
him and that story about a party in
Toronto wasn't true and she was worried
about something but what and that kiss
it was nice of course but why did she do
it maybe she liked my face Nick thought
or my brown eyes but I'm not going to
see her again so it doesn't matter
forget it he put some money in his
pocket and went downstairs to the hotel
restaurant but there were no free tables
so he walked down to gas town and found
a restaurant there after dinner he went
for a walk Vancouver was a friendly City
and Nick liked walking through gas town
and Chinatown looking in the shops and
watching the people it was nearly dark
now and it was a busy time of the
evening there were a lot of cars and a
lot of people after a time Nick began to
walk back to his hotel he came to a busy
street and waited with a small crowd of
people to go across a tall woman in a
blue dress stood next to him she turned
and smiled at him it's the first warm
evening
of spring she said it's nice to be out
after the long cold winter yeah said
Nick it's great it's suddenly there was
a hand in his back and the hand pushed
Nick into the road Nick fell on his face
in front of a big green car people
screamed but the green car stopped only
inches from Nick's head the woman in the
blue dress ran into the road and pulled
Nick to his feet are you okay what
happened she said the driver of the
green car shouted angrily at Nick but
Nick did not hear him somebody pushed me
he said to the woman I didn't fall
somebody pushed me pushed you said the
woman who I didn't see anybody Nick look
to the faces of the people near him but
he didn't know them then he saw a man's
back the man was tall and thin and had
very short white hair he walked quickly
away down the street and did not look
back hey you Nick shouted wait but the
man did not stop and he was soon lost in
the crowds did he push you ask the woman
in the blue dress I I don't know Nick
said do you know him she asked
I don't know his name Nick said but I
know that short white hair now where did
I see it before the woman began to move
away I must get home she said are you
okay now yeah I'm okay Nick said and
thanks thanks for your help that's okay
the woman smiled be careful now back in
his hotel Nick sat on his bed and
thought it was an accident nobody pushed
me it was an accident nobody wants to
kill me and there are hundreds of men in
Vancouver with white hair it was one
o'clock in the morning but Nick couldn't
sleep he listened to the cars in the
road and he looked at the night sky
through his hotel room window then he
sat at the table and tried to write some
more of his book about mountains but he
couldn't think about his work he got
back into bed there were four or five
magazines in the hotel room they were
not very interesting but Nick sat in bed
and opened one and saw a photo of
mystery girl he looked at the picture
very carefully but yes it was her Jan
the girl from the Whistler cafe
she was next to a man of about 50 or 55
and they were in the garden of a big
expensive house they smiled the camera
and they looked very happy Canadian
millionaire Howard Hutson and his
daughter Meg it said under the picture
at their home in Toronto Meg Hutson not
Jan not mystery girl meg Hutson the
daughter of a millionaire Nick read it
again why did she come and sit with me
in the cafe at Whistler he thought
millionaires daughters don't sit with
strangers in cafes and then give them a
big kiss when they leave why did she do
it what did she want he thought back to
the cafe in Whistler and the girl next
to him at the table then he remembered
something he remembered a man at a table
near them in the cafe a tall thin man
about 60 years old a man with very short
white hair Nick didn't sleep much that
night chapter 3 a walk in the park the
next day was Thursday Nick stayed in his
hotel room and wrote about mountains all
morning then he drove to Stanley Park in
the afternoon he SAT and read a book for
an hour then he went for a walk
under the tall trees there was nobody
here it was quiet and he could walk and
sink he thought about Meg Hutson and
about the man with white hair did he
know Meg Hutson did she know him he
remembered meg Hudson's last words drive
carefully mr. Hollywood why did she say
that why did she call him mr. Hollywood
he didn't understand any of it suddenly
he heard a noise he stopped that was a
gun he thought there's somebody in the
trees with a gun there it is again then
something hit the tree over his head
somebody's shooting at me Nick thought
he turned and ran and somebody began to
run after him Nick ran through the trees
there was no Sun in here and it was half
dark and there were no people nobody to
help him I must get to my car Nick
thought find some people the police he
ran on he could still hear the gun man
behind him so he ran faster after three
or four minutes he stopped and listened
nothing it was all quiet
Nick was afraid what's happening he
thought why is somebody shooting at me
first a hand pushes me in front of a car
and now somebody's shooting at me he
waited another second or two then walked
quickly back to his car he was very
careful he looked and listened all the
time but nobody came out of the trees
and nobody shot at him then he saw
people women with young children some
boys with a football two men with a dog
he began to feel better nobody can shoot
me now he thought not with all these
people here ten minutes later he was
back at his car there was a letter on
the window Nick read it it said I'm
going to kill you mr. Hollywood Nick
drove to the nearest police station he
waited for half an hour then a tired
young policeman took him into a small
room Nick told his story and the
policeman wrote it all down so what are
you going to do asked Nick nothing said
the policeman nothing said Nick but
somebody shot at me and mr. Lourdes the
policeman said tiredly how many peep
are there in this town with guns I don't
know said Nick but you didn't see the
gun man was it a man a boy a woman color
of eyes long hair short hair you don't
know because you didn't see anybody
maybe it was an old girlfriend maybe
somebody doesn't like your travel books
mr. Lourdes but what about the man with
white hair in Whistler said Nick the
girl Meg Hutson called me mr. Hollywood
in the cafe and this man heard her and
now I get a letter to mr. Hollywood on
my car who is this mr. Hollywood we all
want answers to our questions mr.
Lourdes the policeman said but we don't
always get them questions but no answers
Nick walked out of the police station
and drove to his hotel he was angry and
afraid how did the man with white hair
find me in Vancouver he thought did he
follow me from Whistler is he following
me now maybe he's staying at my hotel
too in the next room with his gun
chapter 4 the man with white hair Nick
stopped his car in front of the hotel he
looked careful
Lee before he got out but there was
nobody with white hair near the hotel he
half ran through the hotel doors and
went to the desk inside I'm looking for
a man with very short white hair he said
to the woman behind the desk he's
staying here I think he's about 60 years
old and he's tall and thin the woman did
not look very interested there are a lot
of visitors in the hotel she said do you
know his name no I don't Nick said he's
a friend of a friend you see he arrived
in vancouver yesterday and I must find
him it's very important please help me
the woman looked at him there are 350
rooms in this hotel she said and maybe
30 or 40 men with white hair how can I
remember all their names she turned away
to answer a telephone call Nick walked
away from the desk a drink he thought I
need a drink he went into the hotel bar
got a drink and sat down at a table so
what do I do now he thought and then he
remembered something a letter in the
girls half open bag in the Whistler cafe
and we can meet at the Empress Hotel
Victoria vancou
island on friday afternoon and tomorrow
was friday i'm going to Victoria on
Vancouver Island he thought to the
Empress Hotel Nick had dinner in the
hotel that evening he finished eating
and got up from his table and saw the
man with white hair Nick moved quickly
the man was at the hotel desk Nick could
see the white head above the other heads
near the desk excuse me said Nick he
pushed past the people in the hotel
restaurant a small boy ran in front of
him and Nick ran into him the boy and
Nick fell down on the floor the boy
began to cry hey said a woman behind
Nick I'm very sorry said Nick he got up
and helped the boy to his feet are you
ok he asked the boy be more careful next
time said the woman Nick moved away
quickly but when he looked back at the
hotel desk he couldn't see the man with
white hair he pushed through the crowd
of people that man he shouted at the
woman behind the desk that man with
short white hair where did he go the
woman looked at Nick mr. Vickers she
said I don't know Vickers is that his
name said Nick
what's his room number I'm sorry I can't
tell you that the woman said but I need
to begin Nick the woman turned away to
answer the telephone after a second or
two Nick went upstairs to his room
Vickers he thought does meg Hutson know
mr. Vickers I need some answers and I
need them quickly
chapter 5 Vancouver Island tollison was
about 23 miles south of Vancouver Mick
drove there in his car the next morning
for the one o'clock ferry to vancouver
island every five minutes he looked
behind him the road was busy black cars
white cars red cars green cars maybe
Vickers was in one of them at tollison
Nick drove his car onto the ferry there
were a lot of cars and crowds of people
Nick got out of his car and walked up
and down the ship he looked for a man
with white hair but he didn't see one
soon the ferry began to move and Nick
felt better he found the ferry
restaurant and got something to eat more
people came in Nick looked the faces of
all the older men some had hats on so he
looked for somebody tall and thin but
there was nobody maybe he's not on the
ferry Nick thought maybe he's back in
Vancouver later Nick walked around the
ship again once he thought he saw the
man with white hair in the crowds but he
could not be sure ninety minutes after
leaving two wasin the ferry arrived at
swartz bay on Vancouver Island and Nick
went back
found his car swartz bay was 20 miles
north of victoria nick drove quickly and
again looked behind him every four or
five minutes once he saw a red car about
200 yards behind him did I see that car
on the road from Vancouver total wasin
he thought he drove more slowly but the
red car still stayed 200 yards behind
him and Nick couldn't see the driver's
face or hair soon he was in the busy
streets of Victoria and Nick didn't see
the red car behind him again victoria
was a city of gardens and beautiful old
buildings Nick liked Victoria very much
but today he wasn't interested in
gardens or buildings he found the
Empress Hotel went inside and walked
across to the desk can I help you a
young man asked Nick I'm meeting a
friend here this afternoon said Nick
miss Hudson Hudson said the young man
wait a minute he went away and came back
sorry but there's no miss Hudson staying
here Nick took something from his pocket
it was the photograph of Meg and her
father from the magazine this is her
he said the young man looked at the
picture all right you mean Howard
Hudson's daughter he said she's not
staying here but I saw her 10 or 15
minutes ago she was with somebody a man
he asked me about the Tea Room the Tea
Room said Nick where's that the man with
short white hair was tired he couldn't
sleep and he couldn't eat he thought
about only one thing all the time he
drove and he watched and he waited and
he followed when he drove into Victoria
the streets were busy and suddenly he
lost the blue car in front of him
angrily he drove around the city passed
all the big hotels I must find him he
said I must do it today then he saw the
Empress Hotel and in the street outside
it a blue car he drove past the hotel
left his car and ran back down the
street he went across the road and
walked past the downstairs windows there
was a big room with tables and chairs
and a lot of people he looked carefully
at all the faces there she is he said
suddenly there were two men with the
girl he
see their faces only the backs of their
heads but one of the men was in a green
shirt mr. Hollywood the man said and
smiled goodbye mr. Hollywood people in
the street turned to look at him but the
man did not see them he walked up to the
doors of the hotel and put a hand into
his pocket inside the gun was cold and
hard
chapter 6 a tea party Nick looked
through the doors of the Tea Room in the
Empress Hotel meg Hutson sat at a table
with a man the man was about 30 or maybe
a year or two younger he was tall and
brown from the Sun he wore a white shirt
white trousers and white shoes he said
something to Meg and she laughed she
looked very happy a waiter came up to
Nick can I get you some tea he asked no
thanks said Nick I'm with the two people
over there and he walked across to Meg's
table hello mystery girl said Nick
remember me we met at Whistler your name
was Jan then but maybe today it's Meg
Hutson meg Hutson looked up at him oh
she said and her face went red who is
this meg asked the man this is nick said
Meg he's a writer Nick this is Craig
winters sometimes called mr. Hollywood
said Nick maybe but how did you know
that asked Craig winters I guessed said
Nick and I think I'm beginning to
understand
can I ask you a question mr. winters
does somebody want to kill you Craig
winters face went white kill me what are
you talking about asked Meg before I
tell you answer this question please
said Nick you called me mr. Hollywood in
Whistler and you wanted the man at the
next table the man with white hair to
hear you is that right Meg Hutson did
not answer at first then she said
quietly yes why ask Nick I wanted him to
follow you and not me why Nick asked
again I think he's a detective said meg
and I think he's working for my father I
saw him soon after I left Toronto he
followed me meg put her hand on Craig
winters arm my father doesn't like Craig
a month ago he told me not to see Craig
again I'm not happy and he knows that I
think he guessed that I'm meeting Craig
and now he wants to find Craig and stop
him seeing me stop him said Nick or kill
him no Meg Hutson said daddy doesn't the
man with white hair pushed me in front
of a car in Vancouver Nick told her and
he shot at me in Stanley Park what said
Meg tell tell me about this man with
white hair winter said suddenly Nick
looked at him he's about 60 and he's
tall and thin he said do you know his
name asked winters Vickers said Nick
Craig winters suddenly looked ill did he
did he follow you to Victoria did he
follow you here I don't know said Nick
he watched winters you're afraid of him
why why does this man Vickers want to
kill you winters before Craig winters
could answer Meg's face went white oh no
she said look look over there by the
door Nick and Craig winters turned to
look at the door of the tea room stood
the man with white hair he looked up and
down the room and then he saw them and
began to walk across to their table his
hand was in his pocket for a second or
two the three people at the table did
not move then Craig winters jumped to
his feet that's mr. Hollywood he
screamed that man there and he pointed
at Nick
man's hand came out of his pocket with a
gun this his for Anna he shouted Nick
moved very fast the tea-table went over
and Nick was down on the floor in a
second the shot went over his head and
Meg screamed at the same time Craig
winters shouted out and put a hand on
his arm there was blood on his white
shirt then more people began to scream
and two waiters pulled the man with
white hair down onto the floor get the
police somebody shouted chapter seven at
the police station it was 730 p.m. Nick
and Meg were in a room at the police
station the man called Vickers was in a
different room with three detectives
there was a doctor with him to Craig
winters was at the hospital the door
opened and a detective came in with two
cups of coffee he put them down on the
table and turned to go out again
detective Edmonds meg said did the
hospital call is Craig going to be
alright winters detective Edmonds said
yes he's going to be ok can I call the
hospital now ask meg I'd like you to
wait said Edmund
detective keith is going to be here in a
minute he's just coming from the airport
and he looked through the open door ah
here he is now a second detective came
into the room and behind him was a tall
man with dark hair meg stood up quickly
daddy she cried what are you doing here
the police called me said Howard Hutson
and I flew here at once detective Heat
met me at the airport now sit down Meg I
want you to listen to me he did not look
at Nick meg sat down and her father took
her hands meg last week Johnny Vickers
came to my house he wanted to talk about
his daughter you remember Anna meg three
months ago she jumped off a bridge in
Boston and died she was young beautiful
rich and she didn't want to live why
because she loved a man and the man took
her money ran away and left her and the
man was called no said Meg no yes Meg
yes he was called mr. Hollywood no
shouted meg she began to cry that's
right miss Hudson
said detective Keith quietly to you he
gave the name Craig winters when Anna
Vickers knew him he was Carl Windsor but
he liked all his ha girlfriends to call
him mr. Hollywood he took nearly fifty
thousand dollars from Anna Vickers and
there was a girl before that no it's not
true meg shouted it is true meg said her
father winters Windsor gets all his
money from rich men's daughters Johnny
Vickers loved his daughter he went to
her house in Boston after she died he
read her letters and learned about the
money and the name mr. Hollywood and
when he came to my house I told him
about you Meg I said my daughter's got a
new boyfriend and she calls him mr.
Hollywood I don't like him but I can't
stop her she's going away to meet him
next week I think what can I do Johnny
put his hand on my arm and he said don't
be afraid for your daughter I'm going to
find that man and stop him meg said
nothing her face was very white for a
minute or two nobody spoke then
detective Edmonds said Vickers told us
all about it miss Hudson he followed you
to Whistler and saw you with
Nick began to understand with me in the
cafe and Meg called me mr. Hollywood
Howard Hutson looked at Nick you're the
travel writer guy right lords Nick
quartz said Nick Vickers nearly killed
me he shot at me twice and but Howard
Hutson was not very interested in Nick
he looked at his daughter again how much
money did you give him Meg he said I i
gave him $25,000 said Meg only for two
or three months he said then he she
began to cry again well you can say
goodbye to that money said Hudson
angrily what's going to happen to
Vickers Nick asked detective Edmonds
hospital I think said Edmonds okay he
shot at you and about 50 people saw him
but he's not a well man the doctors are
going to put him away in a hospital
Howard Hutson stood up okay Meg I'm
going to take you home my plane is
waiting at the airport meg followed her
father to the door then she remembered
Nick and turned I'm sorry she said I got
you into all this I called you mr.
Hollywood
that was wrong but I didn't know it's
okay said Nick you know everything now
and it's better to learn it now and not
later $50,000 later chapter 8 a nice
smile Nick took the evening ferry back
to Vancouver he was tired and hungry so
he went down to get some dinner in the
ferry restaurant the restaurant was busy
and there was only one free table Nick
sat down quickly and began to eat I must
get back to work tomorrow he thought and
forget about millionaires daughters and
men with guns excuse me somebody said
can I sit with you Nick looked up there
was a pretty girl next to his table he
got up it it's okay he said you can have
this table I don't want it and he began
to move away please don't go the girl
said stay and finish your dinner she
smiled at him it was a nice smile but
Nick knew all about nice smiles I'm not
hungry he said and he walked quickly out
of the restaurant
you