oxford bookworms stage 1 a ghost in love
and other plays by Michael Dean
published and copyright Oxford
University Press 2007 one ghost for the
day one ghost for the night performed by
Ben Elliott Lawrence Kennedy Sarah
Martland Coraline Sheldon and Terry
Wilton
one ghost for the day one ghost for the
night scene 1 a ghost comes to Richard
little the year is 16 53 it is a cold
dark winter night and Richard little a
man of forty is sitting in his chair he
is reading a book he hears something he
goes to the window looks out and then
goes back to the chair his wife Mary
comes in she is making a dress she has
the dress in her hand Mary I can hear
something outside there's nothing there
read your book Richard come and sit with
me no I'm making a dress I'm going
upstairs Mary please there's something
out there Oh Richard hello Richard oh
you James James Heston but you you're
dead yes I am dead but i can't find
peace because of you because of me why
why because of me Beth had a new husband
after me that's animal eh yes Beth was a
good woman and a good sister to me I
said to her don't go with keech think of
James he's dead now she was
teacher's wife for only three months
then she died and now Keech has my son
and he has my son's money ah I
understand now oh you remember now
before I died I said to you my boy gets
my money at 21 and not before he is 8
now 8 and keech has his money I'm sorry
about that but what can I do you must
get my boys money get it from keech no
teach can kill me with one hand he's big
he always has a knife in his pocket last
year he killed a man with that knife I'm
afraid of him James are you afraid of me
no oh yes a little you're a ghost only a
little a look at the table oh no the
table is moving oh no oh the chair is
moving now and now my chair is moving
James don't do this to me at this minute
Keech is building a new home in a
village near here with my son's money
stop him I'm sorry James I can't I
didn't want that was my hand but James
can you get in my head can you tell my
hand
yeah yes Richard and your answer is
going to be yes or you are going to do
this again and again and again and I'm
going mad why does my hand throw a book
when I don't want to can old dead people
do this can they get in your man's head
so he moves a chair or throws a book oh
yes now I can do it to you again or you
can say yes and get my son's money which
but how how can I get the money from
keech sit down I'm going to tell you
scene 2 David keech in court in the
court we can see judge Tim's keech
Barker Reynolds Richard and Mary there
are six women and six men behind keech
they are from the village and they are
watching the trial judge Tim's is in a
big chair in front of the court my name
is Oliver Barker and I speak for Richard
little here today judge Tim's I speak
for David keech here today my name is
phillip reynolds that key took the boys
money you can see it in his face Oh lil
we must listen to one of her Barker and
phillip reynolds first teaches the boy
Tom's father now a good father doesn't
take his sons money and build a new
house with it be quiet in my court sorry
Oliver Barker you can begin judge Tim's
before James Heston died he said this to
Richard little he said my boy gets my
money at 21 and not before at 21 and not
before yes judge but keech has this
money now the boys money he is building
a big house with it we all know that
pork each imprison eyesight hmm five
years no 10 you don't eat in my court
phillip reynolds speak George tins yes
there is a house in a village near here
and yes it is ki cheez house but the
money for it is not young Tom's money
not Tom's money no judge Tim's
it is David catches money so one day
Keech is not rich and the next day he is
rich he has money for a house call David
keech David keech where is the boy Tom's
money do you have it at home no Kate
took the money it was keech I said ki
took the money I said that yesterday I
have the money here in this Court the
money's here didn't teach didn't
whatever court the money is under my
chair you woman bring me the money be
yes you here you are here judge tins
here Richard little here look everybody
here is the money so I didn't take it
from a boy you hear me Richard little
yes one minute Richard little yes judge
Tim's you said teach took the boys money
you said that why why man why why say
that because because because James
Heston came to my home James Heston said
it to me distance did you heard little
James Heston is dead he died in 1651 to
test him oh that's I love you Wow judge
Tim's my husband is ill in our house he
talks to people and there is nobody
there can I take him home now please I
am NOT ill stop laughing be quiet all of
you
down Mary thank you yes James Heston is
dead and yes James Heston spoke to me I
want James Heston here now he can tell
you hey is al he's mad let's listen to
him yes we can listen to head be quiet
call James Heston I say call James
Heston to this court Heston is dead man
and Richard little is mad call James
Heston I am James Heston oh oh no no oh
please no it's Heston Oh Stan dead James
Heston is it you did you speak to
Richard little yes what did you say I
told him he took my boys money and then
teach killed a man in the next village
he was a rich man he took his money you
see the money now here in this Court
yeah I can't kill Heston Heston is dead
but you you Richard little you brought
me to this court I'm going to kill you
next stop him stop him it was cage
Kate's took the money I said that I said
Kate took the money this Court says
teach took the money and Keats kill the
man now find David teach and bring him
to me
scene 3 Keech finds Richard Little
Richard is sitting in his chair at home
what's that can I hear something Mary is
that you oh no it's not James again
James is that you oh oh no oh no Keech
please no oh no not Richard not my
darling darling Richard keech killed him
you're going to go to prison for this
keech
scene for a visit for keech in prison
peaches in prison he is sitting on his
bed he has a table a chair and a book
there too hello what's that is there
someone there ah my table my table is
moving ah now the beds moving am I ill
oh my head oh now the chair is moving
what's happening why did I do that am I
mad it was my hand but ha you're dead I
killed you yes I'm dead and you killed
me but I'm not going away I'm staying
here in prison with you you can't hit me
now you can't hit a ghost and you can't
kill me again but we can talk we have
time for that we have all day and you
can do that all day to all day all the
time yes now throw the book across the
room again and again and again and again
oh no please oh all my days going to be
like this your days yes and for your
nights I have a friend here hello
Richard hello David you you here too yes
David throw the book across the room
please
thank you I'm going to be here at night
David and you have Richard here every
day all right oh no no one ghost for the
day one ghost for the night now throw
the book across the room again
sleep now my darling performed by ben
cohen Candida gubbins Fiona Mollison
Vince Nichols and chris roe
sleep now my darling seen one Jenny must
stay at home it is a hot summer day
Jenny and Gilbert Lawson are having
breakfast at a table in their garden
Gilbert is reading a book Gilbert can I
come with you to America what Oh Gilbert
please listen to me I said can I come to
America too mmm this is good bread did
you make it yes Gilbert I said can I
come with you no Jenny you have work
here there's the house the garden hmm I
remember my new friend it was your best
film it was my best film too they were
happy days yes I watched my new friend
again last week it's the best Gilbert
Lawson film and you were good in it my
love you're a good actress the film had
a good director Gilbert Lawson oh thank
you but now I have this new film so I
must go to America for six weeks Gilbert
can I be in this film too I want to be
an actress again perhaps next time would
you like that perhaps you can be in the
next film you said that before did I yes
this bread is very good can we go to
America together then not for a film
just you and me perhaps next year
perhaps next year then yes next year
love I must go now I'm going to be late
for the plane I love you Jenny I love
you too darling
scene 2 Jenny talks to a film student it
is six weeks later jenny is having a
coffee at the airport she is waiting for
Gilbert's playing a young man Henry sees
her Henry has a big bag in his hand
hello are you Jenny Lawson yes I knew it
here you are and do you want something
thanks sorry but do I know you a coke
for me please and a sandwich one coke
one sandwich oh sorry yes I know your
film my new friend and I know Gilbert
can I sit down you can't stand up and
have a coke into sandwich wait a minute
I know you I know your face but I can't
remember tell me how do you know Gilbert
I'm learning about his work I know all
the Gilbert Lawson films but forget
about me I want to talk about you you
aren't happy I can see that what you
can't say that a coke and a sandwich
thank you that's ok sandwich is very
good I had them for lunch sometimes hmm
yes you're right it's very good thank
you that's ok goodbye then I must go
soon what do you do every day what I
don't know you you can't are any please
tell me what do you do every day ok
here's your answer I get up in the
morning and then I do nothing we have no
children a woman does the house for me a
man does the garden do you have friends
yes no
I have coffee with people i have dinner
with people we say things like nice
weather for the time of year but we
don't talk yes I understand now I'm
going to tell you about me i'm 20 i go
to America sometimes I have friends I
like films so I make films I'm happy
what about you I was happy when I was an
actress there there's your answer be an
actress again Jenny Lawson Laura what
are you doing here waiting for Gilbert
and who is this my name is Henry I'm a
film student sit down Laura please no I
can't stop my children are here we are
all going to America all the family I
write books now you know what do you do
me nothing have you got children no you
look unhappy Jenny at school you were
beautiful and good at everything and now
you are older with no work and no
children oh dear what Laura why did you
say that I have to go now what's what's
that name on your bag Henry Gilbert
Lawson I know you now Gilbert you are
Gilbert when he was 20 years old but why
are you here oh no
scene 3 Jenny learns about Gilbert there
are four people of the check-in woman
one woman to a man and Jenny's father
they are waiting a British Airways man
is looking at father's plane ticket
Jenny runs in excuse me Oh father what
are you doing here Jenny smile be happy
what hey I was here before you I was in
front of you two are you okay laughs
she's white in the face excuse me can
you wait please no my name is Jenny
Lawson ah mrs. Lawson we phoned you at
home there was no answer mrs. Lawson I'm
sorry but mr. Lawson's plane crashed in
the SI he's dead oh no
scene for Jenny understands everything
Jenny's father and mother and Jenny are
all sitting at a table they all died all
the people on the plane oh Jenny your
mother and I is so sorry my love thank
you why were you at the airport father
me I wasn't at the airport yes you were
you were at the British Airways check-in
desk you said be happy then you left no
wait a minute hello Laura Laura this is
Jenny Lawson we were at school together
Laura I saw you at the airport remember
and oh what is Laura saying she said I
wasn't at the airport Laura one question
do you write books now yes thank you she
writes books is that important yes Laura
wants to write books so she writes books
and she's happy at the airport father
said be happy and Henry Gilbert Lawson
said be an actress again I understand I
understand now to my darling husband I'm
going to be an actress for you again a
good actress thank you so sleep now my
darling
you
a ghost in love performed by jennie
brice Rupert Farley crisp in redmond
patience Tomlinson
a ghost in love scene 1 Brad sees a
ghost Brad and Jerry come into the hotel
room and put their bags down it is a hot
day and they are wearing summer shirts
Brad sits on a bed man I want to drink
20 miles in one morning how the bicycles
okay in the street in this little
village oh yes nobody steals bicycles
here how do you know this is your first
time here first time in England or am I
wrong no you're right but I remember
this village I was here before Jerry I
can feel it oh come on we were out in
the Sun for five hours you need to drink
some cold water my friend this hotel
opened in 1853 right right Brad you look
to this book before no I didn't hey you
know something it's 115 my dad died at
this minute on this day last month Oh
bread I'm sorry no no it's okay i'm
going to go back to New York next week
after our three weeks in England and I'm
going to be Brad Davis of Davis TV dad
wanted that yeah hey come on let's go
out in the Sun let's see the village
have a drink find some girls no you go I
like it here here in the room ok let's
stay in the room hey there's a tell
hmm not working oh forget it no you're
Brad Davis of Davis television the
biggest in America you must have a
television look shall I go down and ask
mrs. Finch you stay here you look tired
yeah thanks Jerry I am tired in 1760 the
hotel was a house a family called
Bannister lived in the house one day the
19 year old daughter Ellen I was never
19 I died at 18 yes I remember you hello
Ellen hello Matthew why does your friend
call you Brad is that a name yes it's an
American name but you are Matthew and
I'm going to call you Matthew always Oh
Matthew I waited and waited and waited
for you i love you so much do you love
me yes I think yes I do you think is
that an answer after all these years Oh
Matthew Matthew do you remember
everything no not everything I remember
our love and you died I remember that I
wanted to die too and again last month I
wanted to die Oh Matthew don't say that
Oh Matthew I'm so happy to see you again
Ellen can I see you can we talk oh yes I
want to talk to you about are you okay
love you look
right this is not a happy time for Brad
I'm sorry love do you want some dinner I
make the best dinner in the north of
England no thank you talk to me later
then right the television it's okay now
bye bye Brad by Jerry have a nice time
in our village mrs. Finch wait please do
you know about the banister family did
you see the ghost Ellen banister yes
what Brad you saw a ghost oh come on Oh
Ellen's always here she likes young men
she's always looking for her boyfriend
Matthew's his name i think mrs. Finch
what happened how did she die what
happened to Matthew you're interested
love I can see that there's an old woman
in the village her name is more dance
cim she knows about Ellen you ask mod
grad this ghost what did she say she she
didn't speak Jerry she said nothing at
all
scene 2 Brad and Jerry want to know
about Ellen Mord is a very old woman her
hair is white Brad and Jerry are sitting
at a table with her in her house Ellen
Bannister a bad bad girl when she looked
at someone the next day they were ill so
she was a witch yes she looks at animals
too then all the cows in the village had
no milk in them do do you know this how
do you know how can you know oh it's in
all the books our village is famous
because of bad Ellen Bannister
scene 3 was Ellen a witch Brad and Jerry
are in mrs. Morgan's village shop there
are two men and three women in the shop
and mrs. Morgan yes are you next yes two
cokes please and two of those sandwiches
I am not hungry man you must eat you
can't sit in your room all day and wait
for a ghost that's six pounds please
what ghosts this alan bannister yes do
you know about Ellen Bannister whoa
people in our village had no money then
of course they stole things and alan
bannister sold them she only wanted to
help was she a witch some people say
that a witch no of course not the men
loved her she helped them you see though
women didn't love her so much she was
beautiful you see her boyfriend was the
bad one that Matthew it wasn't her Oh
what did he do he stole things from rich
people then she sold them and he took
all the money he took all her money too
but she loved him did he love her no he
had two or three women no he didn't he
loved her he lived for her who are you
talking about that which alan bannister
she ate cats for breakfast oh don't
listen to him don't listen to these
people you boys what happened to Ellen
Bannister you want
lay that Matthew killed her
scene 4 where is Ellen now it is
nighttime Jerry is sitting on the bed
brad is walking up and down seven hours
we waited seven hours where is she Jerry
I said this before I don't know just
wait she isn't coming because you're
here bread I say again one I sleep here
this is my room too I am your friend and
I am NOT leaving you like this Jerry is
this all a big laugh for you no not now
I want to see Ellen too I want to help
ok thanks Jerry sorry hey here she is
Ellen Ellen it's me Brad Matthew man oh
man it's all true Ellen please tell me
what happened in 1760 you must remember
no we sold things you and me rich
people's things you stole them remember
Wow Brad you were robbing hood sorry the
rich people didn't like me they said bad
things about me alan bannister is a
witch they said that but it's not true
of course not then one day they came for
us twenty men what happened we run away
you found a ship a ship going
to America you said see you at 115 at
the Harbor we can go away you and me and
then what happened Ellen the ship went
early I wasn't there in time you went on
the ship you didn't wait for me oh no
when I arrived there were a lot of ships
there I didn't know the name of our ship
I looked for you I waited and waited and
waited Ellen Oh Elam I'm sorry then the
men came they put me in prison I died
three months later and then I came back
home here and I waited again I waited
for you i love you Ellen I love you too
Matthew
scene 5 what is Brad going to do it is
dark brad is standing at the window of
the room Jerry comes in Brad always has
his back to Jerry in this scene do you
want to die do you want to go to Ellen
before today the answer was yes Matthew
wanted to die and go to be with Ellen do
you understand that yes but Matthew is
dead and I am Brad now and what does
Brad want I don't know I'm thinking is
there a train from here to London
tomorrow yes we can put our bicycles on
the train we can get the next plane back
to America do you want to do that I
don't know I'm going to tell you
tomorrow
scene 6 in love with a ghost the next
day Brad and Jerry are in the street
jerry has two bags mrs. Finch is there
too you must leave then a week early yes
I'm sorry oh hello it's the American
boys are you going home to America
Jerry's going home mrs Morgan I'm
staying here at the hotel I'm going to
live here always Brad do you want to do
this think about Davis TV what are you
going to do here in England I don't know
but yes Davis TV needs a good man my dad
worked for years for Davis TV but now it
has a good man Jerry you me Oh Thank You
Brad that's ok i'm happy i'm in love she
waited for me and now I'm here I am
never going to leave her again
you