oxford bookworms stage 1 a ghost in love
and other plays by michael dean
published and copyright oxford
university press 2007
one ghost for the day one goes for the
night performed by Ben Elliot Lawrence
Kennedy sorry Martland coral and
children and Terry wilton
one ghost for the day one ghost for the
night scene 1 a ghost comes to Richard
little the year is 1653 it is a cold
dark winter night and Richard little a
man of forty is sitting in his chair he
is reading a book he hears something he
goes to the window looks out and then
goes back to the chair his wife Mary
comes in she is making a dress she has
the dress in her hand
Mary I can hear something outside
there's nothing there
read your book Richard come and sit with
me
no I'm making a dress I'm going upstairs
Mary please there's something out there
Oh Richard hello Richard are you James
James Heston but you sure did
yes I am dead but i can't find peace
because of you because of me why why
cause of me Beth had a new husband after
me that animal cage
yes Beth was a good woman and a good
sister to me
I said to her don't go with keech think
of James he's dead now she was kitchens
wife for only three months then she died
and now bitch has my son and he has my
son's money
ah I understand now
no you remember now before I died I said
to you my boy gets my money at 21 and
not before he is 8 now 8 and keech has
his money
I'm sorry about that but what can I do
you must get my boys money get it from
keech know bitch can kill me with one
hand he's big he always has a knife in
his pocket last year he killed a man
with that knife
I'm afraid of him James are you afraid
of me know
oh yes a little
you're a ghost only a little a look at
the table
oh no the table is moving
oh no oh the chair is moving now
and now my chair is moving James don't
do this to me at this minute teach is
building a new home in a village near
here with my son's money stop him
I'm sorry games I can't
I didn't want that was my hand but James
can you get in my head
can you tell my hand
yes Richard and your answer is going to
be yes or you are going to do this again
and again and again and I'm going mad
why does my hand throw a book when I
don't want to can all get people do this
can they get in a man's head so he moves
a chair or throws a book
oh yes now I can do it to you again or
you can say yes and get my son's money
which but how how can i get the money
from keech sit down I'm going to tell
you
scene 2 David key chin court in the
court we can see judge Tim's teach
Barker Reynolds Richard and Mary there
are six women and six men behind keech
they are from the village and they are
watching the trial judge Tim's is in a
big chair in front of the court
my name is Oliver barker and I speak for
Richard little here today judge Tim's I
speak for David keator here today
my name is phillip reynolds that key
took the boys money you can see it in
his face
Oh lil we must listen to one of her
barker and phillip reynolds first
teaches the boy Tom's father now a good
father doesn't take his sons money and
build a new house with it
be quiet in my court sorry Oliver Barker
you can begin judge Thames before James
Heston died he said this to Richard
little he said my boy gets my money at
21 and not before
at 21 and not before
yes judge but teach has this money now
the boys money he is building a big
house with it we all know that book each
imprison eyesight
mmm five years no.10 you don't eat in my
court
phillip reynolds speak George tens yes
there is a house in a village near here
and yes it is key to his house but the
money for it is not young Tom's money
not Tom's
money no judge Tim's it is David catches
money so one day
Keech is not rich and the next day he is
rich he has money for a house haha call
David cage David cage where is the boy
Tom's money do you have it at home
no he took the money it was Kate I said
he took the money I said that yesterday
I have the money here in this court and
then he teaching him whatever right
Sigmund hordes the money is under my
chair you woman
bring me the money they yes you hear you
are here
judge teams here Richard little here
look everybody here is the money so I
didn't take it from the boy you hear me
Richard little yes
one minute Richard little yes judge
Tim's you said teach took the boys money
you said that why why man why why i say
that because because because James
piston came to my home James Heston said
it to me to go scenes- did you Richard
little James Heston is data he died in
1651 talking to them hole that's in our
background judge Tim's my husband is ill
in our house he talks to people and
there is nobody there
can I take him home now please I'm not
ill stop
nothing be quiet all of you sit down
Mary thank you
yes James Heston is dead and yes James
Heston spoke to me I want James Heston
here now he can tell you
hey is l he's mine let's listen to him
yes we can listen to head be quiet
called James Reston I say call James
Heston to this court Heston is dead man
and Richard little is mad call James
Heston i am james Heston oh no no oh
please no it's Heston brain-dead James
Heston is it you did you speak to
Richard little yes
what did you say I told him teach took
my boys money and then keech killed a
man in the next village he was a rich
man he took his money
you see the money now here in this Court
yeah I can't kill Heston Heston is dead
but you you Richard little you brought
me to this Court
I'm going to kill you next stop him stop
him
it was Kate Kate stop the money I
thought that I said Kate still the money
this court says teach took the money and
keeps killed a man now find David keech
and bring him to me
scene 3 Keats finds Richard little
richard is sitting in his chair at home
what's that can I hear something
Mary is that you all know it's not James
again James is that you haha
all ohno ohno teach please no oh no not
Richard not my darling darling Richard
teach killed him
you're going to go to prison for this
keech
scene for a visit for keech in prison
teaches in prison he is sitting on his
bed he has a table a chair and a book
there too
hello what's that is there someone there
are my table
my table is moving huh
now the bench moving am I ill oh my head
oh now the chair is moving
what's happening why did I do that
am I mad it was my hand but your date
I killed you yes I'm dead and you killed
me but i'm not going away
I'm staying here in prison with you you
can't hit me now you can't hit a ghost
and you can't kill me again but we can
talk we have time for that we have all
day and you can do that all day to all
day all the time
yes now throw the book across the room
again and again and again and again home
no please are all my days going to be
like this
your days yes and for your night i have
a friend here
hello Richard hello David you
you here to yes David throw the book
across the room please thank you i'm
going to be here at night David and you
have Richard here every day
alright oh no no one ghost for the day
one ghost for the night
now throw the book across the room again
haha
sleep now my darling performed by ben
cohen canada gabon's Fiona mollison
Vince nichols and chris roe
sleep now my darling seen one Jenny must
stay at home it is a hot summer day
Jenni and Gilbert Lawson having
breakfast at a table in their garden
Gilbert is reading a book
Gilbert can I come with you to America
what Oh Gilbert please listen to me
I said can I come to America to mmm this
is good bread
did you make it yes Gil but I said can I
come with you know Jenny you have work
here there's the house the garden
I remember my new friend
it was your best film it was my best
film to they were happy days
yes I watched my new friend again last
week it's the best Gilbert Lawson film
and you were good in it my love you're a
good actress
the film had a good director Gilbert
Lawson oh thank you but now I have this
new film so I must go to America for six
weeks
Gilbert can I be in this film to I want
to be an actress again perhaps next time
would you like that
perhaps you can be in the next film you
said that before you don't
yes this bread is very good
can we go to America together then not
for a film just you and me
perhaps next year perhaps next year then
yes next year love I must go now I'm
going to be late for the plane i love
your journey
I love you too darling
seemed to Jenny talks to a film student
it is six weeks later
jenny is having a coffee at the airport
she is waiting for Gilbert's playing a
young man Henry sees her Henry has a big
bag in his hand
hello are you Jenny Lawson yes I knew it
here you are and do you want something
thanks sorry but do I know you a coke
for me please and a sandwich
one coke one sandwich
oh sorry yes I know your film my new
friend and I know Gilbert can I sit down
you can't stand up and have a coke into
sandwich
wait a minute I know you I know your
face but I can't remember
tell me how do you know Gilbert I'm
learning about his work
I know all the Gilbert Lawson films but
forget about me
I want to talk about you you aren't
happy i can see that what you can't say
that any sandwich
thank you ok sandwich is very good i
haven't for lunch sometimes
mmm yes you're right it's very good
thank you
that's ok goodbye then I must go soon
what do you do every day what I don't
know you you can't are any please tell
me what do you do every day
ok here's your answer I get up in the
morning and then I do nothing
we have no children a woman does the
house with me a man does the garden
do you have friends yes no
I have coffee with people i have dinner
with people we say things like nice
weather for the time of year but we
don't talk
yes I understand now i'm going to tell
you about me i'm 20 i go to America
sometimes I have friends I like films so
I make films
I'm happy what about you
I was happy when I was an actress there
there's your answer be an actress again
Jenny Lawson know what are you doing
here waiting for Gilbert and who is this
my name is Henry I'm a film student sit
down Laura please no I can't stop my
children are here we are all going to
America all the family I write books now
you know what do you do me nothing
have you got children no you look
unhappy Jenny at school you were
beautiful and good at everything and now
you are older with no work and no
children
oh dear what Laura why did you say that
I have to go now what
what's that name on your bag Henry
Gilbert person i know you now Gilbert
you are Gilbert when he was 20 years old
but why are you here
scene 3 Jenny learns about Gilbert there
are four people of the check-in woman
one woman to a man and Jenny's father
they're waiting a british airways man is
looking at father's plane ticket
Jenny runs in excuse me
Oh father what are you doing here
Jenny's smile be happy
what hey what was here before you
I was in front of you two are you okay
laughs she's white in the face excuse me
can you wait please know my name is
Jenny Lawson
Oh mrs. Lawson we found you at home
there was no answer
mrs. Lawson I'm sorry but mr. Lawson's
plane crashed in the SI he's dead
Oh No
scene for Jenny understands everything
Jenny's father and mother and Jenny are
all sitting at a table they all died all
the people on the plane
oh Jenny your mother and I are so sorry
my love thank you
why were you at the airport father me I
wasn't at the airport
yes you were you were at the british
airways check-in desk
you said be happy then you left
no wait a minute
hello Laura Laura this is Jenny Lawson
we were at school together
Laura I saw you at the airport remember
and oh what is laura's saying she said I
wasn't at the airport
Laura one question do you write books
now
yes thank you
she writes books is that important
yes Laura wants to write books so she
writes books and she's happy at the
airport father said be happy and Henry
Gilbert Lawson said be an actress again
I understand I understand now to my
darling husband i'm going to be an
actress for you again a good actress
thank you so sleep now like darling
a ghost in love performed by jennie
brice Rupert Farley crisp in redmond
patients Tomlinson
a ghost in love scene 1
Brad sees a ghost
Brad him Jerry come into the hotel room
and put their bags down it is a hot day
and they are wearing summer shirts
Brad sits on a bed man i want to drink
20 miles in one morning the bicycles
okay in the street in this little
village
oh yes nobody steals bicycles here
how do you know this is your first time
here first time in England or am I wrong
no you're right but I remember this
village I was here before Jerry I can
feel it
oh come on we were out in the Sun for
five hours
you need to drink some cold water my
friend this hotel opened in aiding 53
right right Brad you look to this book
before
no i didn't hey you know something
it's 115 my dad died at this minute on
this day last month
Oh bread I'm sorry no no it's okay i'm
going to go back to New York next week
after our three weeks in England and i'm
going to be Brad Davis of Davis TV dad
wanted that
yeah hey come on let's go out in the Sun
let's see the village have a drink find
some girls
no you go I like it here here in the
room
ok let's stay in the room
hey there's a television
hmm not working all forget it
no you're Brad Davis of Davis television
the biggest in America you must have a
television look shall I go down and ask
mrs. Finch you stay here you look tired
yeah thanks Jerry I am tired in 1760 the
hotel was a house a family called
Bannister lived in the house one day the
19 year old daughter Ellen I was never
19 I died at 18 yes I remember you
hello Ellen hello Matthew why does your
friend call you brad is that a name
yes it's an American named but you are
Matthew and i'm going to call you
Matthew always oh matthew i waited and
waited and waited for you i love you so
much do you love me
yes I think yes i do you think is that
an answer after all these years
Matthew Matthew do you remember
everything
no not everything I remember our love
and you died i remember that i wanted to
die too
and again last month I wanted to die
Oh Matthew don't say that
Matthew I'm so happy to see you again
Elam can IC you can we talk
oh yes
I want to talk to you about you okay
love you look white
this is not a happy time for Brad I'm
sorry love
do you want some dinner I make the best
dinner in the north of England
no thank you two up to me later then
write the television
it's ok now by Brad by Jerry have a nice
time in our village
mrs. Finch wait please do you know about
the banister family did you see the
ghost
Ellen banister yes what Brad you sort of
oh come on nowhere Ellen's always here
she likes young men she's always looking
for her boyfriend Matthews his name i
think mrs. Finch what happened how did
she die
what happened to Matthew you're
interested love i can see that there's
an old woman in the village their name
is more than scum she knows about Ellen
you ask more read this ghost
what did she say she she didn't speak
Jerry she said nothing at all
scene 2 Brad and Jerry want to know
about Ellen moored is a very old woman
her hair is white Brad and Jerry are
sitting at a table with her in her house
and lit Bannister a bad bad girl when
she looked at someone
the next day they were ill so she was a
witch
yes she looked at animals to then all
the cows in the village had no milk in
them to do you know this how do you know
how can you know
oh it's in all the books of villages
famous because of bad
Ellen banister
scene 3 was Ellen a witch
Brad and Jerry are in mrs. Morgan's
village shop there are two men and three
women in the shop and mrs Morgan yes a
you next
yes two cokes please
and two of those sandwiches I'm not
hungry man you must eat you can't sit in
your room all day I'm wait for a ghost
that's six pounds please what goes this
alan bannister yes do you know about
Ellen Bannister know people in our
village had no money then of course they
stole things and alan bannister sold
them she only wanted to help
was she a witch some people say that a
weight
no of course not
the men loved her she helped them you
see though women didn't love her so much
she was beautiful you see her boyfriend
was the bad one that Matthew it wasn't
her
Oh what did he do he stole things from
rich people then she sold them and he
took all the money he took all her money
too but she loved him did he love her
know he had two or three women
no he didn't he loved her he lifts for
her
who were you talking about that which
alan bannister she ate cats for
breakfast
oh don't listen to him don't listen to
these people you boys what happened to
Ellen Bannister you want to lay that
Matthew killed her
scene 4 where is Ellen now it is
nighttime Jerry is sitting on the bed
brad is walking up and down seven hours
we waited seven hours
where is she Jerry I said this before I
don't know just wait she isn't coming
because you're here
Brad I say again one I sleep here this
is my room too
I am your friend and I am NOT leaving
you like this
Jerry is this all a big laugh for you
no not now i want to see Ellen to I want
to help
okay thanks Jerry
sorry hey here she is Ellen Ellen it's
me brad Matthew man oh man it's all true
Ellen please tell me what happened in
1760 you must remember know we sold
things you and me rich people's things
you stole them remember Wow bread you
were robbing hood sorry the rich people
didn't like me they said bad things
about me
alan bannister is a wage they said that
but it's not true of course not
then one day they came for us twenty men
what happened we run away
you found a ship a ship go
into America you said see you at 115 at
the Harbor we can go away you and me and
then what happened
alum the ship went early i wasn't there
in time you went on the ship
you didn't wait for me oh no when I
arrived there were a lot of ships there
i didn't know the name of our ship
I looked for you I waited and waited and
waited
Ellen all Elam I'm sorry then the men
came they put me in prison I died three
months later and then I came back home
here and I waited again I waited for you
i love you Ellen I love you too Matthew
scene 5 what is brad going to do it is
dark
brad is standing at the window of the
room jury comes in
Brad always has his back to Jerry in
this scene
do you want to die do you want to go to
Ellen if for today
the answer was yes Matthew wanted to die
and go to be with Ellen do you
understand that yes but Matthew is dead
and I am Brad now and what does Brad
want i don't know i'm thinking is there
a train from here to London tomorrow
yes we can put our bicycles on the train
we can get the next plane back to
America do you want to do that i don't
know i'm going to tell you tomorrow
scene six in love with a ghost the next
day Brad and Jerry are in the street
jerry has two bags mrs. Finch's there to
you must leave then awake early
yes I'm sorry oh hello
it's the American boys are you going
home to America Jerry's going home
mrs Morgan I'm staying here at the hotel
i'm going to live here always
Brad do you want to do this think about
Davis TV what are you going to do here
in England I don't know but yes
Davis TV needs a good man
my dad worked for years for Davis TV but
now it has a good man Jerry you me
oh thank you brad that's okay i'm happy
i'm in love she waited for me and now
I'm here i am never going to leave her
again