love or money by rowena akinyemi read by
judy Bennett
chapter one the clocks and family lived
in the country near Cambridge about half
a mile from the nearest village and
about a mile from the river they had a
big old house with a beautiful garden a
lot of flowers and many old trees one
thursday morning in July
Jackie came in from the garden
she was a tall fat woman
30 years old it was the hottest day of
the year but she wore a warm brown skirt
and yellow shirt
she went into the kitchen to get a drink
of water
just then the phone rang
cambridge 1379 Jackie said hello this is
Diane I want to talk to mother mother
isn't here
Jackie said she's at the doctors
why what's wrong
nothing's wrong Jackie said yru
telephoning you are going to come this
weekend
mother wants everyone to be here
yes I want to come Diane said I'm
phoning because I
have no money for the train ticket no
money
mother is always giving you money
this phone call is very expensive
Diane said coldly tell mother please I
need the money
Jackie put the phone down
she took a cigarette from her bag and
began to smoke
she felt angry because her sister always
asked for money
Diane was 20 years old the youngest in
the family
she lived in London in one room of a big
house she wanted to be a singer
she sang very well but she could never
get work
Jackie went back into the kitchen and
began to make some sandwiches
just then the back door opened and her
mother came in
it's very hot
Molly said she took off her hat and put
it down on the table
she was a tall dark woman with beautiful
eyes
two big black dogs came into the kitchen
after her and ran across to her shes
sat down and put her hands on their
heads
Jackie put the sandwiches on the table
mother she said Diane phoned she wants
money for her train ticket
Molly closed her eyes for a minute then
she stood up this afternoon
I want you to get the house ready for
the weekend
she said oh and please go to the village
later and get my tablets
Yes Mother Jackie said Molly went to the
door
mother please wait a minute
Jackie said Peter Hobbs came here this
morning
he's very angry with you about that
letter he lost his job you know why did
you write to his office he wants to talk
to you about it
well I don't want to talk to him
Molly said she opened the door
but mother you don't understand
he's 17 and it was his first job
he is very very angry he says he says
he's going to kill you
Molly did not answer
she went out of the room and close the
door
chapter 2
it was seven o'clock on saturday evening
Jackie stood at the window a car drove
slowly up to the front door and stopped
at all man with white hair got out it
was Albert the husband of Molly's sister
here's Uncle Albert
Jackie said always late
she went out of the room and opened the
front door
Albert came in and went at once to Molly
Oh
dear I'm very late
I am sorry Albert said 50 years old
today
what a wonderful dress
Molly did not smile
Thank You Albert we're all getting older
tonight she wore a long black dress and
the two black dogs sat at her feet
everyone is here now let's go in to
dinner
she said everyone stood up and went to
the table the table looks nice
Jackie what wonderful flowers
Diane said she was a beautiful girl with
long black hair and dark blue eyes
she wore a long red dress
Albert sat down next to roger roger was
Molly's son her second child
he lived in cambridge in an expensive
house
someone called Peter stopped me down the
road
Albert said who is he he is
very angry with you Molly
that's Peter Hobbs from the house across
the road
Jackie said quickly she looked across
the table at Molly
he lost his job last week and he's angry
with everyone its Molly
he doesn't like Albert said Molly said
nothing
everyone began to eat
how is aunt Annie
Jackie asked she's much worse now
Albert said she stays in bed all the
time
she needs a nurse 24 hours a day
I am sorry Molly said Albert stopped
eating and looked
Molly it's very difficult and very
expensive you know Annie feels very
unhappy because you don't visit our
Molly she loves you very much
you are her little sister you know Molly
closed her eyes for a minute
I know that Albert I am 50 years old but
i am always her little sister
well we can talk about it later
Albert laughed oh yes
yeah we can talk later it's always later
with you
Molly always tomorrow
never today Jackie watched her mother
her mother was angry with Albert Molly
never liked talking about her sister
Annie and she did not like visiting her
because she was very ill
that's a beautiful dress
Diane is it new Jackie asked
Thank You Jackie yes it's new and very
expensive
I got it on Wednesday Diane said she
smiled at Jackie all your things are
expensive
Jackie said she remembered the phone
call on thursday about the train ticket
I don't like cheap things
Diane said and i'm going to need more
money soon
I want to go to America
can you help me Roger oh no Roger
said nobody wants to help you Diane
you don't like working
we all know that but we all want you to
get a job Diane laughed
it doesn't matter Roger I don't need
your help
mother always helps me mother loves me
best
she suddenly smiled a quick beautiful
smile
but her eyes were cold
Jackie looked at her mother
Molly's face was white
Jackie did not understand was her mother
afraid of Diane Jackie wanted her mother
to be happy today
would you like some more meat
Uncle Albert Jackie asked Roger
can you give everyone some more to drink
Roger got up and began to give more wine
- everyone this is good wine
he said Molly smiled for the first time
yes your father loved this wine
he often drank it yes
Albert said and looked at Molly
expensive too
would you like to meet mr. breaks this
weekend Roger
Jackie ask quickly he's the new man at
the farm
he wants to meet you Briggs Briggs
Molly said suddenly angry don't talk to
me about that man
I don't like him he wants half my garden
for his farm he needs more land he says
I don't want him in my house
he's always dirty and he has bad teeth
Jackie stood up and got her bag
excuse me I want a cigarette
cigarettes always a cigarette in your
mouth
Molly said I don't like it
cigarettes aren't good for you
Jackie began to smoke
she felt angry but she said nothing she
wanted her mother to be happy this
evening but it was very difficult
Roger
look some more wine well mother
perhaps mr. breaks is right
the garden is very big
you know he said it's a lot of work for
you
the house is big - you're 50 now you
need to be more careful
Roger I don't need a nurse
you know I work in the garden every day
I feel happy there
Molly stood up
I know you all want my money
you come here for a free dinner
you don't want to see me you don't love
me you want my house and my money
well you can all wait
nobody is getting more money from me
not before I die don't say that mother
Jackie cried
Molly walked across the room to the door
I feel ill now I'm going upstairs to bed
Molly left the room
nobody moved one day I'm going to kill
Diane said quietly
Roger looked at Diane but said nothing
Albert moved his head slowly up and down
ill she's angry that's all he said
Molly always gets angry about money
why can't she be good to her sister Inez
going to die soon
Molly knows that Jackie finished a
cigarette and stood up
would everyone like some coffee
come into the kitchen and let's drink it
there
chapter three early next morning the
house
it was quiet suddenly there was a cry
from the room next to rogers his
mother's room
Roger opened his eyes and looked at the
clock it was nearly seven o'clock he got
out of bed and opened the door quietly
at the same time the door of his
mother's room opened and Diane came out
her face was very white
Roger its mother
I brought a cup of coffee for her and I
found her dead she's dead dead in her
bed she cried
Roger went quickly to the door of his
mother's room and looked in the window
was open but the room was warm
molly was on the bed one hand under her
head
Roger went to cross to the bed and put
his hand on her arm
it was cold on the little table next to
the bed was a hot cup of coffee and an
empty Cup
I'm going to cool
dr. Diane said she's dead
Roger
slowly his face to was white mother is
dead
Diane walked across the room to the door
I'm going to phone the doctor she said
again
wait a minute Roger
called let's tell the family first
family
nobody loved mother Diane went out and
ran downstairs
Roger slowly went downstairs after her
and stood by the telephone
dr. Pratt
this is Diane clocks and it's my mother
she's dead
can you come quickly
Diane put the phone down
it isn't true
Roger mother yet daddy died last winter
and now mother Diane began to cry
don't
hey Diane Roger said let's go upstairs
and tell Uncle Albert and Jackie
no you tell them
nobody loved mother you want sorry
look at you you want her money that's
all
Roger suddenly wanted to hit
Diane be quiet
he said what about you
you didn't love mother
you wanted her money too
don't forget that it's true
Diane said oh I can't stay in this house
I'm going out I'm going to the river
with the dogs
no Roger said the doctors coming and I
I want you here Diane said nothing she
went into the kitchen and at once the
dogs got up and came to her beautiful
dogs
daddy loved you and mother loved you
now i'm going to love you
she opened the back door and went out
with the dogs
Roger did
move he stood by the telephone
it's true he thought I am happy about
the money I needed money and now I'm
rich
things are going to be easier for me now
but mother why didn't I love her more
and now she's dead
slowly
Roger went back upstairs he wanted to
dress before dr. Pratt arrived
dr. Pratt was a little fat man without
much hair
he was the family doctor and he knew all
the clocks and family very well he went
upstairs at once and looked at mollies
body
he looked carefully at the cup of coffee
and the empty cup on the table next to
her bed
I'm sorry Roger
he said where is Diane
she found me she went out with the dogs
Roger said she was angry with me
Aang
everyone dr. Pratt said nothing for a
minute
this is going to be very difficult
I'm going to foam the police
Roger police
why what's wrong
I don't know your mother was until I saw
her on thursday and she was very well
why did she die
I don't understand
I want to find out Roger went across to
the window and looked out at the garden
it was a beautiful summer morning
the sky was blue and the garden was
Green
it was all very quiet
his mother loved this garden but Tom
Briggs wanted the garden and Roger
wanted the garden - Roger felt worse and
worse
your mother took sleeping tablets
dr. Pratt said did you know on thursday
she had a new bottle of tablets but i
can't find it here in her room
I didn't know Roger said Mary
well let's go downstairs and you can
phone the police Roger went into the
kitchen and made some coffee
just then Diane came in with the dogs
Roger she said look I'm sorry I was
angry and said some angry things
it doesn't matter Roger said here you
are
have some coffee dr. Pratt is phoning
the police did you know mother took
sleeping tablets
well the bottle is not in her room
what I don't understand
Diane took the coffee and began to drink
her eyes look big and dark
just then dr. Pratt came into the
kitchen
they're coming at once he said Diane I
sorry about your mother
dr. Pratt I want to tell you about last
night
everyone was very angry
be quiet Roger said quickly
Diane never thinks before she opens her
mouth
he thought angrily Diane did not look at
Roger last night mother went to bed
early because everyone
don't tell me dr. Pratt said you can
tell the police
Rogers face went red sudden
only he felt afraid the police are going
to talk to everyone and ask questions
he thought and they're going to want
answers
it's going to be very difficult
he finished his coffee and stood up
I'm going upstairs
he said I'm going to tell Uncle Albert
and Jackie about mother and about the
police
chapter fool
the police arrived very quickly
there were a lot of them some of them
with cameras went upstairs to Molly's
room two detectives talked to dr. Pratt
in the kitchen
the family waited in the sitting room
it was a hot day again and the windows
were open the dogs SAT quietly at
Diane's feet
nobody talked Jackie smoked
they waited for a long time
suddenly the door opened and the two
detectives came in
good morning i am detective inspector
Walsh and this is sergeant foster the
inspector did not smile
he was a big man in an old black suit
and a black hat and coat he wore a coat
because he always felt cold last night
someone put sleeping tablets in mrs.
Clarkson's hot milk
we are going to question everybody and
we need a room please
Rogers stood up
I'm Roger Clarkson
you can have my father's old office
come with me it's along here
the office was not a very big room but
there was a table and three or four
chairs
Roger opened the window
i would like to talk first to your uncle
albert king
inspector Walsh said he took off his hat
and coat and sat down behind the table
of course said
nature and left the room sergeant foster
waited by the door
he was a very tall young man with black
hair and a nice smile
he was not very happy this morning
because he usually played tennis on
sunday mornings
he was one of the best players at the
cambridge Tennis Club
Albert came in and sat down i'm going to
ask some questions mr. king
the inspector said and Sergeant Foster
is going to write it all down
Albert looked at his feet
yes yes it's your job
I know that tell me about last night
inspect to wash asked quietly you were
angry with mrs. Clarkson Albert looked
at inspect to wash for the first time
yes I was
everyone was angry roger was angry die
man wanted money to go to America
then there's a man called Tom drinks he
wants half the garden for his farm
molly was a rich woman
I need money because my wife Annie
Molly's sister is very ill I told Molly
this
what happened next
well molly was angry with everyone and
went upstairs
we went into the kitchen for coffee
Jack
he wanted everyone to go up and say
goodnight to Molly
she lives here with Molly
so she wanted Molly to be happy at first
Roger said no he was angry and didn't
want to see his mother and did you see
Molly in her room
yes i was tired and I went upstairs
first
I went to Molly's room and asked her for
money again
but no there was no money for her sister
Albert stopped and put his hand over his
eyes
inspector Walsh watch Talbot for a
minute
did you hear noises after you went to
bed
everyone went into Molly's room to say
good night
I think later I heard someone he or she
went downstairs
that was about midnight
very
all mr. king thank you you can go now
Albert left the room
inspector Walsh put his hands behind his
head
what time
it I'm hungry we're learning a lot but i
need some coffee
shall I go to the kitchen
sergeant foster asked oh no later
let's see Jackie clocks and next Jackie
came in and sat down she looked down at
her hands and said nothing
we found the empty bottle of your
mother's sleeping tablets in Diane's
room
the inspector said suddenly then he
waited
Jackie's face did not change and she
said nothing
tell me did your mother get her tablets
from the shop in the village
yes my mother usually took a sleeping
tablet every night so she needed a lot
of tablets
sometimes she got them from the shop
sometimes I did on Thursday I asked
Peter Hobbs to get them
he lives in the house across the road
and he often goes to the village on his
bicycle
I see your mother
I wanted to stay in this house
how about you did you want to move
Jackie looked up for a minute and then
down at her hands again this is mother's
house
I loved my mother she was good to me
did you see your mother in her room last
night
yes everyone did Diane made hot milk and
took it to mother she usually drank a
cup of hot milk before she slept
inspector Walsh put his hands behind his
head
jackie was very quiet
what did your mother say Jackie opened
her bag and looked for a cigarette
can i smoke of course this is your house
inspector Walsh said he watched
Jackie what did your mother say he asked
again
she wanted to go downstairs again
she remembered the dogs
she wanted to get some dinner for them
I went to my room and she went
downstairs
what time was this
I don't remember that
about midnight I think and the
up of hot milk it was on the table by
her bed
did you need your mother's money
no inspector money is not important to
me
there are more important things
Jackie said quietly well your uncle
albert wanted money
palm brings wanted the garden
you wanted nothing
Jackie finished a cigarette and looked
up at the inspector
her eyes were suddenly angry
don't forget to Peter Hobbs
he lost his job because of my mother
he wanted to kill her you know
and what about Diane you found the empty
bottle in her bag
inspector Walsh listened carefully
we're going to question everyone is
Clarkson Jackie said nothing for a
minute
would you like some sandwiches and
coffee
inspector ah yes please
inspector Walsh said warmly I would like
sandwiches and coffee very much
Jackie left the room instead
- Walsh thought about her why was she
suddenly angry
the room was quiet
chapter 5
after the car
and sandwiches inspector Walsh called
Roger Clarkson to the office
Roger came in and sat down the inspector
began at once
now mr. Clarkson
why was your mother angry with you last
night
this house is very big
Roger said it was a lot of work for
mother
I wanted her to move but no she loved
this house and garden
she didn't want to move
tell me about your job mr. Clarkson
your mother is dead and now you're rich
do you need money Rogers face was
suddenly afraid
what are you saying I didn't kill my
mother
I need money
that's true a friend and i want to build
10 houses here in this garden we can get
a lot of money for them so i wanted
mother to sell this house
it's true but mr. Briggs wanted half the
garden to you know that his farm
inspector Walsh moved a pencil on the
table
- L
me what happened upstairs
you went to your mother's room
yes I did
I wanted to say goodnight to my mother
did you talk about the house again
yes I did again she said no she loved
the house and didn't want to sell it
inspector Walsh watched Roger for a
minute
I see we found
on the empty bottle of sleeping tablets
mr. Clarkson in Diane's room
Rogers face did not change
Oh someone put them there
Diane did not kill my mother
I know that she found the body very well
i would like to see Diane next
Roger got up and left the room
inspector Walsh stood up and put his
hands in his pockets
he went to the window and looked out the
trees
why was Roger parks and afraid
was it important hello
it's sergeant foster tomorrow morning
go to mr. Clarkson's office
you have the name he said ask some
questions about him about his job
friends money sergeant foster wrote it
down
yes inspector a good day for tennis
sergeant sergeant foster laughed
no don't say that it's not easy you know
I don't like sitting here looking at the
Sun Diane came into the room and sat
down she looked at sergeant foster and
smiled
I saw you at the Tennis Club last month
I think
you play very well sergeant Foster's
face went red
inspector Walsh looked at him
oh yes are far
test and exciting player is sergeant
foster Diane smiled again sergeant
foster and his face went red
well miss clocks on inspector Walsh said
I want you to talk about last night
then stop smiling
oh I can talk about last night
I can't stop talking about it
we were all angry mother went to bed
early and I made hot milk for her
we were all in the kitchen and Peter
Hobbs came in he nearly broke the back
door down
I am stopped
yes he was very angry about a letter he
wanted to kill mother
are you going to talk to him
we're going to talk to everyone
good Tom Briggs came into the kitchen -
are you going to talk to him
I
I'm asking the questions miss Clarkson
when did you take the milk upstairs
I went up after Roger
she stopped for a minute then she began
again
I didn't like my mother
inspector she killed my father you know
last winter after Christmas
she drove the car into a tree and killed
my father
inspector Walsh watch Diane's face
carefully i see so you wanted to kill
your mother Diane laughed
I wanted to kill her but I didn't I can
tell you a lot of things about this
family inspector
everyone wanted mother to die
Uncle Albert wanted her money for his
wife Annie and then my brother he needs
a lot of money
he has an expensive house and an
expensive car and think of Jackie do you
know that Jackie didn't like mother a
long time ago a nice boy worked here
he was the gardener Jackie loved him
very much but mother said know a guy
nah was not a good husband for a clucks
and down inspector Walsh listened
quietly all this was very interesting
but was it important
perhaps water happy family the plaque
sins were we
on the empty bottle of sleeping tablets
in your room
inspector Walsh said quietly
he watched her face carefully
Diane stood up suddenly her face
angry what I didn't put it there
I'm not going to listen to this
she ran out of the room
well well well inspector Walsh said she
likes you sergeant
you need to be careful
Sarge
and foster laughed at his face went red
again
someone put sleeping tablets in Molly's
hot milk
the inspector said all the family were
in the kitchen last night
Peter Hobbs and tom briggs were there to
one of them killed Molly inspector Walsh
got his hat and coat
come on we need to talk to Peter Hobbs
and Tom Briggs let's get some more
coffee first
I'd like a sandwich - I'm hungry again
chapter 6
they found Peter Hobbs under his car an
old green car
he got up slowly
he wore old blue trousers and a dirty
orange shirt
we want to talk about mrs. clocks and
inspector Walsh said oh it's about her
Peter said he looked at the inspector
I know she's dead
someone in the village told me why did
you go to the clocks in this house last
night
Jackie wanted me to come and see her
brother Roger you're angry
she said , and tell Roger
I went to the house but nobody opened
the door so i made a lot of noise and
then they opened the door
old mrs. clocks and wasn't there but I
told Roger
I told them all Peter hit the car with
his hand
I wanted to kill that woman
I lost my job my first job because of
her last month I was in trouble with the
police and that all woman wrote to my
office and she told them about the
police
I wanted to kill her
take it easy
inspector Walsh said what happened next
he gave me some coffee but her brother
didn't listen to me
Peter said angrily then Tom Briggs came
in he wanted to talk to Roger - but
Roger didn't listen to him
jackie was very unhappy she nearly cried
then I went home
that's all I see
I'll tell me about the tablets
you went to the village on Thursday
tablets
oh yes I remember
Jackie wanted me to get her mother's
tablets from the village
I go to the village on my bicycle
this car doesn't work thank you Peter
that's all that's all
Peter laughed angrily you're going to
come back
I know that I know the police
Tom Briggs farm was about half a mile
away near the river
it was not a big farm and the
house was old and dirty not much money
here
inspector Walsh said Tom Briggs was a
young man about 30 years old with dirty
hands and bad teeth
what's wrong excuse me
I meet in my dinner he said we can wait
an issue dinner
inspector Walsh said we want to ask one
or two questions about last night
come and wait in the front room
Tom said and opened the door inspector
Walsh looked at the things in the front
room
there was an old black and white
television and some books on the table
there was a picture of a
happy young girl with long brown hair on
the table to inspector Walsh looked at
the picture for a long time
who was the girl Tom brakes came back
into the front room finished
inspector Walsh asked you know mrs.
Clarkson is dead
Tom Briggs sat down suddenly on the
nearest chair
what how did she die
when did it happen I was there last
night she died last night or early this
morning
what did you do last night
may why are you asking me
I went there to meet mr. Cox and Roger
I'm losing money on this farm and I need
more land
I want half mrs. Clarkson's garden
you went into the kitchen
what did you do next can you remember
Tom Briggs looked at sergeant foster and
and back at inspect the wharf
oh you remember it very well
all the family were in the kitchen
Peter Hobbs was there too
I talked to Roger he wants his mother to
sell the house but he wants the land he
doesn't want me to have it but now mrs.
Clarkson is dead
what's going to happen now
inspector Walsh got up and took the
picture of the girl from the table
who's this Tom's face went red
who all
that's a friend it's not
it was a long time ago
the two detectives walked back to the
Clarkson's house through the garden
it was beautiful green and quiet
inspector Walsh felt tired and hungry
who killed Molly
he knew the answer now but he needed to
ask one or two more questions
let's go sergeant
he said and put on his hat again
tomorrow is a new day
- 7:00 on monday morning sergeant foster
went to rogers office and ask some
questions and then
he went to alberts house and ask some
more questions
inspector Walsh sat in his office and
telephoned he made phone calls about
Peter Hobbs and he made phone calls
about Tom breaks and then he had some
coffee and sandwiches at three o'clock
the two detectives drove to the
Clarkson's house
I would like to see everyone
he told Roger everyone came into the
sitting room and sat down inspector
Walsh stood in front of the windows and
looked at them one by one
I want to talk to you
someone killed Molly clocks
someone put sleeping tablets in her hot
milk and killed her
nobody wanted to tell me the true story
but now I know the true story and i'm
going to tell you the two dogs came
slowly into the room and sat down
Diane's feet it was very quiet in the
room
the inspector look Talbot
mr.
king your wife is very ill and needs a
nurse
you told me this
you didn't tell me about your house
you're selling your house next month
because you need the money
Albert was angry last year I asked
Molly's husband for some money and he
said yes but then he died in an accident
accident
Diane cried that was no accident
mother killed daddy
because she wanted his money
let's talk
are you now Diane said inspector Walsh
you visited your mother every month and
you took money from her last month she
gave you money for your television
this month she gave you money for your
telephone every month
you told your mother it was no accident
you killed daddy i'm going to tell the
police
your mother was afraid of the police
and so she gave you the money but in the
end she wanted to stop you
she told dr. Pratt
no more money
she told dr. Pratt on Thursday and on
Saturday
she died you took the hot milk to your
mother
what did she do
tell you
Diane began to cry I loved daddy
he always gave money to me he loved me
it was mother she didn't love daddy
and she didn't love me
Diane stopped the dogs got up and went
to the door
it's true i took a lot of money from
mother on saturday she told me no more
money
I wanted to kill her but I didn't
the dog
this came back and sat down again
Diane's feet
inspector Walsh looked at Roger
mr. Clarkson also needed money
Rogers face went red
don't tell them please mr. Clarkson lost
his job last month he has no money but
he has an expensive house and an
expensive car
he likes expensive things
his sister's looked at him but Roger put
his hand over his eyes
don't talk to me it doesn't matter now
Diane said mother is dead and we have a
lot of money
you don't need a job
Rogers face went red again
be quiet Diane now inspector Walsh began
again Peter Hobbs is a very angry young
man
mrs. Clarkson was not very nice to him
he got the sleeping tablets from the
shop but did he put the tablets in the
hot milk
I think not Tom Briggs
wanted half the garden for his farm he
was in the kitchen that night did he put
sleeping tablets in the hot milk
I think not sudden
and terrain for a minute
everyone watched it through the window
Jackie took a cigarette from her bag and
began to smoke but someone wanted Peter
Hobbs to come into the kitchen that
night she wanted everyone to see him and
listen to him
inspector Walsh said she I don't
understand
Roger began and stopped
inspector Walsh moved away from the
window and sat down
I'm
tell you the true story now
misc locsin you wanted Peter Hobbs to
come to the house that night he was very
angry with your mother
because of that letter he said I want to
kill her and you wanted everyone to hear
that
why
Jackie's face went white it's not true
what about Diane you found the empty
bottle in her bag
Diane stood up in my back
Jackie what are you talking about
be quiet please
and sit down inspector Walsh said he
looked at Jackie its
we found the bottle in Diane's bank but
how do you know that we didn't tell you
you did before you told me before
no we
around the empty bottle in Diane's room
we told you that you talked about
Diane's back
we didn't tell you sergeant foster wrote
it all down
inspector Walsh looked carefully at
Jackie a long time ago
you knew Tom breaks
he was the gardener here and you loved
him but your mother didn't like him
Jackie put her hands to her head
no no we found your picture an old one
in mr. Briggs house you were younger
then and your
there was long last year
Tom Briggs came back and you wanted him
he loved you too but he had no money
he wanted the garden for his farm he
wanted money he wanted you but your
I said no in the end you wanted to kill
your mother and you did kill her
your mother went downstairs to see the
dogs and you put the sleeping tablets in
her hot
nope later you put the empty bottle in
Diane's bag
Jackie stood up haha
dark and afraid you don't understand
she cried mother gave me nothing
all those years I wanted to be happy to
be with Tom
that's all I love Tom and he loves me
but mother said no always know
then she began to cry
nobody looked at her
Jackie left the house in a police car
inspector Walsh watched and then walk
slowly to his car he felt tired and
hungry
he stopped and looked
back at the house well he said to
sergeant foster in the end they got the
money
Albert Roger Diane
they're all rich now but I
they going to be happy he got into the
car
let's go he said I'm hungry
I
need a sandwich
yeah