colors
head is a vibrant color roses are some
red blood is red white is the color of
snow clouds are very often
white blue is the color of the sky and
the ocean
black isn't really a color at all
tar is black a crow is black green is
the color of grass
it is also the color of leaves on the
trees in the summer
Brown is the color of dirt
many people have brown hair yellow is a
bright color
most people use yellow when they draw a
picture of the Sun orange is an easy
color to remember that is because an
orange is orange pink is the color that
we dress baby girls in we dress baby
boys in blue purple is the color of some
violets the canadian flag is red and
white
what color is your flag
wild animals
some animals
child they don't live in homes or cages
they live in jungles or on planes
the lion is the king of the beasts he is
very mighty he roars loudly the giraffe
has a long neck
he eats leaves from the tallest trees
the elephant is very large
he has a trunk and two tusks a tiger has
stripes some bears are black and some
are brown
there are even white bears called polar
bears a kangaroo lives in Australia
that is the only place that you would
find a kangaroo
except in a zoo it might be frightening
to run into a wolf or a fox monkeys run
and play in the trees in Canada we don't
see lions tigers giraffes or monkeys
running wild
there are squirrels in my backyard
sometimes I see a raccoon or a chipmunk
in Northern Ontario you might see a
moose or a bear
I have seen a deer in the forest there
are many wild animals
you can see wild animals if you go to
the zoo
months
there are 12 months in the year january
is the first month of the year
it is usually cold in january-february
is the second month of the year it is
still winter when februari comes
they say that March comes in like a lion
and goes out like a lamb
that means that it is still usually cold
and sometimes stormy when march begins
by the time that march ends
the weather is starting to get a little
better April is the rainy month april
showers bring May flowers
many of the spring flowers bloom in May
the weather can be quite mild in May
June is usually a nice warm month
many people get married in June July can
be hot
people have vacations in July it is a
month to do summer things
it is still summer in August both the
summer is winding down
August is the time to have last minute
vacations in September we go back to
school
the autumn winds begin to blow October
really feels like autumn
October is Halloween time november is
when we really start to feel the chill
December is the Christmas month most
people do a lot of christmas shopping in
December they spend quite a bit of time
getting ready for Christmas
all of the months are different which
month were you born in
days of the week
there are seven days of the week sunday
is a day of rest for some people but
many people still have to work quite a
few people go to church on a Sunday on
monday morning we go back to school
after the weekend
many people say they don't like monday
because it is the beginning of the work
week tuesday is a school day and a
working day I don't think that there is
anything special about a Tuesday
Wednesday is the middle of the work week
on thursday
many of the stores and malls stay open
later
it gives you a chance to run some
errands on a Thursday night on friday
you feel like the work week is nearly
over
some people say thank goodness it is
friday they look forward to the weekend
on Saturday many people can sleep in
late
people get errands done on saturday you
see a lot of people in the grocery store
on a Saturday
most children look forward to saturday
so that they can play with their friends
then sunday comes again
the week's turn into months and the
months turned into years time goes by
quite quickly
describing things
some things are different shapes they
can be described by their shape
a circle is round a compact disc is a
circle a square has four equal sides a
rectangle is similar but two of the
sides are longer a triangle has only
three sides have you ever seen anyone
play a triangle in an orchestra the word
triangle can stand for an instrument or
shape an oval is rounded but it is not
round an egg is an oval shape
the floor is flat if something is smooth
it has no bumps or lumps silk is smooth
some things are rough sandpaper is rough
if something is dull it is not sharp or
pointed a dome knife will not cut bread
because the blade is not sharp
if something is pointed it has a sharp
and a sharp pencil has a pointed end a
pencil that has been used a lot and
hasn't been sharpened has a dull end
some things are soft a teddy bear is
soft it feels good to touch
some things are hard a rock is hard soft
can also represent a noise level if you
have a soft voice it is not very loud
if someone tells you to speak softly
they want you to speak quietly loud is
the word used to describe noises that
hurt your ears a big truck will make a
loud noise sometimes your mother will
tell you that your music is too loud
fruit
some fruit grows on trees apples grow on
trees you can get red yellow or green
apples some apples are green until they
ripen then they turn red
peaches grow on trees peaches have a
fuzzy skin cherries grow on trees you
can climb a ladder and pick cherries
from the tree
cherries and peaches have pits inside
them
the pits are not edible pairs also grow
on trees
lemons grow on trees they are very sour
have you ever picked strawberries
strawberries do not grow on trees
you have to bend down to pick
strawberries have you ever tried
strawberry shortcake
it is very good grapes grow on vines
people use grapes to make wine
there are many types of berries there
are blackberries blueberries raspberries
and cranberries just to name a few
some fruits are more exotic there are
mangoes and papayas
they don't grow in Canada bananas and
oranges
don't grow in a Canadian climate either
but we are able to buy them here some
fruits have to be peeled and some can be
eaten as they are
it is always a good idea to wash fruit
before you eat it
the farmers spray the crops with
pesticides to kill bugs
so it is good to wash that off
bugs
many people are
of bugs some bugs do bad things like
eating crops or close some bugs such as
termites even eat wood other bugs can be
good
spiders catch flies flies are not good
because they carry germs insects get
caught in the web that the spider builds
ants get into homes and eat food
bees are good because honey comes from
bees
it is not good if you get stung by a bee
a caterpillar turns into a butterfly
butterflies can be very beautiful you
can find grasshoppers outside on a sunny
day
grasshoppers hop through the grass
crickets make a noise by rubbing their
legs together
dragonflies usually live near water
they have large colorful wings ladybugs
are red with little black dots
there are many types of beetles nobody
wants to have cockroaches in their house
centipedes have many legs
please get on to your pets and bite them
they make your dog or cat itchy
mosquitoes can make you itchy when they
might you have you ever had a mosquito
bite
the kitchen
the kitchen is where we make and eat our
meals there is a stove in the kitchen
inside the stove there is an oven where
you bake things you can put a cake into
the oven to bake on top of the stove are
burners the burners get hot
you put pots or pans on the burners
the refrigerator is where we store the
food that needs to be kept cold
we keep milk eggs cheese and vegetables
in the refrigerator at the top of the
refrigerator is the freezer the freezer
keeps things frozen we have frozen
vegetables ice cream and ice cubes in
the freezer
we have a toaster in the kitchen you put
the bread in the toaster and it turns
into toast
we have an electric kettle we boil water
to make tea in the kettle
there is a double sink in the kitchen
that is where we wash the dishes we turn
on the hot tap and put some dish
detergent into the sink to wash the
dishes
sometimes we put the dishes into the
dishwasher and the dishwasher washes the
dishes
there are other things in the kitchen
there are utensils like knives forks and
spoons
there are details and dish cloths there
are oven mitts and pot holders to take
hot things out of the oven
there are pots to cook and boil things
in there are pans to fry things we have
dishes that we eat from we have plates
for our dinner and bowls that we can put
our soup in we drink from cops or coffee
mugs or glasses
we keep our juice in a picture or a jug
there is a timer that you can set when
you are cooking the timer buzzes when
the food is ready
we also have a microwave oven in the
kitchen if we are in a hurry
we cook our food in the microwave
vegetables
vegetables are very good for you they
say that you should have three servings
of vegetables every day
I like green peas peas come in pods
i also like snow peas you eat the pods
on the snow peas
I like corn when it is on the cob
carrots are good to eat raw beans are
good for you
there are many different types of beans
there are string beans kidney beans
baked beans and lots of other types of
beans
some people don't like green vegetables
like broccoli and Brussels sprouts
I like broccoli and Brussels sprouts you
can make a salad and put lots of
different vegetables into the salad in
my salads
I like lettuce tomatoes celery cucumber
radishes cauliflower and spring onions
I tried to have a salad with dressing on
it every day
my dad likes root vegetables like beets
and parsnips
my brother will only eat potatoes he
likes his potatoes baked my mother likes
to buy her vegetables at the market
she says they are fresher there my
mother buys a lot of onions
she put onions in almost all the meals
that she cooks some children won't eat
their vegetables
I didn't like some vegetables at first
but I have become used to them
I like having vegetables with my meals
pets
there are many different animals that
you
have for pets the most common pets are
cats and dogs
I think the second most common pets are
birds and fish
you can hug a cat or a dog you can play
with a cat or a dog but it is difficult
to play with a bird or fish
some birds are very smart and they can
be taught to do things parents are very
clever
some of them even talk birds usually
stay in bird cages fish have to stay in
the water in a tank or a fishbowl
some people have gerbils or guinea pigs
as pets
there are even people who have ferrets
I have a friend who has a lizard for a
pet
she has to buy live crickets for her
lizard to eat another friend of mine has
a pet snake
I don't think i would like to have a pet
snake
there are different types of dogs
some dogs are very big and some art
small a Labrador Retriever is a big dog
a poodle is usually a small dog
although there are some large puddles
some dogs are noisy and they bark a lot
other dogs are quiet and obedient
I once had a dog it was a cocker spaniel
I used to take it for walks there are
different types of cats to my favorite
type of cat is a siamese cat Siamese
cats have blue eyes
my mother had a Persian cat it was very
furry
my mother said that it used to shed fur
all over the house pets are a lot of fun
but they are a lot of work to to be a
good pet owner you have to be very
responsible
parties
parties can be a lot
no fun people get invited to parties
you can have a party because it is a
special occasion or just because you
want to have a party
sometimes people wear paper hats at
parties
these are called party hats some people
decorate with streamers and balloons at
some parties there is a cake
sometimes there are just snacks and
drinks at some parties people play games
there are also parties where people just
stand around and talk
people wear different things to parties
you can go to some parties in casual
clothes and other parties
you need to be dressed up in good
clothes there are other parties where
you are supposed to wear a costume
there are many different kinds of
parties there are christmas parties
birthday parties going away parties and
parties for no reason at all
I have been to parties for people who
are retiring or for people who have just
had a new baby
there are hundreds of reasons for having
a party at some parties you take a gift
if it is a birthday party
then you take a gift and a birthday card
to the person who is having the birthday
sometimes people will ask you to bring
food or drinks to the party
all parties are different it is nice to
be invited to parties
grocery shopping
what do you see when you go to the
grocery store
the aisles are filled with food there
are also refrigerators and freezers
filled with food
there are sometimes things in bins in
the middle of the Isles
there are different departments in the
grocery store
there is the bakery in the bakery
there are sweet things such as cakes
pies cookies and tarts
there are also things that you would eat
with your dinner like bread and buns
there are other things in the bakery
department like bagels and biscuits
the Baker works in the bakery there is
the canned goods section
this is where you might find sauces and
soups vegetables and fruits also come in
cans
there is the section for dairy products
here you would find milk and cream
the dairy section would also have cheese
and butter yogurt is also found in the
dairy section in the meat department
there is beef and pork poultry is also
found in the meat dept poultry is
chicken duck and goose
there are also cold cuts in the meat
department
cold cuts are the meats that are sliced
up for sandwiches some examples of cold
cuts our ham and Bologna the butcher
works in the meat department
the party's department is full of fruits
and vegetables clerks spray water on the
fruits and vegetables to keep them fresh
there is a section in the grocery store
for personal hygiene
this is where you would find shampoo and
toothpaste soap and skin products would
also be in this section
there is even a section for your pets
you can buy cat food and dog food there
are toys for cats and dogs
Oh
differences
are you tall or short are you bigger
small people come in many different
shapes and sizes
some people were size small clothes
other people wear size medium clothes
there are people who wear large size
clothes some people even wear extra
large clothes
some people are thin some people are fat
some people are in between there are
people with short hair
other people have long hair some people
have no hair at all
no two people are exactly alike some
people have long legs
I have short legs I don't walk as fast
as a person with long legs
I am NOT a tall person in fact i am
quite short
my feet are a size seven my mother has
size 5 feet
my father has size 12 feet we are all
different sizes
it is not a bad thing it is a good thing
that we are all unique
the restaurant
when you go to a restaurant you might
see a sign that says please wait to be
seated
a host or hostess will ask you how many
people are in your party then they will
want to know if you want to sit in the
smoking or non-smoking section
the host or hostess will take you to
your seat you might sit at a table or a
boof
host or hostess will give you a menu to
look at sometimes there are different
menus for different meals there can be a
breakfast menu a lunch menu and a dinner
menu
sometimes there is also a wine list and
a dessert menu
the food and the prices of food are
listed on the menu on your table there
will be cutlery cutlery is the knives
forks and spoons
there will also be a napkin you are
supposed to put your napkin on your lap
when you eat your waiter or waitress
will take your order
you might want an appetizer before your
meal some people want a salad or soup
before their meal after your meal you
might have a dessert or tea or coffee
when it is time to go you will pay your
bill and leave a tip for the waiter or
waitress
traffic
traffic moves along on the streets and
highways
there are rules that drivers must follow
to make the traffic flow smoothly
you must wear a seatbelt the seatbelt
helps to keep you safe
you must stop and all stop signs you
must also stop at a red light
a green light means go and a yellow
light means to be careful if you see a
sign that says school crossing
you have to be careful because you are
near a school and children might be
crossing the street
some places are crosswalks those are
places where people cross the street
people who are walking have the right of
way
if you hear a siren behind you you must
pull over an emergency vehicle like a
police car or an ambulance might need to
get somewhere fast when a school bus
puts on its flashing signals
you have to stop you can't go past the
school bus because children may be
crossing the street from the bus
you should always obey the speed limit
it is not good to drive too fast
people should never drink and drive
driving is a serious business you have
to obey all the rules to be a good
driver
music
if you were in an orchestra what would
you play
would you play a tuba a trumpet or a
saxophone
perhaps you would prefer a stringed
instrument like a violin or cello
maybe you would enjoy percussion more
you could play the kettle drum
there are instruments that have
keyboards a piano and an organ have
keyboards
there are instruments that have strings
on them a guitar banjo and mandolin have
strings on them
there are instruments that you blow into
a flute of French horn and a harmonica
are all instruments that you blow into
there are instruments that you hit with
a stick a drum and a symbol are two
things that you would hit with a stick
if you are in an orchestra you have to
watch the conductor
he will lead you through the piece of
music you might just want to be in a
band for fun
you could join a rock band or a dance
band
some people learn to read music music
notes are written on a staff each note
represents a sound
there are whole notes half notes quarter
notes and eighth notes each one of these
is held for a different number of beats
it is good to learn about music
you have to learn your scales and learn
about sharps and flats
if you want to learn how to play an
instrument it's best to take music
lessons
who what where and why
these are important words they're all
words that begin questions
who is about a person who is the girl
with the blue dress on who stole my
watch
who will come with me to the game who is
driving us to the party
what is about a thing what is that big
thing on the sidewalk
what should i do when i get to your
house what kind of clothes should i wear
to the party
what shall i buy you for your birthday
where is about a place where are you
going for your vacation
where did I leave my glasses where did
my brother go
where on earth is timmons why is the
word that asks for an explanation why
did you take the last piece of pie
why is the world round why should I give
you any money
why did the chicken cross the street
they say that you should answer all of
these questions if you are writing a
good story
you have to give the who what where and
why to write a good story
which direction
which direction should i go in should I
go up by go up
I will head toward the sky I can go up
the stairs
should I go down I can go down the
stairs to the basement
I can climb down into a hole should I go
left or right
I am right handed so I know which way
right is shy go backwards
I would be going away from the things
that I am facing now if I went backwards
if I went backwards from the thing that
I am facing i would go away from it
should I go forward i will just go
straight ahead if i go forward if I'm
facing something and I go forward then i
will go toward the thing that I am
facing maybe I should go sideways but
which side left or right
it sounds very complicated but it is not
directions are very easy to follow if
you just stop and think about them
the office
some people work in an office there are
special tools that people in an office
need to do their work
there is a computer in the office there
is a telephone
most of the time the secretary answers
the telephone
the secretary sits at a desk the
Secretary has pens and pencils on the
desk
the secretary rights on a notepad some
other things that you would find in an
office would include the following a
stapler to staple pages together a
photocopier to copy pages a pencil
sharpener to sharpen pencils a water
cooler where the employees could get a
drink of water
a whole bunch to make holes and sheets
of paper and liquid paper which is used
to blank out errors on a page
some offices have many employees in them
all of the employees have their own
desks other offices just have one person
at a desk and some offices there is a
secretary or a receptionist and then
there is the boss in another room
there are often many important papers in
an office important papers can be called
documents
you might have to sign the document or
fill out a form in an office
some offices have bookshelves filled
with books the books are filled with
information of the people in the office
need you will have to visit an office
sometime maybe it will be a doctor's
office or a lawyer's office
there are many different types of
offices
money
I keep my money in the bank I've saved
up my money I saved all my pennies in a
jar a penny is only worth one cent I
have Nichols a nickel is worth five
cents a dime is worth ten cents a
quarter is worth 25 cents a quarter is a
quarter of a dollar for quarters make up
a dollar a dollar is worth 100 sense
I saved up all of my dollars are dollars
used to be paper but now they are coins
we call our dollars loonies
it's a funny name we also have two
dollar coins
we call those 2 knees we have five
dollar bills and ten dollar bills if you
are lucky you will have twenty dollar
bills fifty dollar bills and even
hundred dollar bills are bills in Canada
are different colors that makes them
easy to recognize if you go somewhere to
spend them
it is wise to save your money if you
save enough you can have hundreds or
thousands of dollars
manners
it is good to be polite people liked you
more when you are polite always say
please and thank you
if you ask for some milk you should say
please may I have a glass of milk
when someone gives you the milk you
should respond with
thank you it is not difficult to be
polite
you should not push or shove people you
should cover your mouth when you cough
or sneeze
you should address people properly if
you're trying to get someone's attention
you would say excuse me you wouldn't say
hey you there are table manners
that is where you eat properly and
politely at the dinner table
you don't shove food into your mouth you
don't reach over other people's plates
you don't talk with your mouth full all
of these things are common sense being
polite is mostly thinking about how you
would like to be treated you wouldn't
want people to be impolite to you
it is not polite to point at people it
is not polite to burp out loud
it is not polite to use someone else's
things without asking first being polite
just comes naturally if you have been
brought up in a home where everyone was
polite
the two sexes
there are two sexes or genders there is
the male gender and there is the female
gender males and females are different
both physically and mentally humans are
both male and female and animals are
both male and female
if you have a dog it is either a girl
dog or a boy dog boys grow up to be men
men grow hair on their faces that are
usually more muscular than women men
dress differently than women men are
males males are masculine girls grow up
to be women only women can have babies
women are females females are feminine
another word for women is ladies
it is good that we have males and
females
your father is a male your grandfather
brother and uncle are males
your mother is a female your grandmother
sister and aunt are female
else Oh
me
I am special nobody in the world is
exactly like I am
they might have the same hair color and
eyes that I do but they are not exactly
like me
I am the only person in the world who
thinks my thoughts
no two people in the world are exactly
alike
it is good to be your own person it is
good to be creative and be natural
people have to follow the laws and the
rules
people should always be kind to others
I try to follow all the rules I am kind
to others
I am a lot like many other people yet I
am different i am like my friend Jane
but she has red hair and i have dark
hair she has a loud voice and i have a
soft voice
she likes to eat vegetables and I do not
Jane and I are the same height we both
like movies and we are both afraid of
spiders
we wear the same size shoes and we both
have the same favorite color
we are best friends but sometimes we
disagree about things we are alike in
many ways and different in many ways if
we were all exactly the same the world
would be a very boring place
I am myself and i am glad that I'm
special
you are special to use your own special
talents and take the time to meet other
people
the world is made up of a lot of
different people and that's what makes
life exciting
my cat
I got my cat when she was just a tiny
kitten
I named her puff because her fur is soft
and fluffy
she has white fur butter tail
pause and ears are black she has a
little pink nose and yellow eyes
she says meow whenever she wants a bowl
of milk
I feed her cat food and treats she
washes her face with her paw paw
when she is finished eating my whole
family loves her and we can tell that
she loves us
she loves to curl up in our laps she
purrs whenever we pet her she is very
playful
we sometimes roll out the piece of paper
and throw it to her she loves to chase
the paper and hit it with her paws
she also chases bugs last night she
chased a spider but she was afraid to
touch it at night she curls up in my bed
with me
she likes to be warm I have given her a
blanket of her own
but when i put her on it her tail
twitches her tail twitches whenever
she's upset or angry
I know she doesn't want to be on her
blanket
she wants to be in my bed I let her into
my bed and she falls asleep
purring loudly
music
my family is very musical my father
plays the guitar he plays in a band the
band plays country music
my mother is a singer in the band
she also plays the piano I took the
flute in music class at school I play
the flute in the school band
I also sing in the school choir I have a
low voice
my sister has a high voice she is a
soprano at home
I like to practice the drums but my
mother says that it's too loud
sometimes I place so loudly that I break
a drumstick
I practice whenever she goes out
I would like to be in a rock band some
of my friends and I are thinking of
starting our own rock band
my sister is a very good piano player
she has won many awards at music
festivals
she likes to play classical music but
sometimes i get her to play rock music
with me
she is also a very good singer
I like to sing with her we sing and
harmony
I listen to music all the time on the
radio
I know a lot of songs I can sing along
with most of the songs that come on the
radio
i memorize the lyrics of the songs my
sister and I sometimes get together and
sing our favorite songs
maybe someday we will start our own rock
band and i will be the drummer
spring
it rains a lot in the spring the trees
are full of buds and the flowers are
starting to bloom my favorite spring
flowers are tulips and daffodils the
birds come back from the south
I can always tell that spring is here
when I see my first Robin of the season
the Robins pull worms from the wet
ground when it isn't raining
my friends and I go outside and toss a
ball around
we look forward to the summer but we are
glad to get outside after the long
winter
the air smells so fresh in the spring
my mother always tells me not to track
mud into the house
it's very muddy in our yard in the
springtime
I wipe my muddy feet before i go into
the house
there are a lot of puddles in my yard
I sometimes splash in the puddles and I
get wet and cold so i have to go into
the house
I like it when the snow has melted the
rain has stopped and the sun comes out
on sunny days
I always get together with my friends on
those days we either ride our bikes or
play ball
my parents like to go for walks on
spring evenings they also like to clean
up the yard in the spring
everyone seems to be outside the
springtime brings people out of their
houses
the birthday party
yesterday I went to a birthday party
my friend
Jane had her 10th birthday her house was
decorated with balloons and streamers
her mother had baked a big birthday cake
the cake had
happy 10th birthday Jane written on it
there were ten candles on the cake
Jane blew out the candles and make a
wish
I wonder what she wished for your wish
won't come true if you tell anyone what
it was we saying happy birthday to you
at the party
we played some games i won one of the
games so I got a prize
we also swam in Jane swimming pool
Jane opened her gifts her gifts were
wrapped in bright paper and bows
she got lots of nice gifts she got some
compact discs some clothes and some
computer games
Jane thanks everyone we ate a lot of
food at Jane's party we had hot dogs
I put mustard and ketchup on my hot dog
then we ate cake and ice cream we had
popped to drink
i think i had too much cake and ice
cream I was very full by the time the
party was over
we thank Jane and her mother before we
all went home
it was a very good party everyone had a
good time I hope Jane had a happy 10th
birthday
my classroom
my classroom is a large room
it's full of brightly colored pictures
my teacher hangs pictures up all over
the walls
there are black boards at the front of
the room my teacher always has writing
all over the blackboards
sometimes the chalk squeaks when she
writes on the blackboard
we cover our ears when that happens our
classroom is full of desks
there are a lot of students in our class
our desks are full of books notebooks
and pens
I try to keep my desk neat but I have a
lot of things in there
my ruler and pencils are always falling
out of my desk at the back of the room
is a bookcase full of books we can sign
those books out and take them home to
read i have read a lot of the books I
like mysteries and biographies
so i have taken many of those home there
are also tables at the back of the room
that's where we do our artwork we spread
out big sheets of paper and use paints
or crayons to make pictures sometimes we
cut things out of magazines with
scissors and we glue pictures to the
paper
I like our class after school
my friends and I often erase the
blackboards for the teacher then we take
the erasers outside and clap them
together to get the chalk dust out of
them
my friends and I walk home together and
talk about what we did in school and
what we're going to do after supper
vacation
my family and I went on vacation to Lake
here on the water is beautiful and blue
there and the sand is nice and white the
week that we were there was very hot the
Sun was hot but the water was still very
cold
I went swimming and tried to catch
little fish in my hands
I was careful not to get sunburned we
stayed at a hotel that had a pool and a
game room
I played pinball and video games
sometimes I like to swim in the hotel
pool
but i like the beach better I would lie
on a big beach towel and get warm
then i would jump in the water and cool
off
sometimes I would just lie on the sand
and watch the waves roll up on shore
I found some seashells and saw a crab
walking on the sand
at first I was a bit lonely because I
didn't know anyone there
it wasn't long before I met some other
kids my age
we built sand castles together and swim
in the lake
the other kids were from different towns
so we told each other stories about our
schools and friends
we found that we had a lot in common
even though we were from different
places
our families got together and went to
restaurants together we played
volleyball on the beach and we SAT
around a campfire at night and sang
songs at the campfire we would roast
marshmallows on a stick
I always burned my marshmallows that is
ok I like them that way
mostly we just swim in the lake until we
were very tired
I was sorry when our vacation was over I
had a good time at like here on
I met some very good friends there we
still write to each other
maybe we'll see each other next summer
my house i live in a two story house
the bottom of the house is painted white
the upper part of the house is made of
red brick the chimney is also made of
red brick if you go through the front
door and turn right you'll see the
living room the living room is very
large and comfortable there are easy
chairs a coffee table and a sofa in
there
I like to sit in there and relax next to
the living room is the dining room
there are a dining table and chairs in
there we use this room whenever we have
visitors over for dinner
beside the dining room is the kitchen
the kitchen has a stove and a
refrigerator in it
there's also a kitchen table with some
benches added most of the time we eat in
the kitchen upstairs there are three
bedrooms
my parents bedroom is very big they have
a large queen sized bed in there and
there are two closets for their clothes
my room is smaller my room is painted
pink and I have ruffled curtains on the
windows from my bedroom window you can
see the front yard
there's a pine tree in the front yard my
brother's bedroom is painted blue
he has blinds on the windows he has a
bunk bed in his room
if he has a friends stay over one of
them can sleep on the top bunk and the
other can sleep on the bottom bunk
you can see the backyard from his
bedroom window
there are rose bushes and a picnic table
in the back yard
there is also a white fence that has a
gate in it in the basement
there is a recreation room this is where
we watch television and have friends
over to visit the larger room is also in
the basement
there's a washing machine and a dryer in
there beside our house is a garage
we keep the car in the garage whenever
the weather is bad
our house is just the right size for our
family friends are always welcome at our
house
my family
my grandparents are coming to visit us
from Calgary Alberta
my father is very happy because they are
his parents and he's glad that he will
see them
we don't see them very often because
calgary is a long way from Toronto my
grandparents have two sons
my father and my uncle bill uncle bill
is married to my aunt susan they have a
daughter who is my cousin my cousin is a
lot older than I so we do not have a lot
in common
they also have a son who is the same age
as me
he is my favorite cousin because we both
like the same television shows and the
same games
I have two brothers and one sister my
brothers are both younger than I they
are twins
so they have the same birthday my sister
is one year older than I people say that
my sister and I look alike
we both have blonde hair and blue eyes
my mother's parents live near us
they are my grandmother and grandfather
who visit us often my mother does not
have any brothers or sisters
she is an only child I like it when all
my family is together
I don't have a lot of cousins like some
people do but I have fun with my
relatives my uncle will often take my
cousin and me to the movies
I like to take my grandparents for walks
so they can see my school and they can
meet my friends my parents talk to my
brothers and my sister and I a lot
we are a very close-knit family people
who have closed families are very lucky
winter
once the fall is over and the snowflake
start to fall
I get very excited I can hardly wait for
the ground to be covered with a blanket
of white snow
I put on my mittens my scarf my hat coat
and winter boots and I run out into the
fluffy snow
I have to be careful not to slip on the
ice it can get very icy and cold in the
winter
the first thing that I do is to build a
snowman
I sometimes build a snow fort to my
friends and I have a good snowball fight
we laugh a lot and our cheeks and noses
get very red
when we get too cold we go into the
house and have a cup of hot chocolate
my father fills the backyard with water
that freezes and turns into an ice rink
when the ice is hard enough my friends
and I get our skates and we go out on
the ice to play hockey
all of my friends on hockey sticks I am
usually the goalie and I have to keep
the puck from going into the net
my sister and her friends don't really
like to play hockey
they would rather just skate around on
the ice I took skating lessons so I
don't usually fall down
my little brother is just learning to
skate so he falls down a lot
my father has to shovel the snow off the
paths and the driveway in the winter
I help him shoveling snow is hard work
when my dad and I finish shoveling the
driveway we go into the house and warm
our hands and feet in front of the
fireplace
there is probably nothing more beautiful
than fresh fallen snow on the trees in
the morning when the Sun shines on the
snow it glistens
I like to leave my footprints in the
snow winter can be very beautiful and
exciting
autumn
some people call autumn the fall
all you can call it either one autumn is
the time when the leaves change color
they change from green to beautiful
shades of gold orange and red
it looks like an artist has come along
and painted all the trees the air starts
to get a little colder in the autumn we
begin to wear jackets or sweaters
we go back to school in the autumn the
teachers sometimes gets us to make leave
collections we collect different types
of leaves and make a display of them
autumn is the time when old friends get
back together and talk about what they
did on their summer vacations Halloween
comes in the autumn we dress up in
costumes
some of them are scary and some of them
are funny
we go from door to door and say Trick or
Treat and people give us candies
we wear masks on our faces and we have a
lot of fun
the autumn winds start to blow the wind
blows the leaves right off the trees
until the trees have bare branches
my friends and I have a lot of fun
outside before the winter leaves of
shivering we play football and soccer at
school after school we ride our bikes
through the piles of dry leaves the
leaves go flying through the air as we
drive through them
my parents rake the leaves up and put
them in a big pile
I like to jump in the big piles of
leaves but then my parents just have to
rake them up again
the skies get a little cloudier in the
autumn and we know that soon there will
be snow so we enjoy the brisk autumn
weather while we can
summer
yeah who school is over we are free for
the summer
my
friends and I run out on the last day of
school into the bright summer sun we
sing a song about no more pencils and no
more books we can hardly wait to do all
the summer things that we like to do we
go swimming we play baseball
we ride our bikes and we go to the beach
we go on vacations or some of us go to
summer camp
it is just nice to run barefoot through
the grass or lie on your back and look
up at the clouds summer days are lazy
days we don't have to do school work
we listened to the buzzing of the bees
we watch the birds as they fly from tree
to tree we go down to the pond and toss
rocks into the water
we eat ice cream and we have BBQ years
some of my friends parents have boats so
we go for rides in their boats
some of my friends go to their cottages
they have cottages on legs
some of my friends even have summer jobs
my best friend works at a supermarket my
father pays me to do jobs for him
I cut the grass take out the garbage and
wash the car
I like to be outside in the sunshine on
Sundays
my mother will pack a picnic lunch and
we go down to the park
sometimes we play baseball there is also
a tennis court at the park
I'm a very good tennis player my sister
just likes to swing on the swings and
slide down the slide
we eat our sandwiches and watch out for
the ants that always seem to be a pic
mix after we have our lunch
my sister and I run off to play with the
other children
my dad has a nap and my mother read her
book my skin gets Brown from the Sun in
the summer summer is my favorite season
i like the sounds smells and feelings
that come with the Summer Sun summer is
a lot of fun
I wish summer could go on forever
the doctor
I didn't feel very well last week I had
a sore throat and a fever
my mother took me to see the doctor when
we got there the nurse took my name and
said that the doctor would be with me
soon
the doctor was a very nice man in a
white jacket
I had seen the doctor before when i had
my tonsils out at the hospital the
doctor took a light and looked in my
ears
he put a stick on my tongue and he shone
his light into my mouth
he looked at my throat he said that my
throat was a bit swollen and red
he felt my neck and said my glands were
swollen
he took my temperature and said that it
was quite high
he listened to my heart and he made me
cough
he asked me some questions he said he
might have to do some tests
he sent me to get some blood taken out
of my arm
I was scared but it didn't really hurt
the doctor gave me some pills and told
me to take one in the morning and one at
night he told me to drink lots of fluids
he told me to get plenty of sleep I did
exactly what the doctor told me to do it
wasn't very long before I was feeling
well again I think that I might like to
be a doctor when I grow up I would like
to make people feel better
the dentist
my friend's father is a dentist he has
an office near my house
I went to see him on thursday his nurse
told me to sit in a very big chair
she tied a bit under my chin the dentist
came in he examined my teeth with some
shiny silver tools
he looked at my front teeth and my back
teeth
he told me that the back teeth were
called molars
he told me to open wide he had a little
mirror that he used to look at my teeth
he said that I had good strong teeth
he told me that I didn't have any
cavities I told him that I didn't need a
lot of candies and that I always brush
my teeth after every meal
he said that was very good he asked me
if i flossed my teeth and I said yes I
use dental floss every day he told me
that my teeth were healthy because i
took very good care of them
he left and told me to keep up the good
work
the dental hygienist came in and she
said that she would clean my teeth for
me
she's great my teeth with a sharp tool
and then she put some polish on my teeth
and began to clean them when she was
done she told me to spit into a bowl and
then I rinse my mouth out with water
I looked into a mirror and saw that my
teeth were very shiny and white if I
take care of my teeth all have them
forever
I would like to keep my teeth healthy
and white
I like to smile
the school play
we are putting on a play at school some
of the students are actors in the play
some people are building the sets
some people will sew costumes and some
people will be makeup artists
the teacher is the director of the play
the play will be held on a big stage in
the gymnasium
the curtains will open the lights will
go on and the play will begin
it will be very exciting all of our
families will come to see the play they
will clap when the play is over my
friend is very good at cutting wood and
building things
he's helping to build the set my other
friend michael is an artist so he is
painting the set so that it looks like a
forest my friend Marie likes to put
makeup on people
so she is a makeup artist she will put
makeup on me so that i will look like an
old woman
some of the mothers help - so the
costumes the play is called Hansel and
Gretel
I will play the part of the witch the
boy who plays hensel has to wear shorts
and a shirt I wear a witch's hat and a
black dress
I also carry a broom some of the people
in my class will be dressed like trees
and flowers
this is a musical play and the trees and
flowers will sing to Hansel and Gretel
as they walk through the forest
I can hardly wait for opening night I
want my family and friends to see me
acting on stage
I hope they will like the play we have
all learned our lines and worked very
hard at making this play a success
emotions
do you ever think about your emotions
what kinds of things make you sad
I get sad when i get a bad mark in
school or when someone that I like moves
away
I sometimes see sad movies that make me
cry
I don't like to be sad I don't like to
have a frown on my face
I like to be happy I'm happy most of the
time parties make me happy being with my
friends makes me happy
lots of things make me happy if someone
tells me a joke
i laughs I enjoy laughing funny movies
make me laugh
I think that people look the best when
they smile
what kinds of things make you mad I get
mad when my brother breaks one of my
toys
I try not to show it when I get mad my
parents get mad at me if i come home
light
I don't think anger is a good emotion it
is best to stay calm and talk things
over
emotions come from inside you but they
show on your face
people can tell when you're mad or sad
or happy
I prefer to look happy sometimes I even
smile when I'm feeling sad and the smile
makes me feel a little better
my first job
i just got a job at the grocery store
this is my first job i will receive a
paycheck every two weeks
I wear a uniform the uniform has the
name of the grocery store on it
I have many jobs at the grocery store I
have to collect all the carts from the
parking lot and bring them back into the
store
I have to put all the produce out for
the people to see
i will be putting out the vegetables
there are carrots lettuce cabbages
cucumbers and beans to put out this
morning i also have to put the fruit out
on the stand so that it looks nice
the oranges roll away when i put them
out so i have to be careful
I put out the apples bananas and grapes
i stacked boxes up so that people can
buy cereal and cookies
I have to be careful or the boxes will
fall
there are cans of things which also need
to be placed on the shelves yesterday
the lie
yesterday I told
I don't feel very good about it I was
bouncing a ball in the kitchen and the
ball bounced up and broke up
it was one of my mother's best cops so I
was afraid that she would be mad i put
the broken cut back on the table and I
didn't tell anyone that I had broken it
that night my mother asked who had
broken the cup
my brother said not me my sister said I
didn't do it
I said I didn't break the cup but I was
lying
my mother said that we would all be
punished if someone didn't tell the
truth and say who broke the cup
I still did not tell her that I had
broken it she gave us one more chance
and she said she wasn't mad about the
cup
she just wanted us to be honest I still
didn't say anything
my brother sister and I all got sent to
our rooms we had to stay in our rooms
all morning
my brother said it wasn't fair I felt
very bad because my brother and sister
were being punished because of me
I went to my mother and told her that I
had broken the cop
she said that she was not upset about
the broken Cup
she knew that it was an accident she was
disappointed in me because I hadn't come
forward and told the truth
she said that she wouldn't have punished
me if I had been honest with her
I told my brother and sister that I was
sorry
I felt bad because they were punished
because i was dishonest
I told my mother that I was sorry that I
had lied to her
I told her that I had learned a lesson
honesty is the best policy
it is better to tell the truth it is not
a good feeling when people don't trust
you
I have learned that lying just hurts
people sometimes it is hard to be honest
but it is the best way to be