being a princess sometimes i think that
i would like to be a princess a Princess
would live in a palace and wear
beautiful clothes she would have
servants to do chores for her and she
would probably marry a handsome prince
people would recognize her they would
wave to her as she drove by it seems
like it would be a lot of fun to be a
princess but maybe it wouldn't be so
nice
maybe it would be terrible to be
recognized by everyone
maybe a princess would feel like
everyone was watching her she would have
to look nice
every time she left the palace there
would always be people with cameras who
wanted to take her picture a princess
would have no privacy even in her own
palace
there would be servants around so she
would never really be alone if I were a
princess
I would worry about security for my
family
sometimes people who are in high
positions are threatened by other people
that would be a worry I'm not so sure
that being a princess would be all that
much fun
I think it might be better to be just a
normal person like me
I don't have to worry about looking
wonderful all the time
people don't follow me around and take
my picture whenever you see a picture of
a princess she is smiling
I wonder if she's smiling on the inside
or just smiling for the camera
my worst fear I am afraid of water
I don't know why i am afraid i have
never had a bad experience in the water
I just never learned to swim I should
have done that when I was just little it
would be easier for me to swim now if i
had started when i was young i will go
into the shallow water but I start to
panic when the water gets higher than my
chest
I don't like the feeling of not being
able to put my feet on the bottom of the
pool or the lake
I don't like to get water up my nose I
choke and cough when that happens my
friends just tell me to relax and i will
float but i find it hard to relax in
deep water
they keep telling me that if I panic i
will think most of my friends have had
swimming lessons
some of them are even lifeguards they
have tried to teach me to swim but I
think I need to go to a place where they
actually teach swimming
it would be nice to jump into a pool of
cold water on a hot summer day
that would be so refreshing if I go out
onto a boat
I always wear a life jacket I think it
is wise to do that everyone should wear
a life jacket on a boat
I would rather be safe than sorry I have
decided that I will overcome my fear I
will go and take swimming lessons
I have a goal by this time next year
I would like to be able to swim the
length of the pool without being afraid
it is best to face your fears and deal
with them
I hope that I can overcome my fear of
water
if I live to be 100 i think i would like
to live to be 100
it seems like an awfully long time to
live it is an entire century
imagine all the changes that you would
see if you live to be 100
I had a neighbor who was 85 she used to
tell me what things were like when she
was a little girl she told me what my
town used to look like what her clothes
were like and what her school was like I
used to enjoy listening to her stories
everything was so different when she was
young
listening to her was like having history
come to life
I used to try to imagine what life was
like for her back then if I was a
hundred and I had grandchildren and
great-grandchildren
I would tell them stories about my
childhood I would hope that I had a good
memory so that I could remember
everything
if i do want to live to 100
I'll have to have a healthy lifestyle
not too many people live to be that old
if I do get to be that old I hope I'll
still be mentally alert and physically
agile in my country
the Prime Minister sends a letter of
congratulations to anyone who has their
hundredth birthday
people who live to be 100 are very
special
maybe in the future with better medical
care and healthier lifestyles more
people will live to be 100 if I live to
be 100 all have a birthday cake but I
won't put 100 candles on the cake
I could never blow out 100 candles
what I like most and least about myself
I was trying to think of the best and
the worst things about myself
I think the best thing about me is that
i am very friendly
I have a lot of friends and they all
like me
I try to be good to my friends I don't
often have arguments with people i think
that i am quite easy to get along with
the worst thing about me is that I
sometimes feel sad sometimes I don't
feel sad for any particular reason I
just get into moods where I am depressed
sometimes there is a reason to be sad I
was sad when my pet frog died I was sad
when I lost my favorite baseball card on
those days
I'm still nice to my friends but inside
I feel like there is a heavyweight in my
chest
I think that everyone feel sadness
sometimes I try to do things that make
me happy
whenever I get into one of my sad moods
last Saturday I felt a bit sad so I
called up my friend John and asked him
if he wanted to go to the movies
we went to a comedy we laughed all the
way through the movie so that by the
time the movie was over I didn't feel
sad anymore
my friendliness is my best trait and my
sad moods are my worst traits i have to
work at getting over my sad moves more
quickly being sad doesn't do anyone any
good
there is no use and feeling sorry for
oneself
the trunk in the Attic last month my
grandmother asked me if I could help her
to clean out her attic
I was happy that she asked me my
grandmother says that our attic is full
of junk
I think that our attic is full of
treasures I helped her to dust and
vacuum the Attic
I pulled and pushed around boxes and
crates
I helped her to wash the floors and
walls
my favorite thing that I did was to sort
through the old trunk that she had up
there
the trunk had a rusty latch on it it was
a bit difficult to open
but my grandmother got a knife and pride
the latch open the trunk was full of all
kinds of things
there are lots of clothes some of the
clothes had been my grandmother's there
was a blue velvet dress that she had
worn to a dance when she and my
grandfather were dating
it was a beautiful dress but there were
a few more holes in it
there were some of my mother's old
clothes there was a pair of bell-bottom
slacks that had bright flowers on it
I couldn't believe that my mother had
ever worn something like that
there were some of my mother's old
report cards
some of her marks weren't very good I
had fun reading the report cards
there were photographs there was a
picture of my grandparents holding my
mother when she was a baby
there was an old baseball glove that one
of my uncle's had owned
there was even one of my old dolls in
there one of her legs was missing my
grandmother said that I was rough on my
dolls when i was little i should have
taken better care of my toys
there was even some old jewelry I tried
on some of the old clothes and jewelry
I told my grandmother that I like
looking through old things
my grandmother told me to keep whatever
I wanted
she said that it was all junk I still
say that her trunk was full of treasures
hot and cold I noticed that whenever it
is summer people complain about the heat
but whenever it is winter people
complain about the cold
it seems that people are never satisfied
I don't like the winter it is usually
much too cold for me my teeth chatter
and my fingers turn them whenever the
weather gets cold it is hard for me to
warm up once i start to freeze
I try to wear layers of clothes but
winter winds go through my clothes
no matter how much i wear my feet feel
like they are blocks of ice on a cold
January day when I walk home from school
I would not like to live in a place that
had cold climate all year long
I am not comfortable when it is too cold
I like the summer some people say that
it is hot and sticky in the summer but I
don't mind the heat at all
I love to feel the warm sunshine on my
skin
I like the freedom of not having to wear
heavy coats and boots
I am the happiest when there is a
slightly cool breeze that comes along to
refresh you on a hot summer day
I could live in a place with a hot
climate I would enjoy that
of course when you are in a place with a
hot climate there are more bugs than in
places with cooler climates
I don't care for bugs where I live
it is very humid the heat and moisture
combined to make it uncomfortable
sometimes it is nicer when the heat is
high but the humidity is low it would be
better if I live somewhere where it was
hot but not humid
that would be just perfect
walk a mile in my shoes have you ever
heard the saying walk a mile in my shoes
I think it's a very good thing do you
know what it means it means that before
you judge someone you should put
yourself in his or her position for
example if someone was running in a race
and they did very poorly and came in
last
it wouldn't be fair to say oh he's just
a terrible runner
you would have to look at all the
circumstances that made the person lose
the race
maybe they pulled a muscle in their leg
the day before
maybe this is their very first race
maybe they are not in good form because
something isn't right in their lives
there can be so many things that affect
a person's life performance and moods
if someone was very quiet at a party you
couldn't just assume that they weren't
friendly
you don't know what is happening in
their lives they could be feeling ill or
they might have just had a bad
experience
nobody can know exactly how another
person feels even if someone tells you
what he or she is experiencing you still
won't fully understand what is going on
inside the other person everyone
perceives and feels things differently
to walk a mile in someone else's shoes
is to try and understand things from
that person's perspective we are all
shaped by the events that have taken
place in our lives
no two people have gone through the
exact same things
so before you are quick to judge someone
stop and think about what it is that
they might have gone through
you won't always understand why people
do what they do but you can try to
understand and put yourself in their
position
if I could go back in my life if I could
go back in my life and do some things
differently
this is what i would do I would not
waste so many hours in front of the
television set
I would get out and enjoy my life rather
than watching actors and shows i would
be a little more considerate of other
people
I would realize that my mother has more
to do and pick up after me i would pay
more attention in school tests are
easier when you have paid attention
rather than fooling around in class I
would save more money rather than spend
it on useless things i would read more
reading is enjoyable and it opens the
doors into all kinds of wonderful places
both real and imagined I would learn to
play an instrument music is always
appreciated if it is played well I would
eat better foods
I would try to stay healthy through my
diet and exercise
I would take more pictures and I would
keep a journal
memories are very precious i would take
the time to listen to what people have
to say
people appreciate a good listener I
would take the time to enjoy each day as
it comes
sometimes I am so busy looking forward
to what is coming up that I don't take
the time to enjoy the day that i am
living in
that's what I would do if I could go
back in my life
in fact I think I'll just make a habit
of doing all of those things all through
my life
joking joking is good jokes can be very
funny jokes can also be hurtful jokes
can be tasteless -
it is not an easy thing to find jokes
that do not offend anyone
some jokes make fun of different races
those jokes are not funny
they are hurtful it is not right to tell
racist jokes many jokes use bad language
or are about questionable subject matter
these jokes are also not acceptable many
people are highly offended by rude jokes
what some people find funny others will
not
comedy is a very personal thing some
people like slapstick comedy
that is the kind of comedy that the
three stooges use some people like very
subtle humor
some people will laugh at just about
anything sometimes it is not appropriate
to laugh but you feel like laughing
anyway
did you ever see anyone fall down did
you feel like laughing when they fell
down
you are probably worried that they had
hurt themselves yet the way that they
fell was so funny that you felt like
laughing it's not funny when someone
falls but you can't help but laugh even
though you try to hide it
jokes and comedy differ from culture to
culture many people from other countries
come here and don't understand our
comedy jokes and comedies are often
geared toward our environment sometimes
comedians make fun of the things that we
do in our day-to-day lives like going to
the bank are going grocery shopping
we can all relate to that being a
comedian is not an easy job telling
jokes and making people laugh is
extremely difficult
jokes are fun and they are funny if they
are good jokes can get you into a lot of
trouble if they are inappropriate and
sometimes they're just not funny
and nobody laughs here's a joke why does
the cow wear a bell
because its horns don't work do you get
it
do you think it is funny
well maybe it's not that funny I told
you that it was difficult being a
comedian
drugs there are two different types of
drugs
there are legal drugs and there are
illegal drugs legal drugs are the type
of drugs that the doctor gives you when
you were sick
illegal drugs are the drugs that people
sell on the street
illegal drugs are very dangerous if
someone ever wants you to try any type
of substance that you are not sure about
you should always say no people who sell
drugs on the street are criminals
if they get caught they will be sent to
jail
they sell drugs to get money they don't
care that people's lives are ruined from
taking drugs
if you take illegal drugs you can become
addicted to them
that means that you just have to have
the drug no matter what some people
steal from other people to get money to
buy drugs drugs affect your mind if you
take drugs
you will not be able to think clearly
your marks in school drop your memory
won't be very good
your personality won't be the same
it is very unfortunate that some people
do try drugs they think that it won't
hurt them they are wrong if you are
smart you will stay away from all drugs
except for the ones that the doctor
gives you
drugs are just bad news if you know
someone who is thinking about trying
drugs tell them that their entire life
could be ruined
in America they have a saying just say
no to drugs
it is a good saying but i think i would
rather say I'm just too smart to take
drugs
divorce
Mary's parents just got a divorce Mary
is very upset
she thinks that her parents don't love
her anymore she thinks that they got a
divorce because of her she is wrong
her parents love her just as much as
they always did they aren't getting
divorced because of Mary
sometimes marriages just don't work out
it isn't really anyone's fault
marriage isn't easy it is hard for two
people to stay together for a lifetime
sometimes people change as they get
older and they move on
some people have perfectly good
marriages and they stay together for
their entire lives
divorce doesn't happen because the
parents don't love the children anymore
a lot of children feel that it is their
fault but it isn't their fault at all
children either caused the divorce nor
can they prevent it
it is up to the parents divorce isn't
the end of the world
children can still see both parents and
stay with them
life goes on sometimes children can get
new stepmothers or stepfathers that can
be a good thing
you just have to be understanding and
know that your parents still love you
life doesn't always go the way that we
planned it but it has its twists and
turns
life is an adventure if your parents got
a divorce
just be understanding know that they
love you and that this is a hard time
for them
it is a hard time for you to but these
things have a way of working themselves
out in the end
if my fish could talk
I have a goldfish he swims around in his
bowl all day
he looks bored I look inside the bowl
and watch him his mouth always moves
he looks like he is talking I imagine
what my goldfish would say if he really
could talk
I think he would say hey i'm bored in
this little Bowl
why don't you get me a bigger tank with
more fish in it
I would like to have some friends to
swim around with
I went out and bought a bigger tank for
my goldfish
I put some plants at the bottom of the
tank and I got a miniature deep sea
diver to put at the bottom of the tank
I looked into the tank and imagine what
my goldfish was saying he seemed to be
saying this is a nice tank
it's roomy in here and you decorated it
well but i still don't have any friends
to swim with i went to the pet store and
bought three more gold fish
I put them into the tank all of the
goldfish seem to look at each other they
swim near each other and seem to be
playing games
I knew which one was my goldfish because
he has a black spot on his fin
I looked at him and imagine that he was
talking again
he said this is great i have a big new
home and friends to swim with these are
nice goldfish that you brought home for
me
thank you goldfish can't really talk
i know that i just like to pretend that
my goldfish talks he seems very happy
now with his nice new home and his new
friends
I don't think goldfish can smile either
but it looks like my goldfish has a
smile on his face
the best teacher
I have had a lot of teachers some of
them are good and some of them are
boring
there is one teacher whom I remember
very well he is the best teacher that I
ever had
his name was mr. Alvin he was a history
teacher
history is not my favorite subject
I don't really enjoy history a lot when
I was in mr. albums class he made
history seem exciting
he was more of an actor than a teacher
if he was describing a war he would make
us feel all the emotions that the
soldiers and their families would have
felt we could almost hear the guns
firing and the people shouting he would
paint a picture in our minds that was
very vivid when I had a history test in
this class
I didn't have to study much I would
remember every word that he had said I
would see him doing the actions that
went along with his stories
he was very animated he would shout out
orders as if he was a general or you
would speak softly and reverently when
describing the death of a great hero
the most important thing that I learned
from mr. Albin was that I did really
like history
I just thought that I didn't like it
because most people had made a doll by
just reading from the textbooks
history is not just a series of dates
and all facts
history is what really happened history
is real life
all the historical figures had real
families and emotions they weren't just
fictional people after i took history
for mr. Alvin I realized that I really
did have an interest in it
he was my favorite teacher and I will
always be grateful to him for making me
aware of just how interesting history
really is
weather
sometimes I watch the Weathermen on
television
it is fascinating to watch them . to
different areas of the country on the
map
he tells us where the weather will be
nice and where it will be bad
the weatherman is not always right
weather reporting is not an exact
science
nothing is very exact when it comes to
the weather the weather department does
a lot of research but they can never be
sure of exactly what will happen
sometimes it looks like it will be clear
but the wind changes direction and
clouds move in the weatherman can warn
people if there is a chance of a
hurricane or tornado
the weatherman can also warn people of
floods sometimes entire towns have to be
evacuated because of bad weather
it is important to be aware of the
weather for example it is not good to be
caught in the middle of a field when
there is going to be a thunderstorm
you might want to take extra precautions
if there is going to be a heavy
snowstorm
you would need to be in a secure place
of a hurricane or tornado was predicted
you might want to cancel a picnic if you
knew that it would rain that day the
weather affects us in so many ways
some people are really affected by dog
cloudy days
if there are no sunny days they become
very depressed heavy air pressure can
cause some people to have headaches
weather affect all of us in one way or
another it is always a topic of
conversation
people often say things like hello it's
a beautiful day today
often we plan our lives and activities
around the weather
so if you are planning on walking home
tonight keep an eye on the sky
are those rain clouds up there you might
need an umbrella
how to avoid catching a cold
how many calls do you catch in a year
most of my friends catch quite a few
colts they cough sniffle and sneeze to
carry around tissues and blow their
noses all the time
their eyes water and they have scratchy
throats I don't get many colds in fact i
can go for a whole year and never catch
a cold
this is why i consider myself an expert
on how not to catch a cold
I'll tell you how to avoid catching a
cult I think that you need to take a lot
of vitamin C
I eat a lot of fruits and vegetables I
drink fruit juice - I also take vitamin
c pills
whenever I begin to feel a cold coming
on I make sure that I have taken my
vitamin C pill and I drink a lot of
orange juice that usually knocks the
cold right out of my system
I make sure that I get a lot of fresh
air in the winter a lot of buildings are
shut up tight so that the air is stale
and people's germs circulate through the
building's I get outside and breathe in
fresh clean air if somebody is rude
enough to confer sneeze right in front
of me without covering his or her mouth
I just hold my breath for a second I'm
not sure if this works or not but I
don't want to breathe in anybody's cold
germs many germs are passed through
hands
it is important to wash your hands
thoroughly if you touch anything in a
public place
if I hold a banister while I'm walking
down the stairs
I think of all the people who have used
that banister and I make sure that I
wash my hands before I eat
door knobs also have a lot of germs on
them money is another thing that is
passed from hand to hand and is covered
with germs
sometimes I see people stick money into
their mouths
just think of all the germs that you
would be putting into your mouth if you
did that
if you just give it a little bit of
thought you can avoid a lot of germs
that cause colts if you eat good food
and stay fit your body will be able to
fight off the germs that cause colds and
other diseases
it is not always possible to avoid cold
but if you do catch a cold drink plenty
of fluids and get a lot of rest
the future
I sometimes wonder what life will be
like in the future life has changed so
much in just the past few years
I'm sure that there are still big
changes that are coming
do you think will still drive cars maybe
we'll get into computerized vehicles
that we won't have to drive will just
push a few buttons and the vehicles will
take us to where ever we have to go
maybe there won't be roads you might
just fly through space to get where we
want to go instead of telephones we'll
just use our computers will be able to
see each other when we talk that type of
thing is already happening
maybe we won't have to cook our meals we
might be able to push buttons to order
whatever we want a nice roast beef
dinner or an ice cream sundae might just
pop out of a machine would be nice to
have a robot to clean the house for you
in the past few years computers have
been extremely important people used to
write to each other through the mail
now people communicate so much more
frequently through email
most of my friends own computers if we
had all of these things to do the work
for us
what would we do we would still need
people to program the computers we could
spend more time being creative
rather than doing everyday chores the
future holds many surprises
I'm sure that technology will become
even more and more amazing when my
parents were young they had never even
seen a color television
nobody owned a computer it doesn't take
long for things to change a lot
who knows what amazing things are in
store for us
giving a speech
I had to give a speech last week I gave
a speech - 300 people have to speak in
front of a group of students
I had to tell them about a campaign that
we were having to raise money for cancer
research
giving a speech can be a difficult thing
when you stand in front of a big crowd
you can get very nervous some people
feel like they have weak knees their
legs feel as if they are made of rubber
their heartbeats very hard inside of
their chests their palms get sweaty
some people even become short of breath
for some people giving a speech is their
worst fear when you give a speech
everyone is looking at you they're
waiting to hear what you have to say
when you have 300 people looking at you
you have six hundred eyes that are on
you it is a little frightening when you
think of it that way before I give a
speech
I take three big breaths I call myself
and I remind myself that what I have to
say is important
I like to be sure of what i am going to
say so I practice my speech in front of
a mirror at home
I like to look like I am relaxed and
friendly
they say that practice makes perfect so
the more speeches that you give the
better you will become at it whenever I
have to give a speech
I imagine that the audience is just one
big person I look out into the audience
until I find a friendly smiling face
I focus on that person and I pretend
that I am just talking to them
I've become used to giving speeches I'm
more relaxed now than I used to be
people tell me that i do not look
nervous at all
I like to hear that sometimes I do feel
a little flutter of nervousness but I
just ignore it and do the best that I
can
giving a speech is not as scary as it
appears to be anyone can do it with a
little practice
moving to another country
my friend Steve moved to another country
he had lived in Canada all his life and
he moved to Japan life in japan was very
different for Steve than what he was
used to at first steve suffered from
culture shock
his whole life seem different he was not
used to the way of life in Japan
steve was not used to the large crowds
of people that walked up and down the
streets in japan in his hometown in
Canada
the streets were fairly quiet Steve had
to get used to the food in Japan the
people eat a lot of fish
Steve had never eaten much fish before
Steve wanted pizza
but it was expensive in Japan steve said
that he had to adjust his eating habits
the people in Japan have different
customs then we do here in Canada
Steve didn't want to offend anyone so we
had to learn the customs
he had to learn about what Japanese
people considered polite and fruit
sometimes in a foreign country you can
do something to insult someone without
even realizing that you are being rude
at first steve had trouble with the
language he said that the only way to
really learn the language is to talk to
people
Steve talked to a lot of people he made
a lot of mistakes but people were
patients with him and they tried to help
him with his Japanese it wasn't long
before steve felt more comfortable in
his new surroundings
you have to be willing to learn new
customs and a new language if you move
to another country c feels very
comfortable in japan and in canada now
he is thinking about going to another
country now he thinks that he might like
to try and live in Italy
I'm sure that he would get over his
culture shock very fast if he moved
there
moving to a new country can be difficult
but if you are willing to learn
it can be a very rewarding experience
look for the beauty
I've learned that things don't always go
the way that they were planned
if something doesn't happen the way that
I wanted to I try to make the best of
the situation
I always try to find something good and
everything that happens
last year I broke my ankle when I was
walking on an icy sidewalk at first I
was very upset i was missing school and
there was a party that I wanted to go to
I couldn't do very much of anything my
ankle was very sore
I stayed home and I read a book it was
an excellent book and one that I
probably would not have had time to read
under normal circumstances
my friends brought my homework to my
house and we had some really nice visits
while they were here
I had to accept the fact that i couldn't
go anywhere on my broken ankle so i made
the best of a bad situation
once I lost my way when I was out
camping
I ended up in a very large field was
afraid that nobody would find me but I
calmed myself down and took time to
examine all the interesting wildflowers
in the field
my family did find me they're surprised
at how calm I was
I've learned that there is something
valuable inside every adventure and
something beautiful inside every person
we had a new boy who came into our class
his clothes origin style and he was not
particularly handsome
some of the boys and girls made fun of
him sometimes people can be really cruel
he seemed to handle it all right but
inside I knew that it must hurt
some of my friends and i invited him out
with us we found out that he had a
terrific sense of humor and he is
probably one of the nicest people I've
ever met
he has since become one of my best
friends makes me ashamed when someone
that I know judge someone by how they
look
it isn't fair to do that you'll find
that something good comes out of almost
every situation
you'll find something good about almost
everyone that you meet
if you look hard enough if something
doesn't work out the way you planned it
just make the best of the situation look
for the beauty in everything
my doll
when I was an infant I got a rag doll it
was a very plain little doll and it wore
a clown outfit and a clown's hat
I used to take back dolls to bed with me
every night I couldn't go to bed without
my doll
my mother used to pretend that the doll
was talking to me she would make the dog
dance and sing songs
I would talk to the doll my mother would
answer for the doll but I was a baby
I thought that the doll was actually
talking to me that doll was my best
friend
I took her everywhere one time I took
her to a store with me and I left her on
a shelf in the store
we were halfway home when I realized
that didn't have my doll with me
I was very upset my mother and I rushed
back to the store
my doll was still there I was so
relieved I hug my doll and I promised
myself I would never leave her anywhere
again
I couldn't imagine life without that
doll through the years the doll became
less important in my life and other
things to do but the dogs still sat on
my bed during the day and I still took
it to bed at night I gave that doll a
lot of love when I was little
in fact I loved that doll so much that
she looks tattered and torn now there
are parts of her face and hands are
almost worn away
I have a lot of other toys when I was
little but none of them were ever so
important as that doll
I don't play with toys anymore but that
doll is still in my room
she sits in a special chair in the
corner I'll always have that doll
no matter how worn out she is always
keep her and cherish her as part of my
early child
childhood child