hobbies
a lot of people have hobbies hobbies are
interesting things that people like to
do in their spare time
my father has a hot
p he has a model railroad set that he
put together a tiny electric train runs
through make-believe villages and
travels through tunnels and over
mountains
my father also enjoy sailing he has a
real sailboat that he takes us out on
he is teaching me how to sail I like to
collect things I collect comic books
stamps and coins
I trade comic books with some of my
friends and sometimes i buy comic books
at stores some of the very old comic
books are worth a lot of money i have
stamps from all over the world
whenever any of my friends get a letter
from a faraway place they save the
stamps for me i have stamps from England
Japan Australia and even Russia
I use a magnifying glass to look at the
stamps and I keep them in a special
album
I don't have too many coins yet but I
have a very old i'm from canada and i
have a coin with a hole in it from
Africa
my mother used to collect dolls when she
was a little girl
the dolls were costumes from different
countries my friend jon's hobby is
painting he does oil painting he has
even sold some of his paintings
he is a good artist my friend Linda so's
she has made clothes for herself and
some of her friends maybe Linda will be
a fashion designer when she gets older
sometimes people's hobbies lead them
into their careers
Christmas
in December christmas comes we get a
holiday from school and our parents get
a few days off from work
our family gets ready for christmas by
decorating the house we decorate it
inside and errands on the outside of the
house
we put up lights that twinkle and glow
we have a wooden Santa Claus and a
reindeer set that my father puts up on
the roof
inside we put up a Christmas tree some
years we have a real tree real pine
trees smell nice
but you have to be careful that they
don't dry out and start a fire
this year we have an artificial tree we
hang tinsel and ornaments on the tree
we also hanging strands of light on the
tree and put a star at the top
everyone thinks that the tree is
beautiful when we turn on the lights
we place gifts under the tree there is a
gift for me under the tree
it is wrapped in red paper and it has a
big green bow on it red and green are
the Christmas colors on Christmas Eve
my brother and sister and I will hang
our stockings near the fireplace Santa
Claus comes down the chimney and fills
our stockings full of toys and goodies
on Christmas morning
it is exciting to see what Santa has
left for you
my mother will make a big turkey dinner
for us on Christmas Day
we have lots of vegetables and good
tasting foods to go with the turkey
we will have dessert to some of my
family like Christmas pudding but i will
just have ice cream last year some
carolers came to the door
it was snowing outside they stood in the
snow and saying Christmas carols to us
my father gave them some money and my
mother gave them some hot chocolate to
warm them up they had lovely voices and
they saying some of my favorite carols
we also collect food gifts and money for
some of the people in town who cannot
afford to have Christmas
my family is collecting things for a
poor family who live near here
we had fun deciding which toys to buy
for the children in that family
it was a good feeling to share with
people who do not have as much as you do
my parents have always taught us that
christmas is a time for giving not
receiving I think that
right
the garden
the garden is very interesting
I sometimes go outside and i watch all
the things that go on in the garden
it smells wonderful in the flower garden
there are red white pink and yellow
roses that have a sweet smell
i watch the bees as they take pollen
from the roses
there are tiny bugs that live on the
rose bushes
my mother tries to get rid of the little
bugs but it is difficult to get rid of
them
she is glad to see the red lady bugs who
eat the little bugs the birds like the
sunflowers
they like to eat sunflower seeds there
is a bird bath in the garden
the Blackbirds and swallows go in there
to take a drink or have a bath
I sometimes see a Robin or a blue jay in
there too
in the dirt there are little holes where
the ants go in and out
the ants are hard workers i watch them
as they work together as a team to bring
food to their nests there are snails in
the garden -
they carry their homes on their backs
they move slowly and leave a silvery
trail as they go they eat the leaves
from my mother's plants
my mother also has vegetables growing in
her garden
she grows green peas we like to pick
those and eat the peas raw right out of
their pods
she grows lettuce and tomatoes -
we have so many tomatoes that we always
give some to our neighbors
my mother sends us outside to pick
lettuce and tomatoes
whenever we have a salad my favorite
vegetables are carrots their tops grow
above the earth
but the carrots are below the dirt when
you pick them you have to pull the
carrots out from under the soil weeds
also grow in the garden after a good
rain fall
it seems that the weeds just spring up
I pull the weeds out by their roots so
they won't grow back
weeds choke the good plants so we don't
want them in our garden
gardening is a good hobby you get fresh
air sunshine and exercise you even get
beautiful colorful flowers and nice
fresh food
the pet store
on Saturday my parents took us to the
pet store
they had everything that you would need
if you had a pet
they had dog food collars and leashes
for dogs they had treats to give your
dog and brushes to brush your dog for
cats they had food toys and litter boxes
for birds they had seed and cages
there was a section for fish they had
fish in big tanks and little bowls in
the big tanks
there were colorful fish swimming around
the girl who worked there said that they
were tropical fish there were gold fish
in the smaller fish bowls
I saw the girl get a goldfish out with a
little net
she sold it to a boy who said he had
another goldfish at home there was a
very large cage with a parrot in it
I walked up to the cage and the parents
said hello
I was surprised that the parrot could
talk
it could say a few things it said I love
you
pretty bird and bye bye I told my mother
that I would like a parrot
but she said that parents need a lot of
care and attention at the back of the
store
there were some puppies they seemed glad
to see me
I stuck my hand into the cage and one of
them licked my hand
they were very lively they were running
around and chasing their own tails in
the next cage
there were two kittens one of them was
playing with a toy and the other one was
asleep
the kittens were very small the one that
was sleeping was curled up into a ball
I couldn't even see her face
I didn't want to leave the pet store I
was wishing that I could take all of the
animals home with me
my first day of school
I remember my first day of school
I was excited but I was afraid I held my
mother's hand as we walk to the school
when we got near the school
I wouldn't let her hold my hand anymore
I didn't want to look like a baby
we got to the school the school looked
very big and frightening
there were children outside on the
playground
they all looked very big I looked at
them and some of them looked at me I
felt very small
my mother and I went into the school and
found the kindergarten room
there were children in their most of
them were the same size as me
my mother spoke to the kindergarten
teacher the teacher was very nice
she said my name and she introduced me
to some of the other children
I already knew some of the children
because they lived near me
I began to play with some of the things
that were in the classroom
there were tight rucks coloring books
and even a dull house
I soon forgot to be scared and I began
to play with the other children
I didn't even notice that my mother had
left the room
in school we sang songs played some
games and listened as the teacher read
us a story
I had a lot of fun on my first day of
school
I even drew a picture of my teacher
I took the picture home and my mother
put it on the refrigerator
I like school it is a good place to meet
new friends and learn all about the
world
transportation
people move from place to place there
are lots of ways you can move around
from one place to another
sometimes you can just move your feet
and walk walking is good for you
some places are too far to walk to you
might have to ride a bicycle or ride on
a skateboard
some places are too far away to ride
your bicycle to you might have to drive
in a car or a van or even a truck
my father has a car my uncle has a van
I have never been in a big truck trucks
are usually used to carry big loads from
one city to another
I would like to be a truck driver
I would travel all over and sit high up
in the cab
I have been in a taxicab
once my mother and i took a taxi to the
hospital
there was a special meter in the taxi
when we finished our taxi ride the
driver looked at the meter to find out
how much money we owed him
I once rode a horse i sat in the saddle
and held on tight to the reins the horse
ran very fast
it was a bumpy ride and I was afraid
that I would fall off the horse
not too many people around here use
horses for transportation
they used to use horses for
transportation in the old days if you
want to travel very far away
you have to go on a train a plane or a
boat
if you are in a hurry it is best to take
a plane planes fly through the air
very fast trains go along the tracks
sometimes I can hear the train whistle
from my house boats take a long time to
cross the ocean
great big boats that cross the oceans
are called ships
if you like to take it easy and look out
at the water than ships are a good way
to travel
they say that the world is a lot smaller
now because of Transportation people can
travel to all parts of the world quickly
and easily
the world is not really smaller but it
has become easy to get to faraway places
television
do you watch television my mother says
that i watch too much television
i watch cartoons on saturday mornings
cartoons make me laugh my brother and I
each have our favorite cartoons
we have trouble deciding which cartoons
we will watch on Saturday afternoons we
like to watch sports
my brother really likes to watch
baseball but usually my mother tells us
to go out and play on a Saturday
afternoon on weeknights
we have our own favorite shows I like
shows about outer space and monsters
my brother likes comedies he likes to
laugh my mother like shows about real
life situations
she likes to watch the news she says
that the news is important
she watches the news and weather to find
out what is going on in the world
sometimes she watches real-life shows
about doctors or policemen
my father doesn't watch television
he says that he would rather read a good
book or the newspaper
my dad gets all his news from the
newspaper
my favorite thing is to sit in front of
the television with a bag of popcorn and
a bottle of pop I sit there and change
the channels with the remote control
I change channels and watch a few
different shows at once
my mother won't let me watch too much
television
she doesn't want me to get lazy
television is good if you don't spend
too much time watching it you can learn
a lot from television
if you watch the educational channels I
learned about dinosaurs and rainforest
last week
just from watching television
my country
i live in canada it is a very large
country that is made up of ten provinces
and three territories
most of the provinces and territories
are quite unique for example in
Saskatchewan
the land is flat and it is not
surrounded by water
they grow wheat in Saskatchewan British
Columbia has mountains
I have never been to British Columbia
but I hear that it is very beautiful
nova scotia is on the Atlantic Ocean
so there are many fishermen out there
the people in the provinces are even
different from each other in Quebec many
of the people speak french in the
Maritime Provinces the people like to
play their own kind of music they play
fiddles and accordions and many of them
dance very well known of it is in the
north
so life is quite different they're the
people who live in the new territory of
Nunavut are very close to wildlife
they do a lot of hunting and fishing it
can get very cold up in the Arctic where
none of it is i live in ontario even
within Ontario life can be quite
different
the capital of ontario is toronto
toronto is a very busy city with lots of
apartments offices and shops
toronto is an exciting place and it has
a lot to offer
there are theaters and restaurants to
suit every taste the culture in toronto
is very diverse
if you drive a few miles north of
Toronto you will find places that are
tranquil and peaceful many people leave
Toronto on the weekends and drive to
their cottages where they find rest and
relaxation
canada is made up of many different
cultures
people of many different ethnic
backgrounds live in harmony in Canada
that is why i like Canada in Canada we
celebrate our differences
food
what kind of food do you like to eat
I am lucky because in Canada there are
many foods to choose from
I like to eat hot dogs hamburgers &
steak
these are all meat products i also like
cheese ice cream and yogurt these are
all dairy products
I like vegetables my favorite vegetables
are broccoli cabbage carrots and peas
I eat a lot of fruit I eat which ever
fruit is in season in strawberry season
I eat a lot of strawberries in peach
season
I eat many peaches sometimes my mother
will make a peach pie many different
crops grow in canada we have many
orchards and farms fresh fruit and
vegetables are plentiful in Canada meat
and fish are also plentiful here in
canada we have a lot of different foods
to choose from in my city there are a
lot of Italian restaurants
my favorite food at the italian
restaurant is pizza
my parents would rather have spaghetti
or lasagna
there are Greek restaurants mexican
restaurants and chinese restaurants in
fact there are restaurants from most
cultures
I can go around from restaurant to
restaurant and pretend that I am
traveling the world and trying all the
different foods from around the world
sometimes I eat things that aren't good
for me
I eat potato chips and candies these
foods aren't part of a nutritious diet
but they are fun to eat
the zoo
my class took a trip to the Toronto Zoo
I
I had a wonderful time they're my
favorite animals were the Lions
they look very powerful and strong
they say that the lion is the king of
the forest and I think that title suits
him
the monkeys were funny they were looking
at us just as much as we looked at them
they were swinging from branches and
doing tricks to impress us
there was a baby monkey that was
clinging to its mother's back
it was very cute the Tigers were pacing
back and forth
they seemed Restless the stripes on a
tiger are very beautiful
we watched the toll giraffes as they
nibbled leaves off the tallest trees
we spoke to a colorful parrot that spoke
back to us we saw exotic animals that we
had never seen before
some of them were very strange there
were different types of bears they're
there were black bears
I saw a black bear once when I was
camping up north we saw polar bears
polar bears are white they like the cold
we even saw panda bears one of my
friends bought a toy panda bear from the
gift shop because she thought that the
pandas were so cute
we saw slippery snakes some of the
snakes had very bright skins
most of the girls were afraid of the
snakes the zookeeper was looking after
the snakes and one of them hissed at him
he has to be very careful when he works
with the snakes
the last thing that we saw at the zoo
was the elephant
he was enormous he looked at us
then he raised his trunk and made a loud
sound it made us jump
the museum
the museum was very interesting there
were so many things in the museum that I
would need more time to really see
everything
there were clothes from the past I don't
know how people wore some of those
things they look like they would be
uncomfortable
I like to wear my jeans
there were things from Wars there were
bullets and cannons and even uniforms
from the soldiers
I don't think that war is a good thing
but it is good to remember the past and
honor the people who died for your
country
there was an old fire truck at the
Museum this fire truck was pulled by a
horse
there were some very old photographs of
the firemen putting out fires
there were rooms in the museum that were
set up like an old house
there were antique irons and sewing
machines
the women used to clean the clothes with
a washboard
there were no modern appliances back
then
I'm glad that we have electricity and
modern appliances the things that we
have make life so much easier
there were mummies from Egypt at the
Museum
I was fascinated by those there were
artifacts from the Indians
there were arrowheads and cradles that
the babies slept in
I tried my best to see everything but it
was almost impossible
the museum is a good place to learn
about your past
I tried to imagine my grandparents using
some of the things that were on display
at the Museum
the police
my mother always told me that if I was
lost I could go up to a policeman and
that he would help me to find my way
home I never did get lost
but I always remembered what my mother
told me about the police
I think policeman look very nice in
their uniforms
I see police officers drive by in their
police cars in my town
we even have police officers on bicycles
policeman and police women have a job
that can sometimes be dangerous
they have to catch people who break the
law
sometimes they have to chase people or
try to calm people down to be a police
officer
you need a lot of training it's
important to be able to deal with people
effectively a police officer came to our
school
he had a police dog with him
the officer showed us how the dog could
track down criminals
the dog was very smart he could even
find things that were hidden
criminals sometimes hide things that
they don't want the police to find the
policeman told us that he and his dog
were partners
his dog lives at his house with the
policeman and his family
sometimes I see police cars on the side
of the road
the police stopped at people who are
speeding or are not wearing their
seatbelts
the police officers warn people or give
out tickets
sometimes they even have to arrest
people
police officers are just doing their job
when they arrest people some people need
to be arrested and put in jail to make
it safer for the rest of us
pretending
I like to pretend i like to make up
things that aren't real
I use my imagination I was pretending
that i was in a time machine
I set the date for a prehistoric time I
turned on the time machine and it buzzed
in Word and spud madly when it stopped
spinning i opened the door and stepped
out into a very thick jungle
I listened carefully to the sounds of
the jungle I could hear strange animal
noises and the leaves were rustling I
wasn't sure if I'd gone back in time or
just landed in a jungle somewhere in the
21st century
it didn't take me long to realize that I
had indeed gone back in time a very
strange bird-like creature with a large
beak flew overhead
I've never seen anything like it in my
life I took a few steps out into the
long grass and ferns
I didn't want to go too far away from my
time machine
I heard a noise over on my right side
there was a man who looked quite
different from me
he was dressed in an animal skin and he
carried a big stick
I didn't want him to see me so I hid
behind a tree
he didn't speak any language that i
could understand he grunted at someone
who must have been in the distance
then I felt the earth shake beneath my
feet
I heard giant thumps on the ground as
the floor of the jungle shook the man
and the animal skin began to run
I saw why he was running a giant
dinosaur appeared above the tops of the
trees
it was bigger than anything I'd ever
seen my heart began to pound my chest it
was coming toward me
I ran toward my time machine and jumped
in I set the dial for the 21st century
the Machine word and buzzed my time
machine landed in the 21st century
I got away just in time
a baby
my and just had a baby girl
we went to the hospital to visit my end
and to see the new baby
my aunt was feeling fine although she
was just a bit tired
she walked with us to a big window that
had lots of babies behind it
she pointed to a crib with a baby in it
the baby was wrapped in a pink blanket
we all said how pretty the baby looked I
couldn't believe how tiny the baby was
she was asleep so we couldn't see her
eyes when the baby went home
we went to visit her we heard the baby
she was crying
my aunt said the baby was hungry my aunt
had a baby bottle full of warm milk
she fed the baby with it the baby was
happy after that my and patted the baby
on the back until the baby burp and then
the baby fell asleep
I held the baby I looked at her tiny
fingers and tiny toes
I was very careful with her she opened
her eyes and looked at me
I spoke to the baby but I knew that she
could not understand me
babies have to learn to walk and talk
my aunt change the baby babies wear
diapers so they need to be changed often
the baby has a lot of toys but she is
still too young to play with them by and
says that it won't be long before the
baby is crawling and trying to talk
babies are cute I have seen pictures of
myself when I was a baby and it's hard
to believe that I was once that small
a wedding
the church bells are ringing I am inside
the church waiting for my cousin to walk
down the aisle
today is her wedding day she has a bride
the organist is playing a song on the
organ
we all stand up and watch my cousin walk
down the aisle
she is our man armed with her father she
is dressed in a long white dress and
veil
she looks so beautiful she looks like a
princess
the man who she is going to marry is
standing at the front of the church
he is the groom he looks nice too he is
wearing a suit and he has a flower in
his lapel
the minister says words to the couple
which will make them man and wife
the bride and groom smile at each other
but they seem to be a little bit nervous
they give each other gold rings - where
to symbolize that they are married they
kiss each other and walk out of the
church as the organist plays joyous
music
some of the people in the church cried
at the wedding but not because they were
sad
everyone in the church is very happy for
the couple a photographer takes pictures
of the happy couple
we wish them well and look forward to
the reception where we will have dinner
and we will dance and have a good time
until it is very late
the bride will throw her bouquet of
flowers and it is said whoever catches
the bouquet will be the next bride
the next day the bride and groom will
leave for their honeymoon
my cousin and her husband are going to
Mexico for their honeymoon
my dad
my dad is the man whom I respect the
most in my life
he works very hard to make the money
that supports us
my mother has a job too and she also
works very hard
my dad is the principal of a high school
he works at the school all day and often
has to go to meetings at night
he deals with parents students and staff
there was always something that he has
to deal with
he has a lot on his mind it doesn't
matter how much work my dad has to do he
always has time for my brother's my
sister and me if I go to him with a
problem
you will sit down and discuss it with me
he doesn't yell
he is always very logical and he tries
to think of the best way to deal with
things
my dad is a very patient man once I
spilled some ink on papers that he was
working on
I thought he would be mad but he didn't
get angry he said it was ok he takes
time out to do things with us
he has taken my brother's fishing he
takes me to the arena to skate and he
helps my sister to write your essays and
assignments
he always makes us laugh he makes us
feel like we are very special to him he
is a very good father and on father's
day I always buy him a car that tells
them just how much he means to me
I think it is important to have good
parents
I hope that when I have children I will
be a good parent like my parents are to
me
parents give children the foundation
they need to live good lives
my mother
my mother does so many things she has a
job at a dress store
she cooks our meals she cleans the house
she feeds the pets and she still finds
time to spend with us
my mother is always busy but she says
that her favorite time is time that she
spends with us
my mother works from monday to friday
when she comes home from work she makes
something for supper
we usually do the dishes so that she
won't have to do them after supper she
helps us with our homework or she sits
down to watch television
some nights she go shopping and she
takes whoever wants to go with her
mother's are a little bit of everything
my mother is like a teacher when she
helps us with our homework
she is like a nurse when she looks after
us all when were ill she is like a cook
when she makes meals for us
she says that cleaning the house is
released favorite thing she says that
the house gets dirty again right after
you clean it
she gets my father my brothers sister
and me to help her with the cleaning my
mother washes all our clothes and
sometimes she irons them if they need it
my mother says that there are not enough
hours in a day
we try to help my mother as much as we
can there's a lot of work involved in
keeping a home neat and organized
most of my friends mother's work mothers
are the people who you go to when you
need to be comforted mothers are the
people who could make you feel better
i'm glad that i have the mother that I
have my mother is caring and funny
she has fun to be around
a surprise
last Friday my dad came home from work
and said that he had a surprise for us
we tried to guess what the surprise
might be my brother gets that we were
going out for dinner
my dad said no my other brother asked if
my father had tickets to a hockey game
my dad said no my sister asked if we're
going on a trip
my dad said no my mother knew what the
surprise was so she just stood and
smiled at us
I guess that we might be getting a
swimming pool my dad said no we were
getting very frustrated trying to guess
what the surprise might be my brother
asked how big the surprise was my dad
said that the surprise was quite small
we were not sure what the surprise could
be well we all like it
I ask yes my dad replied every one of
you will love this surprise
we heard a noise it was a crying noise
your surprise wants to see you my dad
said he opened the door to the bedroom
and a tiny puppy came running out
we were all very excited our surprise
was a puppy
it was a little baby spaniel the puppy
loved all of us
she ran around and let all of our faces
we had always wanted a dog
we take turns feeding the puppy and
taking her out for walks
she is growing quickly and will soon be
an adult dog
we all agree that the puppy was the
nicest surprise my dad could have given
us
rhyming words
sometimes my friends and I play a game
it's something we made up so it doesn't
have a name
we like to take words that rhyme we put
them together line by line
do you get the picture now we're playing
the game and this is how i might say I
like to drive a car
I really don't like to go very far if i
decide to take a walk
I'd go with a friend so that we could
talk do you see that these lines rhyme
play the game
if you have the time we could talk about
school or even playing
do you know what i am saying rhyming
words is easy to do
it's fun for me it can be fun for you
just join in and say something or make
it into a song that you can sing
there are so many words that rhyme with
others like smile and mile and mothers
and brothers
I could spend all day just making up
these things i could let my imagination
fly on wings up to the clouds and back
to my mind there are so many rhymes that
i can find there are some words that are
hard to find rhymes for I don't use
those words anymore
I like to choose words that are easy to
rhyme like cat and bat or lime and time
so give it a try I know you'll have fun
I'll say goodbye my rhyming is done
homework
sometimes my teacher gives us homework I
don't mind doing my homework
except when the weather is really nice
and all my friends are outside those
nights I'd rather be outside with them
so I try to get my homework done quickly
tonight i have some english homework
we have been reading a book we have to
read a chapter of the book and answer
the questions at the end of the chapter
it is an interesting book so the
homework for this is quite easy
my math homework is not so easy
I have to do some addition and
subtraction I don't mind that but there
are some problems that need to be solved
the problems involve addition
subtraction and multiplication
I am not too good with numbers I need to
work harder on my math I just finished a
project for history
I had to make a map of canada with
diagrams showing the roots of all the
Explorers it was an interesting project
because i have been to some of the
places that the Explorers went to I
don't have any science homework at
school we are growing bean plants we go
in every day and see how the plants have
grown we write down all the changes that
occur in the plant every day
the only other homework that i have is
geography
I have a map of canada and i have to
write the names of all the provinces and
their capitals on it
it won't take me long to do that because
i know all the provinces with my
homework is all done i will go inside
and play ball with my friends until it's
time to come in
I am a good student I get good marks
because I like school my favorite
subjects are physical education
english and history math is my least
favorite subject but I'm trying to
improve my marks in that