I am curious I am curious about many
things i would like to find the answers
to a lot of questions that i have one
holds the stars up in the sky
why does ice form on the top of the lake
when it is cold
is there life on other planets why do we
not fall off the face of the earth
how did caterpillars turn into
butterflies all of these things are
mysteries to me
there are so many questions that are
unanswered
I think I should go to the library and
get a book to find out why people grow
old
what makes a television work i also want
to know where electricity comes from
who is the strongest person in the world
who was the smartest person in the world
why does some people have blonde hair
and some people have black hair
why do people in different countries
speak different languages
why do people have to die why are no two
snowflakes are alike
what makes people fall in love
what makes the rivers run why does the
sunrise every morning
how did the oceans form why did the
dinosaurs vanish from the earth
I wonder if I'll ever find out the
answers to all of my questions
I think I'll have to study hard and stay
in school to find out everything that I
want to know some questions never get
answered it is good to be curious people
who are curious about things are the
ones who learn a lot and some curious
people go on to invent things and make
important discoveries
creative people some people are just
born to create that's what I think some
people just have the need to write
stories composed beautiful music or
paint pictures creativity seems to be
inside them and they need to let it out
it's good that we have people like that
composers like Mozart and Chopin have
given us music that is incredibly
beautiful
it's not just the classical composers
who have given us great pieces of music
there are modern composers who have
written great songs also Elton John is
an example of someone who has composed
many wonderful songs
andrew lloyd webber has given us some
very popular musicals like cats and the
Phantom of the Opera
there are so many talented and creative
people in this world when you visit an
art gallery you marvel at how artists
are able to recreate realism or make up
something that seems totally unreal yet
beautiful
the American artist Norman Rockwell
painted some pictures that actually look
like photographs
he tried to portray life as it was in
America through his paintings one can
get a good sense of American life
through the years
on the other hand artists like Jackson
Pollock did not portray realism Jackson
Pollock painted
abstract pictures his paintings are just
as good as Norman Rockwell's but they
are entirely different some books that
we read our classics
Mark Twain portrayed american life
through his characters
Tom Sawyer and Huckleberry Finn Charles
Dickens brought Victorian England to
life through his books
most people are familiar with his
Christmas Carol where the mean and
miserable Scrooge learns the true
meaning of Christmas
people don't have to read the classics
there are modern writers who entertain
readers through their stories
Stephen King has written a number of
horror stories some of his books
have even been made into movies we are
lucky to have creative people who share
their gifts with us if you are lucky
enough to be creative
you should use your talents to create
works of art that we can all share
career choices what do you want to be
when you grow up there are so many
things that you can be
you might want to work in the field of
law you could be a police officer
you could be a judge or a lawyer maybe
you'd like to work in the food industry
you could be a cook or a waitress you
might want to manage a hotel dining room
perhaps you would want to do room
service in a hotel
you could be a chef and make fancy meals
for people
maybe show business is what you'd like
to be involved in
you could act in television shows or
movies
you could sing or play an instrument in
a band
if you like to help people you could go
into medicine
you could be a doctor or a nurse you
might be a surgeon and operate on people
there are other jobs in the field of
medicine to you could be an x-ray
technician or a lab technician
it takes a lot of Education to be a
doctor
maybe you would rather be a teacher you
could teach in a primary school or high
school
if you don't want to work with children
you could become a professor at a
university
there are hundreds of other jobs to
choose from to you might want to fix
cars or work in a store you could be a
dentist or a veterinarian
you could be a janitor or a zookeeper
there are so many jobs and I just can't
name them all
maybe you'd like to be a minister or an
organist at a church
you could be a babysitter or a shop
clerk you might be interested in being
an astronaut or a baker
you could work in a bank or at a shop
you could work on a construction crew
and build roads and houses maybe you'd
rather decorate the houses
so you could become an interior
decorator
you could cut hair or be a driving
instructor
the list is endless there are even jobs
that you may never have heard about the
choice is yours
you just choose whatever you want to be
and do your best to become that i could
go on forever
you could work in a library you could be
a factory worker or a fisherman
you could make clothes or build bridges
you could watch windows or be a
bricklayer
the possibilities are endless
I need glasses I have been having
trouble seeing the blackboard
everything is blurry i keep getting
headaches
I told my mother about it and she made
an appointment with the up tom at rest
I went to a place where they made me
read words and letters on a chart some
of the words were big and some were very
small
I tried to read everything but sometimes
I couldn't see some of the small letters
the optometrist would cover one of my
eyes while i read the charts
then she would cover my other eye
she even put some drops in my eyes
I asked the optometrist if I had passed
or failed the test
she laughed and said it wasn't that kind
of tests that you passed or failed
she was just tried to find out if I
needed classes
I did meet glasses my mother and I
looked around there were many pairs of
frames
I wanted something that was in style I
tried on many pairs of frames
some of them look good on me and some of
them look really funny on me
I finally chose a frame that was my
favorite
I gave them to a lady who did some
measurements
she told me to come back on Friday to
get my classes on friday i got my
glasses my friends like them they said i
looked smart in my classes I wore them
to school on monday and i was able to
see the blackboard clearly I didn't
realize how much I hadn't been able to
see now I don't get headaches anymore
i'm glad that i have my glasses
everything is a lot clearer now
I am clumsy my mother says that I am
clumsy
my father says that I am clumsy i know
that i am clumsy
I do things all the time that are clumsy
I fall down for no reason at all if
there is a crack in the sidewalk
I will be sure to trip on it and fall
down if I carry a plate of food in the
cafeteria
I almost always either drop it or bump
into someone with it
I don't try to do these things it just
happens when i drink juice
i miss my mouth and get juice all over
my shirt
I always have something spilled on my
clothes
last week I opened a jar of peanut
butter the jar flew out of my hands and
landed upside down on the floor
there was a big glob of peanut butter on
the floor yesterday I knocked over the
sugar bowl
there was a big sticky mess on the floor
I bumped my head when I get into the car
I ripped my pants on things I lose my
money out of my pockets
I step on the cat's tail I always feel
bad when i do that because the cat
thinks I don't love her
I don't need to do these things I am
just a clumsy person
my parents tell me to slow down
I am always in a hurry maybe that's why
I'm so clumsy
maybe it's just the stage that I'm going
through
if it is I hope it is over soon
being clumsy is no fun at all
home alone I remember the first time
that my parents left me home alone
I was very grown-up and I thought that I
would be just fine
I was fine for a while i watch
television and had something to eat
I called my friend on the phone and we
talked for a while then I sat down to
read a book
the house was quiet very quiet
I found myself listening very carefully
I heard a tap tap tapping noise I
wondered where it was coming from
it seemed to be coming from the window I
turned out the lights so that nobody
would see me and I peeked out the window
carefully
I was expecting to see a robber tapping
at my window
there was nobody there it was just a
tree branch swaying in the breeze and
tapping at my window I felt silly
I turned on the lights and sat back down
to read my book
a few minutes later I heard some
creaking noises
I listen carefully then I heard a
clunking noise
I think it might have been the furnace
then there was a whirring noise my
imagination began to play tricks on me
I was imagining that there were all
kinds of creatures in the house
I told myself to grow up I wouldn't let
my imagination run away with me
I was glad when my parents got home I
told them about all the noises that i
had heard my parents laughed and said
that all houses make noises
we're usually just so busy that we don't
hear all the noises that go on
I have stayed home alone many times now
I just ignore all the little creaks and
noises that I here
I'm still alert and listen for anything
suspicious
but i know that there are lots of noises
that are harmless that tree that taps of
my windows still frightens me sometimes
but I'm a lot braver now then I was the
first time that I stayed home alone
family what does the word family means
to you
the easiest way to define family is to
talk about who you are related to
usually there is a mom and a dad and
children who are brothers and sisters
this would be the core family then there
is the extended family which would
include grandparents aunts and uncles
cousins nieces and nephews and in-laws
people married to your brothers or
sisters husband or wife
however i think the word family has a
much deeper meaning the word family
brings words to my mind like love
support help kindness fun love trips
closeness love for giving sharing love
understanding respect and love
you'll notice one word that is repeated
over and over again love
I believe if a family has real love for
one another they will be able to
overcome any problems they may have
actually they may not have too many
problems if they all love and respect
one another
however there are things that cannot be
helped
like death sickness or accidents
it is during those hard times that our
families love helps them to go through
those experiences we had quite a few
children in my family there were
brothers and sisters which included an
adopted brother and a number of foster
children - I was also very fortunate
that I had both my mom and dad to live
with and do things like vacations
together we had a lot of fun and there
were sometimes of tears -
above all we love one another family is
a wonderful thing
I am so lucky
my first job my first real job was
during my last year of high school I had
taken classes in various business
subjects in that last year of high
school
we could do a co-op that meant we could
work part of the time instead of going
to school it would count as a credit
towards our diploma
the place i got a job was at a men's
tailor shop
the owners were a very nice older german
couple they had two other men working
for them to one of the men had had brain
surgery for cancer
he had a big long scar all around the
top of his head
he told me all about it he was always
happy and full of fun
I thought he was very brave the tailor
shop made suits to order one of the
salesmen would measure the man and the
customer would choose a fabric and style
for he or his wife
light the people in the back of the shop
would then cut and sew the suit suits
cost a lot of money
there were also suits already made that
the customer could buy instead if they
wished they could also rent suits or
tuxedos for weddings or parties i worked
at a little desk
I answered the phone wrote letters filed
papers and did some bookkeeping
it was about a mile walk from my school
to work i passed many clothing shops
that wasn't good because i spent a lot
of my money that I earned in those shops
I worked at the tailor shop for almost a
year
it was a good experience and helped me
get my next job with the United States
Navy
that was fun too
first trip away from home today I'm
going to my friends house
her name is Valerie this is going to be
my first trip away from home without my
parents my dad is driving me to
Valerie's house and i'll be staying
there for two weeks
her mom will drive me back home it takes
about one and a half hours to get there
I have to pack enough clothes for play
work and church
i hope i'll pack the right things of
course i have to remember my toothbrush
and hairbrush
Valerie lives on a farm I'll be helping
her dad with milking the cows
I think we'll play up in the hayloft
after we have helped put that Bales into
the barn will be all bitchy when the job
is done
there are a lot of things to do on a
farm
her mom is a good cook and will feed us
well there is a nice pond where we can
go swimming
I mustn't forget my bathing suit I
wonder if the farm dog comes into the
pond to that would be funny
my dad and mom are giving me money just
in case we go shopping
I hope we do go shopping because i want
to buy lots of candy
I won't tell my mom that oh dear
I hear dad yelling let's go I haven't
even finished packing my things yet i
guess i better stop writing this now and
get busy fast
bye
my job
I work at a conservation park called
balls falls
I've only worked there for three weeks
now
I am a tour guide and I tell people the
history of all the old buildings there
somebody told me that one of the houses
i work in is haunted
now I get chills every time I walk into
that house
my boss told me that the stories are
real but i have an active imagination
balls balls is very beautiful
it has two different waterfalls the
upper falls and the Lower Falls there
used to be tons of water cascading over
them which turned a big water wheel to
grind grain
however through the years the amount of
water has really lessened
I love working at balls balls because i
get to work outside a lot i'm getting a
tan in july and august i will be working
with kids they're at a day camp
I am getting ready now making different
crafts and thinking of fun new games to
play
I can't wait to start working with them
I think that will be the best part of
the summer i will be going to work
tomorrow
I usually have to work from nine am
- 4:30 p.m. I also like the people I
work with
they are very nice come two balls falls
and i'll give you a tour