london by john esket read by Judy
Bennett
chapter one this is London every year
more than 9 million people come from
countries all over the world to visit
London they go to the theaters and
museums they look at interesting old
buildings many of them hundreds of years
old they sit or walk in the beautiful
parks or have a drink in a pub they go
to Oxford Street to look at the shops or
to Harrods two million visitors go to
the Tower of London a million more go to
cease and Paul's Cathedral yes London is
a big and beautiful city with lots to
see and do but how did it all begin
chapter 2 in the beginning the name
London comes from the Romans there were
people living here before they came but
we do not know very much about them the
Romans came to England in AD 43 they
built houses and other buildings and
made a town next to the river thames
they called the town Londinium they
built a bridge over the river and ships
came up to Londinium from the sea the
town got bigger and bigger important new
buildings went up and you can see some
of the Roman city wall today near the
Museum of London it was a rich town with
about 50,000 people living in it but
soon after ad 400 the Romans left
londonium to go back to Rome and nobody
lived in the town for many hundreds of
years the buildings began to fall down
Danish soldiers destroyed more buildings
nearly 500 years later king alfred was
king of england then he got the danes to
leave London and his men built the town
again in 1066 William the Conqueror came
to England from France to be king soon
after he began to build the Tower of
London when Henry the Eighth was king in
1509 50,000 people lived in London again
by
a year 1600 there were 200,000 but a lot
of them lived in old and dirty buildings
in 1665 a hundred thousand people died
from an illness called the plague this
was called the year of the Great Plague
a year later in 1666 there was a big
fire the fire of london it began in a
house in pudding Lane near London Bridge
more than a quarter of a million
Londoners lost their homes in the fire
it destroyed Zant Paul's Cathedral and
eighty-eight other churches but the fire
also destroyed most of the worst old
buildings and the new houses that went
up after this were better for people to
live in a new scent Paul's Cathedral was
built between 1675 and 17 11 by 1881
more than 3 million people lived in
London today more than 6 million people
live here there were eight million in
the 1960s but in the 1970s and 1980s
people moved out of the centre of London
chapter 3 visiting the city a quick and
easy way to get to different places in
the city is to use an underground train
the trains run all day and most of the
night buy your ticket before you get on
the train it's better not to make your
journey between eight o'clock and ten
o'clock in the morning or four o'clock
and six o'clock in the evening these are
called the rush hours thousands of
people are going to work or coming home
again then and it is difficult to move
or to find a place to sit on the train
you can see much more of London from one
of its famous red buses some special
visitors buses take you to many of the
interesting places in the city on one
journey it takes about one and a half
hours but you can break your journey and
get off and on again at the different
places you want to visit London taxis
are called black cabs most of them are
black but some are not you can stop one
if it has a for-hire sign on it the
drivers are usually friendly and helpful
why not take a boat trip along the River
Thames boats leave Westminster pier and
Charing Cross pier and they go to tao
appear and Greenwich
between April and October you can take a
longer boat trip to Hampton Court about
four hours a beautiful palace in a big
park
chapter for some places to go the Queen
has her London home at Buckingham Palace
it is at the end of the mal a long road
that begins at Trafalgar Square at
half-past eleven most mornings the
soldiers at Buckingham Palace change the
guard it takes about 30 minutes and
hundreds of visitors come to watch and
in august and sep tember you can usually
visit some of the rooms in the palace
but there are always lots of people
coming to see them so be ready to wait
you can also visit the Royal Mews at the
palace this is the home of the Queen's
horses and coaches the Queen's gallery
is also at the palace and you can visit
it at most times of the year here you
can see pictures from all over the world
the Tower of London is now a museum and
one of London's most famous buildings
more than 2 million people visited every
year yeoman warders also called
beefeaters tell them all about the tower
you can see the crown jewels and visit
the bloody tower and the white tower or
take a walk around the wall and perhaps
see one of the towers famous black birds
the Ravens tower bridge is near the
Tower of London it is one of the most
famous bridges in the city and first
opened in 1894 st. Paul's Cathedral is
not far away on Lud get hill it was
built by Sir Christopher Wren after the
fire of london Wren built more than 50
London church's visitors can go up to
the golden gallery to look across London
chapter 5 Westminster Westminster Abbey
is more than 900 years old and is a very
famous London church after William the
Conqueror every king and queen of
England was crowned king or queen here
the houses of parliament are near
westminster abbey this is the home of
the british government the clock high up
on the building is called Big Ben the
Prime Minister the head of the British
government lives at 10 Downing Street
walk along Parliament Street to
Whitehall past the government buildings
and you can see the little Street on
your left parks and gardens when you are
tired of looking at buildings you can
sit or walk in one of London's beautiful
parks
Hyde Park has a lake in the middle
called the serpentine and you can take a
boat out on the water it is a good place
to get away from the crowds and the
noise of the city you can listen to the
speakers at speakers corner near Marble
Arch people from all over the world come
and speak here you can ask a speaker
some difficult questions if you like or
you can stand on a box and speak to some
of the listeners Kensington Gardens is
next to Hyde Park here you can see the
Statue of Peter Pan the famous boy in
the children's story Peter Pan by JM
Barrie Regent's Park is the home of
London Zoo the zoo has thousands of
birds and animals from all over the
world there is also a theater in the
park on a summer's evening you can sit
out under the night sky and watch a play
by William Shakespeare England's most
famous writer st. James's Park is next
to the mal it is smaller but many people
think it is more beautiful
chapter 6 shops and eating
the most famous shop in London some
people say the most famous in the world
is Herod's in Knightsbridge it opened in
18-49 Oxford Street has many big shops
selfridges Marks & Spencer John Lewis
debenhams there are always lots of
people looking at the shops here but at
Christmas thousands more people come to
see the wonderful Christmas lights and
to buy things for their friends and
family for Christmas
Charing Cross is famous for its book
shops there are lots of them and they
sell old and new books one of the oldest
and most famous is foils it has
thousands of books but it can sometimes
be very difficult to find the book you
want
Covent Garden was once a big food market
but now it has lots of small shops and
cafes and there are street performers to
watch
there are two very famous markets in
London petticoat lane market open on
Sundays is in Middlesex Street and is a
good place to buy cheap clothes and
things for the home
at the market in Portobello Road open on
Saturdays you can buy old clocks old
chairs and tables and hundreds of other
things
you can find food from nearly every
country in the world in London
in Soho in the West End of London see
map on pages 18 and 19 you can eat food
from Italy India China Japan Greece and
lots more places there are also
thousands of pubs in the city in many
pubs you can eat as well as drink or why
not have some English fish and chips
they are cheap and good to eat or you
can have tea at the Ritz in Piccadilly
or at the Savoy Hotel in the Strand
chapter 7 going out theaters and music
London's West End has some of the best
theaters in the world so tickets can be
expensive go in the afternoon it is
often cheaper there is something for
everybody from a play by the Royal
Shakespeare Company at the barbican
theater to agatha christie's the
mousetrap this play began in nineteen
fifty two and thousands of visitors see
it every year
there are lots of cinemas to visit the
most expensive are in the West End but
you can sometimes get cheap tickets on
Mondays you can hear wonderful music and
singing from all over the world at the
royal opera house in Covent Garden the
royal albert hall in Kensington gore the
london coliseum in st. martin's lane and
the barbican centre silk street for
ballet go to the Sadler's Wells theatre
in rosebery avenue or to the royal opera
house to get cheap tickets buy them an
hour or two before it begins do you like
to listen to jazz musicians you can hear
some of the best at Ronnie Scott's club
in frist street or at the Bulls head
barnes at barnes bridge or at 100 club
at 100 oxford street
sport
some of the most famous English football
clubs are in London you can see Arsenal
play at Arsenal Stadium avenel road n5
Chelsea play at Stamford Bridge Fulham
Road sw6 and Tottenham Hotspur play at
White Hart Lane high road n 17 to watch
the very English game of cricket go to
Lord's Cricket Ground in st. John's Wood
nw8 this is the home of cricket for most
English people
you
chapter 8 museums and galleries the
British Museum in great Russell Street
is the biggest Museum in Britain tickets
are free the Museum of London at 150
London wall is one of the most
interesting museums in the city it tells
the story of London and its people one
more museum that tells a story is the
Museum of the moving image momi on the
south bank under Waterloo Bridge this
tells the story of cinema and television
and there are many things for visitors
to see and do you can act with actors on
a film set or you can read the news on
TV
four million people visit the National
Gallery in Trafalgar Square every year
they come to look at more than 2,000
pictures tickets are free at the
national portrait gallery in Sint
Maartens place you can see pictures of
famous people tickets are free here to
the london dungeon in tooley street is a
museum of horror half a million people
visited every year but they don't always
stay to see it all Madame Tussauds in
Marylebone Road is famous for its people
made from wax you can see famous people
from the past and famous people of today
Abraham Lincoln Mahatma Gandhi Nelson
Mandela Pavarotti Marilyn Monroe Charlie
Chaplin Sylvester Stallone and in the
chamber of horrors you can see some very
bad people
chapter nine places and parades the city
Londoners often talk about the city see
map on pages 18 and 19 they are talking
about the oldest part of London the home
of the Bank of England and many other
big offices about 5,000 people live in
the city and at weekends it feels empty
but between Monday and Friday nearly
half a million people come here to work
in the banks and offices look for the
city man with their dark suits and
umbrellas
st. Paul's Cathedral is in the middle of
the city and the Bank of England has an
interesting museum that you can visit
also in the city is a very tall building
60.6 meters high called the monument
Christopher Wren built this too and it
stands on the place where the fire of
london began in 1666
some interesting and exciting days every
year on a saturday morning in june foot
guards and horse guards have a parade
for the Queen this is called trooping
the colour the colour is the flag that
the soldiers carry thousands of people
stand in the mall to see the Queen and
the soldiers go past the exciting
Notting Hill Carnival is on the last
Sunday and Monday in August there are
two wonderful parades to watch one on
Sunday and one on Monday and you can see
them going through the streets near
Portobello Road and Ladbroke Grove
on the second saturday in november
Londoners can see their new Lord Mayor
in the Lord Mayor's Show a parade from
mansion house the Lord Mayor's home to
the Strand the Lord Mayor is the most
important person in the city after the
Queen the first mayor of london was
Henry fitzalan in 1189 they were not
called Lord mares until the time of King
Henry the Eighth big red buses London
policeman Buckingham Palace speakers
corner Big Ben notting hill carnival
these are some of the things you can
find in London but there are many many
more come and see
you