I want to dye my hair green
many of my friends have dyed their hair
different colors
I don't mean normal hair colors like
brown or black
my friends have dyed their hair orange
purple and blue
I told my mother that I would like to
dye my hair green
I explain to my mother that I would only
use food coloring the green would not
last forever
my mother said that dying your hair was
a silly fad
she said that I would not look good with
green hair
I said that if I couldn't dye my hair
green
maybe I could get a nose ring my mother
said no I said that maybe a tattoo on my
arm would be nice
my mother said no way my mother said
that she did some crazy things when she
was a young girl she said that she used
to iron her hair to make it straight
that sounds quite boring to me my friend
Joan came over her hair is dyed bright
pink
my father said nice hair Joan I don't
think that he really meant it
my mother says that when I am an adult I
can dye my hair
whatever crazy color I like but for now
she would like me to leave my hair its
natural color
I tried to tell her that all my friends
were doing it
my mother asked if all your friends were
jumping off a cliff would you do it - I
said no I think I'll have to wait to
have green hair but maybe by the time
i'm old enough to dye my hair green
I won't want it that color my mother
says that fads change all the time
one day something might be popular and
the next day it's not in style at all
I'll just have to live without green
hair for now I wonder what the Fed will
be next month
why do people dislike other people
some people don't like other people just
because they look different
I think that is silly I don't think that
it is fair to judge someone by the way
they look
some people look very nice but they are
mean or cruel
some people look very ordinary but they
are incredibly nice
I remember when I was in grade one I saw
a girl across the room she had a mean
look on her face
I thought to myself that she was
probably not a very nice person
I stayed away from her and played with
the other children then we had to play a
game and the teacher said that she would
pick partners for us
the teacher picked the girl with the
mean face as my partner
I didn't think that the game would be
much fun at all with a partner who
seemed as mean as that girl
I walked up to her and said hello the
girl's face changed
she smiled at me and she began to talk
to me
hermine face disappeared we had lots of
fun playing the game
we laughed a lot and enjoyed each
other's company that girl became my best
friend
now when I look at her I see what is
inside her
sometimes she doesn't smile but I know
what she is like she is a kind and funny
person
I have learned that you can't judge a
book by it's cover
it is not fair to dislike someone just
because they don't look like you want
them to look you have to get to know a
person
it doesn't matter to me what color a
person's skin is it doesn't matter to me
if they are short or tall skinny or fat
or happy or sad looking
I judge people by how they treat me and
I try to treat people like I would want
to be treated
the birthday gift
it is going to be my father's birthday
what can I give him
I don't have much money i have looked
all through the stores and i have not
found anything that I think he would
like or that i can afford
I have thought very hard about what to
buy for him
I thought that he might like some candy
but my father really doesn't eat many
sweets
I thought that he might like a new shirt
but he has lots of clothes
I can't afford a new car or computer for
him
I was watching him on the weekend he cut
the grass wash the car took out the
garbage
we did the garden and water the plants I
got an idea
I went to my room and took out some
paper
I cut out pieces of paper and I wrote on
them
I wrote on one piece of paper that i
would wash the car every weekend for the
summer
I wrote on another piece that I would
take out the garbage every week for the
summer
i also wrote that I would cut the grass
weed the garden and water the plants
every week for the summer
I made a birthday card for my dad and I
put the pieces of paper inside it
I went downstairs and gave my gift to my
dad my dad thought that the gift was
very thoughtful
he said that it was a gift from the
heart I did all those things for my dad
all summer
he said that he had a lot of free time
because I helped him so much
my dad and I are good friends I don't
mind doing things for him because I know
that he is always there to help me out a
good gift doesn't have to be something
that costs a lot
my dad says that the best gifts are the
ones that show how much you care for the
other person
I'm glad my dad liked his gift
New Year's Day
on New Year's Day people start a new
year
many people make resolutions they
resolved to be better people
some people decide that they will lose
weight so that they can be healthier
some people decide to give up smoking
they also want to be healthier there are
all kinds of resolutions that people
make some people try not to lose their
tempers
some people say that they will work
harder there are people who try to give
up bad habits
every year my brother says that he will
stop biting his nails
he stops biting his nails in January but
my februari he always starts again
that is the thing about New Year's
resolutions people seldom keep them
everybody starts out with good
intentions but it is very hard to stick
with them
I don't make new year's resolutions I
find that I just break them
I just work day by day to break my bad
habits
I know that they eat too many sweets
every day I just try to resist them
I think that every day is a new day
regardless of whether it is New Year's
Day or not bad habits are hard to break
the best thing is never to start any bad
habits
I don't know if my brother will ever
stop biting his nails but I know that
each January he intends to stop
maybe one of these new years days he'll
get over that habit
if I could fly
I sometimes imagine what it would be
like if I could fly like a bird
just imagine what it would be like to
soar into the sky flying high above the
trees you could stand on high rooftops
and never be afraid of falling
you would see so many things as you flew
over rooftops and forests you would feel
incredibly free as you traveled from
place to place not bothered by road
signs or traffic jams
if I could fly like a bird I would start
from my backyard and travel through town
I would look down on the houses and
factories when I got tired i would land
in a field and take a nap
I would travel above rivers and follow
them as they wound along and emptied
into lakes and oceans
I would fly above parks and i would call
out to the children as I flew high above
them
I would dip and dive as I flew I would
soar up high and dive down low so that I
could almost touch the tree tops
have you ever flown I know that you
can't fly like a bird but you might have
taken an airplane ride when you're in an
airplane you pass through clouds
it is exciting to take an airplane ride
I love taking airplane flights
I like to look down at the earth when
you're up that high
everything below you looks tiny that's
the closest i'll get to flying like a
bird but i can still use my imagination
and spread my wings and soar high above
the world just like a bird
what I look for in a friend
what is it that makes somebody your
friend some people are nice and you have
fun with them
some people are nice to talk to but they
don't become special to you
some people become very close to you
those people are the ones who become
your good friends
did you ever wonder why certain people
do become your good friends friends
usually have something in common
often friends enjoy doing the same
things as each other
maybe they like the same sports or the
same music or maybe they can even talk
about problems or schoolwork friends
usually find a common bond
friends share ideas and listen to each
other sometimes people who don't have
similar interests even become friends
you can learn a lot from a person who
likes different things than you
the most important thing about friends
is that they must communicate with each
other
a good friend is a person who takes the
time to listen to the other person one
of the most important things that i
think a friend should have is a sense of
humor I like to laugh with my friends
I like to feel comfortable around my
friends it is nice to be able to talk
and laugh with people who have similar
interests
it is nice to share things with people
and learn about their interests you
become a better person if you are able
to learn things from others
life is a journey on that journey you
meet many people some of those people
will change your life you have to choose
your friends with care
a good friend is worth more than all the
gold in the world
a good friend will make your journey
through life more pleasant make friends
along the way and the path through life
will be very rewarding
a funny thing happened on the way to
school
last Friday it was very windy I was
walking down the street with my friend
John we were having a difficult time
walking against the wind the wind was
pushing against us and we felt the force
of it pressing against us
we even had a hard time breathing we
were walking slowly we watch the leaves
as they danced and twirled in the wind
we watched a plastic bag as it flew by
us we saw a little boy whose baseball
cap flew right off his head his cap flew
along the sidewalk and he had to chase
it
he finally caught it and he held it in
his hands tightly after he got it back
the trees were swaying frantically their
branches swished and waved in the wild
wind
John and I were hit by flying bits of
paper and leaves
we laughed when a garbage can lid rolled
along and hit John in the leg
we saw another garbage can rolling along
the road as if it was alive
everything was moving because of the
wind then the funniest thing happened
I wasn't paying any attention and a
paper bag came flying up the street
toward us
it hit me right in the face and covered
my whole face
at first I didn't know what had happened
I was blinded
I couldn't see where I was going I
stopped and held out my hands when I
stopped the bag fell off my face
I looked at John he was laughing very
hard
he was laughing so hard that tears were
rolling down his cheeks
he said that I looked very funny with
the brown paper bag stuck to my face
I started to laugh - we laughed about it
all the way to school
John said that he wished he had a camera
he would have taken a picture of me with
a bag on my face
advice
sometimes my mother gives me advice
she tells me to save my money for a
rainy day
she says that I should eat my vegetables
if I want to be strong when I grow up
she says that you reap what you sow I
didn't know what that one meant so i
asked her she said that if you are good
to people they will be good to you if
you do bad things and bad things will
come back to you
my mother is always giving me advice she
says that a penny saved is a penny
earned
I am still thinking about that one some
of these things are difficult to
understand my mother is very wise
she says that she has learned from her
mistakes
she tells me that she would like me not
to make mistakes but she says that
everyone does make mistakes
the important thing is that we learn
from our mistakes
my mother says that nobody is perfect
my mother tells my sister that time is
precious
my sister wastes time and my mother
doesn't like that
my mother tells me to be true to myself
she says that I should not follow the
crowd
I should listen to my own conscience and
do what I think is right
she says that it doesn't matter if you
fail at something the important thing is
that you try if you've done your best
then that is all that matters
I listened to my mother I think she
gives very good advice
my mother has a lot of common sense i
hope i am as wise as she is
when I have children of my own sometimes
I wish that she would not give me so
much advice
I think that I know what I'm doing but
in the end i always remember what she
has said and I try to live by the
standards that she has set for me take
the advice that your parents give you
they only have your best interests at
heart
a trip to the hospital
I have to get my tonsils out I'm not
really happy about it but I'm tired of
being sick and having sore throats
I have to go to the hospital two hours
before my surgery my mother will go with
me
the nurses will take my temperature and
check my blood pressure
they will make sure that i am ready for
my operation
I will be dressed in a white gown and i
will be wheeled down the hall to the
operating room
I can't have anything to eat or drink
for a long time before my surgery my
mother will walk down the hall with me
then she will wave goodbye as they will
me into the operating room the doctor
and the nurses will be busy in the
operating room
they will be getting ready to perform my
surgery the doctor will say hello to me
and tell me that he is going to put me
to sleep
he will put something into my arm he
will tell me to count backwards from ten
I think that I will only say ten nine
and then i will be fast asleep
I won't be awake for the surgery when I
wake up I will be surprised that the
surgery is over my throat will hurt and
i probably won't feel very good
my mother will be there with me the
nurses will give me a drink and try to
make me comfortable
I won't be in the hospital overnight I
will go home later in the day my parents
will have to make sure that i have a lot
to drink
I can't eat any hard foods or they will
hurt my throat
I will sleep a lot because I will not
feel very well for a couple of days
it won't take long before I recover from
my surgery
sometimes we need surgery to make us
feel better hospitals can be a bit
frightening but the doctors and nurses
are very nice and their job is to make
you better
what my cat did
one day I was sitting in a chair
drinking a cup of tea
my cat came into the room and sat on my
lap she was quite content and she SAT
there purring my cat likes to drink
water and sometimes she drinks milk
I would never give her tea to drink cats
just don't drink tea
we were sitting there quietly when
suddenly my cat stood up she was looking
at something on the floor
she crouched down low and got ready to
pounce
I saw what she was looking at it was a
huge centipede
I think that centipedes are ugly they
have many legs and they move very fast
I would hate to have one crawl over me
my cat jump to the floor and she ran
over to the centipede
she was incredibly fast I was surprised
that she caught the centipede
she put her paw on it and then she
reached down and ate the centipede the
centipede must not have tasted very good
my cat got a funny look on her face and
she looked like she was trying to get a
bad taste out of her mouth
I was thinking that I would be sick if I
ate a centipede my cat looked at B and
jump back up in my chair
she stuck her face in my teacup and took
a big drink of tea
I was shocked i had never seen a cat
drink tea before I think that the
centipede must have tasted so bad that
my cat just needed something to wash the
taste out of her mouth
guess what I didn't finish my tea
I threw it out and washed out the cup my
cat has never had a drink of tea since
that day she has also never eaten
another centipede if a centipede walks
by she just pretends that she doesn't
see it
if I was tiny
imagine what life would be like if you
were two inches tall
you would have to be careful that nobody
stepped on you you would have to watch
out for cats dogs and birds
it would be very dangerous but just
think of the things that you could do
you could live in a dollhouse or even a
shoebox
you could use a bottle cap for a plate
you would have to wear dolls clothes a
stamp would make a lovely picture to
hang on your wall
you could hide in a Mousehole or a
drawer
you wouldn't need much food you could
probably live comfortably on the crumbs
that people would leave on the table a
thimble would make a good cup if you
went outside the grass would seem like a
jungle an insect would be huge and
frightening a puddle would seem to be an
ocean
you could cross the puddle in a paper
cup and use a spoon for or a matchbox
would make a good bed with a
handkerchief as a bedspread you brush
your hair with a toothbrush but you'd
never find anything small enough to
brush your teeth with you could take a
ride on the back of a mouse
you wouldn't find any books that were
small enough to read but you might read
the back of a pill bottle
you could ride in a toy car and have a
super ball for a swimming pool a leaf
could be your umbrella and a mitten
would make a great sleeping bag if you
use your imagination
you could think of something to use for
almost all your purposes
being small might be fun but then again
it would be frightening
I'd be afraid of my pet cat I wouldn't
want a book to fall on me I would be
afraid of being swept away by a big gust
of wind
I think I'd rather be my size
do people have the right to smoke in
public
my father used to small
he got very ill
the doctor told him that he had to quit
smoking
my father tried for a long time to quit
it was very difficult for him smoking is
an addiction
after many months
my father finally gave up smoking but he
still craved a cigarette once in a while
he says that quitting smoking is the
hardest thing that he has ever done
when my father did smoke he smoked
everywhere
he smoked in restaurants stores and many
public buildings
now you are not allowed to smoke in a
lot of public places
when my father smoked the rules were not
so strict people could smoke just about
anywhere
it really wasn't fair to the people who
didn't smoke their clothes always
smelled like smoke and they breathe in
secondhand smoke some people think that
the second hand smoke is actually worse
for you than if you smoke yourself
people with smoke in their houses and
very young children would inhale the
smoke that was in the air
some people still smoke in their houses
and their children breathe in the smoke
some restaurants have areas for smokers
and non-smokers
but usually the smoke drifts from one
area to the other
there are some businesses that have been
smoking altogether
personally I think that smoking in
public places should be completely
banned
I don't think that I should have to
breathe in another person smoke if I
choose not to smoke myself it wouldn't
be fair for a nonsmoker to get lung
cancer because they had to be in a place
where smokers were allowed to light up
I know that smoking is a powerful
addiction and that it is very difficult
to quit but smokers should restrict
their smoking to places where there is
nobody else around
lung cancer is an awful disease
nobody should have to suffer with monk
answer people should be educated about
the dangers of smoking smoking should be
banned in public places but eventually I
would like to believe that fewer people
will smoke it would be nice to live in a
smoke-free environment
if I were a giant
if I were a giant I wouldn't be able to
fit in my house I'd have to live in a
building that had a high ceiling but i
probably have a hard time getting
through the door
I'd have to make my own clothes but
where would I get a giant needle and
thread to sew with I couldn't ride in a
car or a plane
I suppose I would just have to take
giant steps to get from place to place
I would have to be very careful not to
step on anybody or anything
when I talked people would cover their
ears my voice would sound very loud to
them I wouldn't find the shoes to cover
my feet
I wouldn't find a knife and fork to eat
my dinner with I might have to use a
rake as a fork
my dinner would be huge what would I
cook my dinner in
I certainly wouldn't find an oven big
enough to put my dinner and if I sneezed
it would be like a hurricane
if I fell down it would be like an
earthquake
I wouldn't have any friends because
everyone would be too tiny for me to
talk to
I think that being a giant would be very
lonely
I couldn't have just one Apple I would
have to have a lot of apples to fill me
up
I would have to drink gallons and
gallons of water to quench my thirst
I could never relax under a tree I would
be taller than all the trees
I don't think that being a giant would
be fun
I won't ever make a wish to be a giant i
would rather be my height
I'm very happy the way I am yeah
superstitions
I am NOT superstitious are you yesterday
was Friday the 13th
some people think that friday the 13 is
an unlucky day I think that it is just
like any other day
some people believe that if a black cat
crosses your path you will have bad luck
I don't believe that either
my mother always gets upset if i open an
umbrella in the house
she says that is bad luck she is
probably right about that one because an
open umbrella would take up a lot of
space and you might not things over
if your left hand is itchy you are
supposed to get money i have had an
energy left hand before but I haven't
received any money because of it
it is bad like to walk under a ladder
that is probably true because you might
knock somebody off the ladder or have a
can of paint fall on top of you
if you are acting in a play it is bad
luck if someone says good luck to you
this is very confusing you were supposed
to tell an actor to break a leg
it doesn't mean that you want the actor
to break his leg
it means good luck to the actor actors
have a lot of superstitions that are
very unusual
I am NOT superstitious I don't believe
in superstitions at all
it is just fun to learn about
superstitions
some of them are very old and have been
passed down from generation to
generation
I once did a project at school on
superstitions
it was a very interesting topic and they
got a good mark for it
my favorite bedtime story
every night when I was little my mother
would read me a bedtime story
my favorite story was Tom's midnight
garden
this was a story by Filipa pierce it was
quite a long book and it took quite a
few nights for my mother to read the
entire book to me in Toms midnight
garden
Tom moves to the city to stay with his
aunt and uncle he is very bored at their
apartment
they have no children so tom has nothing
to do
one night the clock strikes 13 times
tom knows that this is impossible
a clock can only strike up to 12 times
he sneaks downstairs and goes outside
when he goes outside there is a
wonderful garden
that wasn't there the day before
the next day Tom goes outside and finds
there is no garden the garden only seems
to appear at night every night
Tom slips out to this wonderful garden
and meet some people in the garden
he meets a girl named caddy happy and
Tom become very good friends in this
garden
some very strange things happen in this
book
there are some coincidences that keep
you guessing about what is really going
on the surprise ending is wonderful
I really enjoyed Tom's midnight garden
and I was very sad when my mother and I
came to the end of the book
I felt that I had visited the magical
garden with tom
it is a book that i will remember all my
life
if I found a magic lamp
if I was walking down the beach one day
and I happened to bump my toe on a magic
lamp
I would pick it up and rub it if it was
a real magic lamp
but i don't believe that there really is
a magic lamp a genie would pop out in a
cloud of smoke and he would call me
master
he would say that he would grant me
three wishes
I would have to think very hard about
those wishes because I wouldn't want to
waste them
I don't think I'd want millions of
dollars
money doesn't buy happiness or so they
say
I might wish for good health
because if your health isn't good you
won't be able to enjoy anything
some people might wish for beauty but
beauty is only skin deep
some people would wish for a mansion or
a beautiful car or a big boat
I don't want any of those things some
people would want Fame
some people would want talent
some people would wish for happiness
that might be a good thing to wish for
yes maybe I'd wish for health and
happiness
but what would my third wish be I could
wish for something enormous something
global I could wish for world peace
that would be a wonderful thing if
somebody could grant me that
yes that would probably be my third wish
it's too bad there aren't any genies
inside magic lamps
I won't get my three wishes
I can still work toward getting my
wishes
I can eat well and exercise to stay
healthy
I can be involved with a lot of things
and be with my friends to stay happy
I can volunteer my time two different
organizations to help achieve world
peace
I can do my fair share in my community
to help others
that's how i can get my three wishes not
through a magic lamp
I can only get what I want through self
determination and hard work that is the
key to getting your wishes fulfilled
help
did you ever have to call for help
were you ever in a situation that was an
emergency
it is good to know what to do in case of
an emergency
you should always know how to get in
touch with the police and fire
departments
i have read stories were very young boys
or girls have called the police and
saved their friends or family members
lives because they knew just who to get
a hold of
if you see a fire you should call the
fire department
a lot of tragedies have been prevented
because the calls have been made quickly
it is important than emergency vehicles
arrived very quickly
that is why those vehicles have sirens
when their sirens go
it means to get out of the way
policemen firemen and ambulance
attendants are trained to handle very
difficult situations they often save
people's lives they go through a lot of
training to become good at what they do
they never panic in emergencies
for your part you should keep emergency
numbers near the phone or know what the
emergency numbers are
where I live there is a special number
that you call for any emergency
we teach that number to everyone even
very tiny children
it is important to remain calm if you
need help
if you call an emergency number
you have to be able to speak clearly and
tell the person you are talking to
exactly what the problem is
I hope you are never in an emergency
situation but it is a good idea to be
prepared
the peach orchard
when I was very young I lived in erie
peach orchard
now there is a park where the orchard
used to be
I always remember the peach orchard
because my grandmother and I used to go
there and pick peaches
the owner of the orchard would let all
the neighbors pick peaches
it's not the fact that I used to get
many ripe tasty peaches that I remember
it's the time that I used to spend with
my grandmother that I remember my
grandmother was very old but she was
very healthy
she used to walk a lot i think that is
what kept her fit
she had a lot of energy so she like to
go to a lot of places
she would get a fruit basket and then
she would ask me if I wanted to go to
the orchard
I always said yes because I enjoyed
walking through the orchard on a sunny
day
we never climbed up on a ladder to reach
the peaches
we just reached for the low hanging
fruit my grandmother and I used to talk
all the time that we were out there
it was nice to spend time with her
she told me many stories about when she
was a young girl
we laughed and got to know each other
better
my grandmother only visited us during
the summer
she lived in california and i lived in
Niagara Falls
so we didn't get to spend a lot of time
with each other
we enjoyed the hot summer days in the
orchard
you could smell the peaches and the bees
buzz lazily bias
my grandmother would point out different
insects and birds to me
I learned a lot about nature from her
we would end up with a big basket of
peaches
when we got home my mother would wash
the peaches and often she would bake a
peach pie for us
nobody bakes the peach pie like my
mother it's good to have memories like
that childhood memories of time spent
with my grandmother are very precious to
me sometimes is just the simple things
that you do in life that leave you with
the nicest memories
learning to dance
I went to England with my mother she
used to be a singer in a band
we went to the hotel that she used to
sing at it was a big fancy hotel
some of the people that she knew when
she saying in the band were still there
they remembered my mother and they had a
good time talking to her and remembering
old times
many people told me that I looked like
my mother
in the hotel they had a fancy hall where
they had ballroom dancing
i am not used to that kind of dancing
I always danced to rock music
a man told me that he would teach me how
to dance
it looked very easy i held one of his
hands and put my other hand on his
shoulder
he told me exactly how to move my feet
I was very clumsy and I stepped on his
toes
he was patient with me and he counted
one two three
I tried to waltz with him i would start
out pretty well but then i would get
mixed up and stand on his toes again
the man laughed about it I told him that
I wasn't a very good dancer but he said
that I was good for a beginner
I think he was just being polite
the man asked my mother to dance my
mother is a very good dancer
I didn't know that about her
she never stepped on the man's toes once
the man thanks for Dancing with him and
I thank him for giving me dancing
lessons
I don't think i'll ever be very good at
that type of dancing
each generation has a specific type of
dancing
the way that I dance is different from
the way that my mother dances the way
that I dance doesn't involve moving your
feet too much
I'm not too good at fancy steps
superheroes
when my brother was very young he loved
he could
the plastic figures of all the
superheroes
I think he had every superhero figurine
that there was he used to tie a towel
over his shoulders and run through the
backyard
he pretended that he was rescuing people
one time he stood on the roof he really
thought that he could fly with this
superhero cape on
he would have hurt himself if he had
jumped my dad saw him and told him to
get down my dad explained to my brother
the superheroes are not real real people
cannot fly from rooftops
my brother was disappointed he thought
that the superheroes really existed
my dad explained that most superheroes
were created as comic book characters
somebody used their imagination to make
them up and then an artist through them
my brother was not impressed he said
that he wanted to meet the superheroes
my father told him that he might meet
someone dressed up as a superhero but it
wouldn't really be a superhero in the
classroom
it is hard to explain two small children
that the things that they see in comic
books and on television aren't really
real
my brothers still pretty
he is a superhero he doesn't jump from
rooftops but he runs around and makes
noises like he is flying
I look at him and remember when I used
to do things like that
I'm more mature than my brother I know
that superheroes aren't real but I know
that he is having fun and using his
imagination