first snowfall
today is November 26th
it snowed all day today
the snow is beautiful
the snow finally stopped
my sister and I are excited
my mom doesn't like the snow
my mom has to shovel the driveway
my sister and I get to play
put on my hat and mittens
my mom puts on my scarf
my mom zippers my jacket
my sister puts on her hat and mittens
my mom puts on her scarf
my mom zippers her jacket
my sister and I go outside
we begin to make a snowman
my mom starts to shovel the snow
my sister and I make snow angels
my sister and I throw snowballs
it starts to snow again
we go inside for hot chocolate
Jessica's first day of school
today is Jessica's first day of
kindergarten
jessica and her parents walk to school
Jessica's mom walks with her to her
classroom
Jessica meets her teacher
his name
is mr. Parker
the school bell rings at 8 45 a.m.
Jessica hugs and kisses her mom goodbye
Jessica's mom says I love you
9am
the stands for the national anthem
mr. Parker calls out children's names
each child yells back here
- Parker teaches them about letters
mr. Parker teaches them about numbers
at 10:15 a.m. the students have recess
recess is fun
the students get to play and eat
30 am the students go to gym class
at 11:15 a.m. the students return to mr.
Parker's classroom
mr. Parker tells the students to sit on
the carpet
mr. Parker reads the students a story
- Parker teaches the students a song
the lunch bell rings
Jessica's first day of school is over
my flower garden
my name is an i love flowers
have a flower garden
my garden is in front of my house
my neighbor has a garden -
my garden has different types of flowers
I have roses in my garden I have tulips
in my garden
I have petunias in my garden my garden
has different colors
I plant red flowers I plan orange
flowers
I plant blue flowers I plant purple
I take care of my garden I water my
garden every day
I kill the weeds in my garden I kill
insects that eat my flowers
I love my beautiful garden
going camping
the bright family went camping on the
weekend
bright family went to silent lake
bright family left on Friday
they camped for three days
bright family brought a big tent
they brought a lot of food
brought insect repellent
bright family had a campfire on friday
they roasted marshmallows
they saying campfire songs
on Saturday they went canoeing
on Saturday they went fishing
on Saturday they went swimming
they went hiking on sunday
bright family saw many birds they saw
blue jays they saw hummingbirds
the bright family saw many animals
they saw a raccoon
they saw a squirrel
they didn't see a bear
the bright family had a fun vacation
my house
I live in a house my
house is small
my house has two bedrooms
my mom and dad sleep in one bedroom
my sister and I share the other bedroom
my house has a kitchen
my mom and dad cooked dinner there every
night
my house has a living room
my family watches television there every
night
my house has a big bathroom
my house has a lot of closets
my house has a basement
my dad has a workshop in the basement
my dad makes wood furniture
my house does not have a second floor
my house has a garage
the house has a big backyard
my backyard has a maple tree
my backyard has a swimming pool
my backyard has a vegetable garden
my family likes our house
my first pet
my name is Sarah
14 years old
fat cat
my cat's name is Milo
my cat is black and white
Milo's paws are white
Milo's body is black
she is very cute
Milo's fur is very soft
Milo was a very small kitten
Milo is a very big cat
Milo cannot have kittens
t is fixed
Milo likes to eat
Milo likes to play outside
Milo likes to hunt for birds
Milo likes to hunt for mice
she likes her ears scratched
Milo likes to sit in my laugh
Milo likes to sleep on my bed
Milo is a good pet
Jennifer the firefighter
jennifer smith is a firefighter
she is one of the first female
firefighters
Jennifer works hard every day
Jennifer exercises every day
she lifts weights
she wants her muscles to be very strong
she saves people's lives every day
she is very strong
jennifer is married
her husband is a schoolteacher
Jennifer's husband is proud of her
jennifer is a mother
as two daughters
Jennifer's daughters are proud of her
too
jennifer is happy being a firefighter
jennifer is happy being a wife
jennifer is happy being a mother
Mark's big game
Mark's favorite sport is hockey
he is 15 years old
mark practices three times a week
practices are two hours long
mark plays one game a week
mark is a good hockey player
he plays on Friday nights
friday night hockey games are popular
Mark's family watches him play
marks friends watch him play too
there are always many fans
tonight is the big game
coaches are coming to watch mark play
mark wants to play in the national
hockey league
mark wants to make a lot of money
it is very hard to play in the NHL
Mark's parents want him to go to college
they want him to have an education
they want mark to be successful
they want mark to be happy
the easter egg hunt
samantha is going to an easter egg hunt
Tracy is going to an easter egg hunts
the easter egg hunt is at sydney's house
it is going to be fun
Sydney's mom had chocolate eggs
Sydney's mom had chocolate bunnies
everybody is here
everybody has an Easter basket
the easter egg hunt can start
everybody must close their eyes
one two three go
Samantha finds an easter egg
the easter egg is behind a table
she puts it in her basket
Tracy finds a chocolate Easter Bunny
it's under the couch
Tracy puts it in her basket
Sydney finds a chocolate Easter Bunny
too
it's in front of the television
he puts it in her basket
everybody finds lots of chocolate
everybody shares their chocolate
Samantha Tracy and sydney Love east
stir stir
Joe's first car
Joe is 18
years old
Joe works at McDonald's
Jose saves all his money
Joe has twenty-five hundred dollars in
the bank
he wants to buy a sports car
Joe starts to look for a new car
Joe looks in the newspaper
Joe looks in magazines
go find a car he likes
Joe goes to see the car with his dad
really likes it
Joe doesn't have enough money
Joe's dad tells him to keep saving his
money
joe wants this car a lot
Joe asks his dad to help him
Joe and his dad make a deal
Joe's dad will lend him the money
Joe must work hard
must pay the money back to his dad
Joe is very happy
Joe owns his first car
summer vacation
today is the last day of school
it is summer vacation
grace is very excited
this summer will be fun
grace is going to visit her grandparents
they have a cottage
the cottage is on Lake Erie
it is a lot of fun
grace is going to swim
she is going to play board games
she is going to talk with her
grandparents
grace is going to have fun
grace is going to a summer camp
she will sleep in a cabin
she will make lots of new friends
grace will learn campfire songs
camp will be fun
grace is going to cape cod with her
parents
we are going for two weeks we are going
to drive
grace will see the ocean
cape cod will be beautiful
summer vacation is fun
cleaning up leaves
believes our chain
colors I see red maple leaves
I see orange maple leaves I see yellow
maple leaves
believes are beautiful
it is starting to get cold
the wind is strong
winter is coming
the leaves fall off the trees
on Saturday we will clean them up
the whole family helps
my dad gets the rake
my mom gets the garbage bags
my brother and I helped too
we gather leaves with our hands we make
a big pile
my brother and I jump in the leaves we
make a big mess
our parents don't mind
our parents fill our coats with leaves
we look really big everyone laughs
playtime is over back to work
Susan's wedding day
Susan is getting married
her fiancé's name is Michael
they are in love
they are getting married today
Susan wakes up early
she is getting her hair done
Susan is having her makeup done to Susan
looks beautiful
he puts on her white wedding dress
she puts on her veil
Susan needs something blue
her garter is blue
Susan needs something old her
grandmother's ring is old
Susan need something borrowed
she is wearing her mother's jewelry
Susan needs something new
her shoes and dress are new
Susan needs a penny for her shoe it will
bring her good luck
Susan is ready to get married
remembrance day
my grandfather
World War two
my grandmother was a nurse in World War
two
today is November 11th
today is Remembrance Day
today we celebrate soldiers
everyone wears a poppy
poppies are red flowers
poppies remind me of my grandparents
poppies remind me of their sacrifice
at 11am there are two minutes of silence
people remember their friends and family
people recite the poem in Flanders field
it is a sad poem it helps us remember
a we wish for peace in the world
halloween night
halloween is fun
my mom buys candy
my mom buys potato chips
my mom buys chocolate bars
it is for the trick-or-treaters
my mom buys me a costume
it is a ghost costume
i am going to be scary
my sister is going to dress up as a
princess
she will have a wand
she will have a crown
she will look beautiful
my dad buys a pumpkin
it is going to be a jack-o'-lantern
we draw a face on the pumpkin
we carved the face with a knife
our jack-o'-lantern looks funny
we go trick-or-treating
we knock on the neighbors door
we say trick-or-treat
our neighbors give us candy
we say thanks
we go to many houses we go home
our parents check out our candy
it's safe
we eat lots of candy
we don't feel very good
we go to bed
Christmas Eve
Ben and Melissa are getting ready for
Christmas
then and Melissa's house has lots of
lights on the roof
the lights are many colors
inside they listen to christmas music
Ben and Melissa drink eggnog
eggnog tastes good
Ben and Melissa hang stockings on the
fireplace
they string popcorn
Ben and Melissa put the popcorn string
on the Christmas tree
they put Christmas lights on the tree
they put tinsel on the tree
Ben and Melissa put ornaments on the
tree
they put a star on top of the tree
they get ready for Santa Claus
they leave milk and cookies for Santa
then opens one present
Melissa opens one present
they go to sleep
Ben and Melissa wake up early
they run downstairs
there are a lot of presents under our
tree
they wake up their mom and dad
and and Melissa open their presence
they love our presence
everyone cleans up the wrapping paper
it is time for breakfast
thanksgiving
we are having Thanksgiving at our house
my whole family is coming
my parents bought a turkey
it weighs 30 pounds it takes a long time
to cook
my mom wakes up early to cook the turkey
I clean the house with my dad
the house smells good
we helped mom in the kitchen
I peel potatoes and carrots
my dad makes pumpkin pies my mom cooked
squash
I help my mom makes stuffing
I mix the bread and spices
we make good stuffing
it goes inside the turkey
we put on nice clothes
I set the table my dad carves the turkey
my mom makes the gravy
our relatives arrived
we say thank you for all we have
we eat and eat
it is a good thanksgiving
learning how to drive
amy is 16 years old
she lives in a small town
amy is learning how to drive
Amy's dad is giving her lessons
Amy's dad's name is Howard
he has had three lessons
Amy and her dad argued during the
lessons
Amy's mom is giving her driving lessons
Amy's mom's name is Jane
Jane has given a me a lesson
Jane has decided to stop giving Amy
lessons
Jane and Amy argued during the lessons
too
amy's parents call a driving school
baby is going to get lessons from a
professional
the classes cost three hundred dollars
for ten lessons
the lessons are very good
he learns how to drive
amy gets her license
housework there is always housework to
do when you live in a house you have to
wash the windows so that you can see
outside the floors and the carpet need
to be vacuumed the floors also need to
be washed and some of them need to be
waxed the furniture has to be polished
the bathroom has to be kept clean after
you have a bath you need to clean out
the bathtub laundry needs to be done
regularly or you will run out of clothes
to wear the clothes go into the washing
machine and then they have to be dried
in the dryer
sometimes we hang the clothes out on the
line to be dried some of the clothes
need to be ironed you have to buy
groceries and put them away
meals need to be made you can't let the
dishes pile up in the kitchen
the dishes have to be washed and the
counters need to be wiped the stove
needs to be cleaned and sometimes the
refrigerator and the cupboards need to
be cleaned out
you can dust the furniture and sweep up
the dirt you can make the beds the beds
have to be changed to they need to have
clean sheets put on them
there are just so many things to do
household chores take up a lot of time
working outside today i was working
outside
it was a sunny day and I was very hot
I wore a hat on my head i watered all
the plants
I read it the flower beds I cut back all
of the plants that we're growing too big
I gave some of the plants plant food I
cut the lawn
i rake to lon I filled up the bird bath
with water
I swept the sidewalks and the past i
took out the garbage
I feel the car up with gas
I washed the car I hung out the clothes
on the clothesline
I wash down the lawn furniture
I washed all of the windows on the house
from the outside
I was so tired so I had a glass of
lemonade
I talked to my neighbor and I helped her
trim a tree I planted some bulbs and
then I went into the house
I was exhausted
daily schedule
I wake up every morning at seven o'clock
I take a shower I eat my breakfast I
usually have toast or cereal
I brush my teeth I put on my clothes
I catch the school bus I ride to school
in my class we have math and English
before recess at recess time the girls
skip or walk around and talk
the boys play in the playground or play
baseball after recess
we have physical education and geography
we eat lunch and then we play outside
when the bell rings
we line up to go back into the classroom
after lunch we have history and science
at recess
we play ball again some of the girls
play ball too in the winter we build
snowmen
if it is too cold we stay indoors and
talk to each other after recess
we have music and health we get out of
school at three-thirty I sometimes walk
home with my friends or I take the bus
I have a snack and change my clothes
when i get home if it is raining
i watch television if it is nice outside
i play with my friends I have supper at
five-thirty
I'm some nights I helped my mother to do
the dishes after supper
I do my homework I wash my face and
hands and brush my teeth I change into
my pajamas
i go to bed at nine o'clock
meals breakfast is very rushed at our
house
my brothers and sisters and I have toast
or cereal
we also have orange juice on weekends
my mother makes bacon and eggs for us my
father just has a cup of coffee for
breakfast
my mother packs a lunch for all of us we
usually have a sandwich a piece of fruit
and a drink of juice or milk my favorite
sandwiches are egg salad tuna
roast beef and ham my brother always
wants peanut butter and jam sandwiches
my mother sometimes packs a treat for us
today we had cookies with our lunch at
suppertime the family sits around the
table and talks about what they did all
day
my mother makes good suppers
we sometimes have spaghetti my mother
makes a roast of beef with potatoes and
vegetables quite often
she makes many different dishes out of
chicken
she make soups or stews she also makes
casseroles my brothers and sisters and I
have milk with our dinner
my parents sometimes have wine with
their dinner
sometimes we have salad before our
dinner
I set the table for my mother I put all
the forks the knives and spoons
i also put out glasses and fill them
full of milk or water for dessert we
sometimes have ice cream cake or pie
my mother says that it is better to have
fruit because it is better for you
tonight I ate a peach for dessert
my favorite fruits are apples peaches
plums and bananas
after supper my mother always has a cup
of tea with sugar and cream in it after
dinner I help my mother with the dishes
usually she washes the dishes and i will
dry them
seasons
there are four seasons winter is the
cold season it snows in the winter
the winds blow and ice forms on the
water we play hockey on the ice we play
in the snow after winter is the spring
that is when it begins to get warmer
trees get buds on them flowers start to
bloom it rains a lot in the spring
spring is followed by the summer
it can get very hot in the summertime
the Sun shines brightly we go swimming
in the summer we spent a lot of time
outdoors
many people go on vacations in the
summer we get a summer vacation from
school
summer is followed by the fall or autumn
the leaves on the trees change colors
they change from green to red orange and
brown the leaves fall off the trees the
weather gets cooler the days get shorter
we go back to school in the fall then
winter comes again
the seasons follow one after each other
whether you can watch the weather man on
TV to find out what the weather will be
like it might be a nice clear day with
no clouds in the sky the Sun might be
shining it could be a cloudy day
sometimes cloudy days are just dull on
some cloudy days
it begins to rain or snow some days are
rainy you need a raincoat umbrella and
boots on a rainy day
rain makes the flowers and grass grow
the weather forecast might say that it
will be windy
you could have a gentle breeze
it might be very gusty so that the wind
pushes you
it is dangerous if the wind is very
strong a hurricane or tornado is very
dangerous
once in a while the weatherman says
there will be hail hail stones are hard
cold pallets of ice that fall from the
sky
sometimes the weatherman will say that
there will be snow flurries
sometimes there is just a light dusting
of snow
sometimes there is a blizzard or a
snowstorm
it can be dangerous driving through a
blizzard
if there is a lot of snow the streets
have to be plowed
you need a hat coat mittens and boots on
a very cold day sometimes the weather
forecast is wrong
the weatherman might say that it will be
a sunny day but then the clouds come in
and it rains
that is not good if you are planning a
picnic
I prefer sunny days that are warm but
not too hot
I like to feel a gentle breeze to cool
me down
house a house is divided into different
rooms in my house
there is a living room there is a couch
two chairs a coffee table and a
television set in the living room in the
kitchen
there is a stove and a refrigerator
there is also a sink and a dishwasher in
the kitchen
there is a kitchen table and chairs we
most of our meals at the kitchen table
we have a dining room there is a dining
table and chairs in there
there's a washroom or bathroom
there is a toilet sink and bathtub in
the bathroom
there is also a shower in the bathroom
we have three bedrooms the bedrooms are
upstairs
my brother's room my room and my parents
room all have beds in them
we also have dressers in our rooms there
are closet in all of the bedrooms
we keep our clothes in the closets there
is a basement in our house we store
things in the basement
there is a laundry room in the basement
there is a washing machine and a dryer
in the laundry room
this is where we wash and dry our
clothes
there is a garage attached to the house
we keep the car in the garage
you drive up the driveway and into the
garage
we also have a front yard and a backyard
there is a vegetable garden in the
backyard
there are some flowers and a tree
planted in the front yard
school there are different types of
schools there is an elementary school
the children at the elementary school
are young
there is a playground for them to play
in the classrooms are bright and airy
there are black boards in the classrooms
the children sit in deaths to do their
work
there is a parking lot for the teachers
to park in there is a cafeteria for the
students to get food
the principal has an office nobody wants
to go to the principal's office
it usually means that you are in trouble
if you have to go to the principal's
office
when you finish elementary school you go
to high school
most of the students in high school are
teenagers
there is a parking lot outside the high
school
there's also a football field outside
the students go to classes in different
classrooms they move from classroom to
classroom for each subject
there is a cafeteria where they can get
their lunches or eat the lunches that
they have brought from home
there is a gymnasium where students have
physical education dances are also held
in the gymnasium
some students go on to University from
high school students at the University
are older
some of the students are even senior
citizens
people come from all over the world to
attend the University
there are lots of different things at
the University
there's a theater where plays and
concerts are held there is a bookstore
where students can buy their textbooks
there's a physical education building
that has a swimming pool in it
the parking lot at the university is
very big
they call the land that the university
is on a campus
some of the students live on campus in
residence
subjects
there are many subjects that you can
take at school my favorite subject is
music I like to sing and to play the
clarinet
i also like art I am quite good at
drawing and painting
history is a good subject
I like learning about the past geography
is very interesting
we look at many maps in geography we
learn where there are deserts and
mountains
I know the names of all the continents
in all the oceans
mathematics is my least favorite subject
I'm not very good with numbers i am good
at addition and subtraction but i'm not
good at division and multiplication in
my school we learn to speak French
we learn french because Canada has
french and english speaking citizens
English literature is a good subject
i enjoy reading books i also like to
write compositions and poetry
science is my brother's favorite subject
he is interested in plants and he likes
to do experiment we also take drama at
my school
I like to act I got the lead role in the
school play
international students we have many
international students at my school
some of the students come from England
they speak english but they have an
accent that is different from a Canadian
accent
many students are from Japan they are
learning our language and our customs
we have students from Germany Italy
China Korea and Iran we try to make
those students feel welcome here
the students like to see what is here
they go sightseeing
they visit all the places that the two
words like to go to niagara falls and
toronto are interesting places to visit
the students practice their english by
talking to Canadians when they first get
here we show them around
they do many exercises to learn the
language they listen to english songs
they read story books that are written
in English they listen to english
language tapes
the best way to learn the language is to
talk to other people
it is good to ask questions in English
Canadians try to be helpful to
international students some of the
international students live with host
families the host families had the
students living in their homes
it is a good way for the host families
and the students to make friends
many of the international students stay
in contact with their friends and host
families even after they have gone back
to their homelands the international
students learn a lot from their host
families because they eat Canadian foods
and they learn what it is like to live
in a Canadian household
interests and hobbies it is very
rewarding to have different interests
and hobbies
some people like to play computer games
other people spend a lot of time
watching television
there are people who would rather watch
movies
some people prefer more physical things
they would rather play a sport like
baseball hockey or basketball
some people do exercises at a gym or
they just go for walks
there are many ways to exercise they can
ride a bicycle or lift weights
there are people who like to collect
things they can collect all kinds of
different things you can collect stamps
coins dolls
postcards movies rocks or posters
some people even collect bugs or leaves
some people are lucky enough to be able
to travel you can travel to a nearby
place or you can travel far away to a
different country there are people who
like to listen to music
people have different tastes in music
some people like rock music rap
classical music or folk music there are
many different types of music
some people would rather play music and
listen to it you can play an instrument
or you can sing many people learn to
play the guitar or the piano
some people join bands or orchestras
there are people who like to read books
there are a lot of different hobbies it
depends on what you consider to be fun
you can have more than one hobby or
interest
it is good to be interested in a lot of
different things
movies I go to the movies almost every
week sometimes I rent movies from the
video store my favorite films are action
films
I like to watch car chases
I like it when the bad guy has a
shootout with the good guys
I like the good guys to win i also like
science fiction movies
I like things that take place in the
future I like movies that have aliens
from different planets in them some of
the science fiction movies can be silly
and unbelievable
I don't like those ones my mother likes
dramas
she has a lot of favorite actors and
actresses
she sometimes watches sad movies that
make her cry
she also likes comedies
she laughed out loud if a comedy is very
funny
my father likes horror movies
he likes movies with monsters in them
he also likes thrillers I have
which to some thrillers that keep you
tense and on the edge of your seat
sometimes I have to shut my eyes
if the movie gets too scary my brother
likes animated films in animated films
there are no actors just cartoon
characters
my brother goes to the movies on
Saturday afternoons with his friends he
goes to the matinee
he gets popcorn candy and pop he usually
comes back with a stomach ache because
he eats so much
sometimes my father watches
documentaries documentaries are about
real things you can learn a lot from
watching a documentary
i watch documentaries with him sometimes
but i would rather see a good action
film
flowers
there are hundreds of different types of
most people like roses roses grow on
bushes and they smell beautiful
you have to be careful that you don't
prick your finger on a rose thorn roses
come in many colors
there are red pink yellow and white
roses in the spring tulips are in bloom
in Ottawa
there are many tulips some people go
there just to see all the tulips in the
spring
forget-me-nots are also spring flowers
they are tiny and blue
lilies-of-the-valley look like white
bells where I live
many of the trees have blossoms on them
in the springtime the apple and cherry
trees look particularly beautiful when
they are in blossom
we have a blossom festival in my town my
neighbors like to plant geraniums
petunias and marigolds in the summer
some people plant sunflowers sunflowers
grow very tall
they have bright yellow petals all of
those flowers grow best in the sunshine
if your garden is shady you have to
plant different things
hostas grow well in a shady garden
chrysanthemums our fall flowers
chrysanthemums come in many colors also
there are purple yellow and white
chrysanthemums flowers are good to give
as gifts
women like to receive a dozen roses on
Valentine's Day
carnations also make a nice gift they
have a very sweet smell
many people give away lilies for easter
. set us are very festive at
Christmastime
if someone goes to a dance they often
give their partner a flower to wear
sometimes a girl will get an orchid from
her date
if you go to a wedding you will probably
see a lot of flowers they're flowers
help to make place is beautiful
the shopping mall
there are many different stores in the
shopping mall there are ladies wear
stores they sell dresses blouses and
many kinds of clothes for women in the
men's wear stores there are suits ties
shirts and slacks
there are also clothing stores that
appeal just two teenagers some clothing
stores only sell children's clothes
there is even a store that sells bathing
suits and cover-ups for the beach or
pool
there are lingerie stores that sell
ladies underwear and nightwear there are
hardware stores that sell tools there
are shoe stores you buy shoes and boots
in a shoe store
there are bookstores you can buy a book
on almost any topic at the bookstore
there are stores that sell compact discs
those stores also have tapes and videos
there are sports stores that sell
special shoes and clothes for sports
they also sell sports equipment and
t-shirts and hats with the logo of your
favorite teams there are gift stores
that sell all kinds of things that
someone might want for their house
there are kitchen stores where you can
buy utensils and pots and pans those
kinds of stores also sell aprons and
napkins and anything you might need for
your kitchen
there is a movie theater at the mall
there is a jewelry store that has a lot
of gold and silver jewelry
there is a hairdresser in the mall
sometimes I go in there to get my hair
cut
there are fast food places in the mall
you can get a quick lunch like a
hamburger or some french fries
there are also fancy restaurants in the
mall
you can sit down for a nice meal
there is a furniture store in the mall
you can buy a new sofa or bed at the
furniture store
there are bulk food stores at a bulk
foods store all the foods are in bins
you take as much as you want and pay for
it at the counter
there is even a telephone store and an
electronics store at the mall
my brother's favorite store is the toy
store
he could spend hours in there
there are also department stores at the
mall department stores sell all kinds of
things
they sell perfume clothes shoes kitchen
utensils or just about anything you
might need
you can get almost anything you want at
the shopping mall
travel
it is fun to take a trip to a farm
our way place my brother just went to
italy and france he got on a plane at
toronto airport
he took a flight to France
he stayed there for a couple of days
he visited the Eiffel Tower
he was in Paris he said that he enjoyed
the food in France
he then traveled to Italy
he saw many towns and villages in Italy
he went to Rome and visited many of the
tourist attractions in Venice
he saw the canals he tried to speak
Italian
but he is not too good at it
he said that the people were very
helpful
they tried to understand him he bought
souvenirs for us when he was in Italy
he ate Italian food he said that pizza
in Italy is quite different from the
pizza we eat here in canada he saw many
streets that were made of cobblestones
he saw many old buildings
a lot of people in Italy travel around
on scooters
he stayed at a very nice hotel in Italy
he was sorry when it was time to come
home
my brother likes to travel
he likes to fly in airplanes
the airlines lost his luggage once he
was not too pleased about that next year
he would like to travel to England
the farm
my uncle is a farmer he lives on a farm
he has many different types of animals
in the barn
there are horses and cows to cows switch
the flies away from themselves with
their tails
it sounds very loud if a cow says Moo
when you are standing there the cows eat
the grass from my uncle's field he gets
milk from the cows
I put a saddle on one of the horses and
went for a ride there are pigs in the
pig pen
he has goats he says that the goats will
eat just about anything he has a chicken
coop with chickens in it
the chickens lay eggs
have you ever seen baby chicks
they are very cute
my uncle collect the eggs every morning
there is a rooster to the rooster crows
when the Sun comes up
my uncle also has a goose goose makes
honking noise
I don't think that the goose likes me
it nips me when I go near it many cats
live in my uncle's barn
they are stray cats but he lets them
stay there because they keep the mice
away my uncle feeds the cats
my uncle says that he would like to get
some sheep for his farm
you can get wool from sheep
there are a lot of animals on my uncle's
farm
transportation
every family that I know has at least
one car
some families have two or even three
cars
most people get their license to drive
when they are 16 in my house
we just have one car if my father takes
the car to work
my mother will take the bus I ride in a
school bus to school
my sister works in another town
she gets on the train to go to work
the train station is not far from my
house the train tracks run right by my
house my grandfather from Ireland comes
to visit us
he came over by boat
he had to cross the ocean we went to
Florida last year we flew on a plane
the plane flew right through the clouds
my friend's brother drives a motorcycle
he wears a helmet
I wrote on his motorcycle once i had to
sit on the back and hold on tight
I ride my bicycle when the weather is
nice
i also have a scooter that I used to
travel around
I took a helicopter ride once
the helicopters propellers were going
around when I got on
I went straight up in the air I enjoyed
the ride
I would like to learn how to fly a plane
or a helicopter
I like flying through the air
holidays in canada we have many
different days that we celebrate on the
first day of January there is New Year's
Day
that is when we ring in the New Year and
say goodbye to the old year in February
there is Valentine's Day
that is the day when you tell your
girlfriend or boyfriend that you love
them you can buy them flowers or candy
or take them out to dinner in March
there is st. Patrick's Day everyone
pretends that they are Irish on st.
Patrick's Day
they all wear green
Easter comes in the spring easter is a
religious holiday
some people celebrate by going to church
some people think that the Easter Bunny
comes and leaves chocolate eggs for them
in May
there is victoria day we celebrate this
day in honor of England's Queen Victoria
there are fireworks on Victoria Day
july the first is canada day in
September
there is labor day this is the day that
we honor the working man or woman in
October there is thanksgiving
we give thanks for all the things that
we are fortunate enough to have we
usually have a turkey dinner on
thanksgiving day on the last day of
october there is Halloween the children
dress up in costumes and go from door to
door collecting candies Remembrance Day
is in November people wear red poppies
and they remember all the people that
died for their country christmas comes
in december
christmas is also a religious holiday
but many children believe that Santa
Claus arrives on Christmas Eve in a
sleigh pulled by reindeer
they believe that Santa Claus fills up
their stockings with toys and goodies
he gets in and out of people's houses
through their chimneys
we don't get off work or school for all
these days but many of them are holidays
from work and school
diseases there are many diseases some
diseases are very deadly and some are
not so serious
most people catch a cold sometimes a
cold makes you cough and sneeze cold can
be passed on from person to person
some people get the flu with the flu
you get chills and a fever a fever is a
high temperature if you have the flu
you will feel very bad you have to stay
home in bed
there are diseases that children get the
mumps make you have lumps in your neck
chicken pox and measles leave you with
red itchy dots on your skin
older people sometimes get arthritis
their bones get stiff and sore
there are people who get heart disease
in many cases a healthy lifestyle can
prevent heart disease cancer can attack
different parts of the body
many smokers get lung cancer
some diseases are treated with pills or
medicine other diseases need to be
treated in the hospital
sometimes doctors need to give you test
to find out what kind of disease you
have the doctor might have to do a blood
test or an x-ray to find out what is
wrong with you
most diseases can be cured by a doctor
jobs there are many different jobs that
you can choose from you can be a doctor
or a nurse
you could work in a hospital or doctor's
office
you might be a firefighter and put out
fires a policeman enforces the law an
actor plays rolls on stage or in the
movies
you could drive a taxi or be the pilot
of an airplane
what kinds of things do you like to do
you might want to be a sales clerk in a
store
maybe you are good at a sport you could
be a baseball player or a hockey player
being a dentist is a good job
I dentist fixes teeth
if you were good at arguing
you might want to be a lawyer do you
like to fix people's hair you could be a
hairdresser or a barber
if you are good with your hands you
might want to be a carpenter or a
mechanic
if you like to travel
you could be a stewardess or a travel
agent you could be a teacher or a
photographer
are you artistic or creative
you might want to be an artist or a
writer
you could work on construction and build
houses
you could
after animals and be a veterinarian if
you like to cook
you could be a cook or chef there are so
many places to work and so many jobs to
do
maybe you could fix computers or work in
a library
you could wash windows or be the captain
of a ship there is no limit to what you
can be
my body
on the top of my head i have hair below
my hair is my face
I have two eyes
I have eyebrows and eyelashes below my
eyes I have a nose
my mouth is below my nose
I have lips if i open my lips
you will see my teeth and my tongue
below my mouth is my chin on the sides
of my head i have two ears
my cheeks are on either side of my nose
my neck
holds up my head my neck attaches my
head to my chest on either side of my
chest or my shoulders my arms hang down
from my shoulders
I have risks on my arms my hands are
attached to my wrist
my fingers are part of my hands
I have ten fingers and ten fingernails
my back is at the back of me
further down there is my waist if I wear
a belt I put it on my waist
my hips are below my waist my legs come
down from my hips my legs are made up of
my thighs my knees and my cads my knees
can bend my ankles are below my legs my
feet are attached to my ankles
my toes are part of my feet
I have ten toes and 10 toenails
I am me from the top of my head to the
tips of my toes
clothing
I change my clothes a lot if I am going
somewhere fancy i wear a dress I wear
stockings on my legs and I wear a pair
of nice shoes
if I am going to play sports I wear a
sweatshirt and jeans
if I am going to the beach
I wear a bathing suit or a bikini my
brother we're swimming trunks to the
beach at work
I wear a skirt and a blouse underneath
my clothes I wear underwear
a lady wears a bra and panties as
underwear
a man wears boxer or jockey shorts as
underwear today i am wearing a blouse
and a pair of jeans over my underwear
I have socks and shoes on my feet in the
summer
I often wear sandals on my feet in the
summer the tops that I where are usually
sleepless i usually wear shorts in the
summer
sometimes I wear sweater or a jacket if
the weather is cool
I wear a cap or a hat on my head
I wear a belt to hold up my jeans or my
slacks
women sometimes wear a dress or a skirt
men wear a pair of slacks and a shirt
some men wear a suit and a shirt and tie
if it is very cold outside I wear winter
coat if it is cold
I like to wear gloves or mittens on my
hands sometimes I wrap a scarf around my
neck to keep warm
I wear to con my head in cold weather I
wear boots on my feet in the winter
if it is raining I wear a raincoat the
way that I dress depends a lot on the
weather