oxford bookworms stage 1 mutiny on the
bounty by Tim Vickery read by Gareth
Armstrong published and copyright Oxford
University Press 2007 chapter one from
England to Tahiti it was a cold day in
December 1787 there was a strong wind
and a green sea three men and a boy
stood on the deck of the little ship HMS
Bounty behind them on the land were some
hills and small white houses the ship
moved slowly out to see the boy Peter
Hayward was 14 years old he was a young
officer and he was happy and excited
England looks very small mr. Christian
he said Fletcher Christian smiled at him
Christian was a tall young man with
black hair and a long tired face England
is small he said but we&#39;re going to some
much smaller islands Tahiti the friendly
Islands they&#39;re small but they&#39;re very
warm and beautiful a sailor John Adams
laughed that&#39;s right mr. Christian sir
he said good food warm Sun blue skies
and hot beautiful women too I won&#39;t be
quiet man someone shouted Christian and
Hayward looked behind them they saw the
captain william bligh he was a small man
with brown hair Christian new Bligh well
they were friends but Bligh was a
captain now so things were different the
bounty was his first ship and it was
very important to him don&#39;t talk about
women on my ship Adams he said angrily
be quiet and sail this ship are you here
yes sir said Adams quietly now listen to
me mr. Christian and you too mr. Heywood
Bligh stood very near them but he didn&#39;t
speak quietly all the sailors could hear
him I&#39;m the captain of this ship
remember that we&#39;re going 30,000
kilometers through bad weather and very
bad seas and I don&#39;t want any accidents
you are officers so you don&#39;t talk to
sailors about women or drink or anything
you must work hard and your sailors must
work hard to do you understand me mr.
Christian yes sir said Christian but he
didn&#39;t look happy good and you mr.
Hayward yes sir the boy looked at Bly
afraid then bly smiled
is this your first time at sea boy yes
sir well you must work hard and listen
to me one day perhaps you can be a
captain too would you like that yes sir
of course Peter Hayward smiled right
then mr. Christian look at those men
there they aren&#39;t working run and talk
to them quickly ly smiled again at
hayward in a happy ship the men must
work hard but the officers must work
harder do you understand boy the bounty
sailed south across the Atlantic for 10
days they were in a storm near Cape Horn
but they could not sail west because of
the strong west wind so they sailed east
to South Africa Tasmania and Tahiti
there were 33 sailors on the bounty and
11 officers Bligh was the captain
Christian was his second officer the
ship was often wet and cold but no one
was ill once Bligh gave the sailors some
apples but they would not eat them
because they were old and bad Bligh was
very angry damn you men he shouted
apples are good for you you eat them I
say on the twenty-sixth of October 1788
the bounty arrived at tahiti the
islanders came to the ship in big canoes
with food the king of Tahiti or two was
friendly bly went to Otto&#39;s house and
gave him things from the King of England
Thank You captain OTT who said you are
welcome here I must give the King of
England something too but he&#39;s a rich
man what would he like do you know fly
smiled it was an important question my
king is very rich auto he said but we
don&#39;t have any bread fruit trees in
England my king would like some for his
people in Jamaica can I take some on my
ship or two laughed of course he said
that&#39;s easy take lots of them my people
can help you the bounty stayed at Tahiti
for five months and by March there were
a thousand breadfruit trees on the ship
Tahitian children played on the ship and
in the evenings the sailors danced and
sang with the women one morning some
sailors and Tahitian women took a ship&#39;s
boat to a different Island lie was very
angry when the sailors came back he put
chains on their legs
then he shouted at his officers and men
your men must stay away from these women
he said you must all listen to me and
work hard for me and the King some
officers kept pigs on the ship sometimes
Bligh took the pigs from his officers
I&#39;m giving this food to the sailors he
said they need it not you April the
fourth was the Bounty&#39;s last day in
Tahiti the ship was full of food and
people are too and his family all the
sailors and they&#39;re tahitian friends but
nobody sang or danced everyone was quiet
and sad Peter haywood sword john adams
with a Tahitian woman she cried and he
talked to her for the last time then she
got into a canoe and went back to the
island Peter stood near him sadly the
Sun went down in the West mr. Christian
shouted Captain Bligh are all the
Tahitians off the ship yes sir Christian
answered good then we sail for Jamaica
and then back to Old England he looked
at Peter don&#39;t stand there boy get to
work look at all our beautiful
breadfruit trees King George is going to
be very happy about them
chapter 2 mutiny on the evening of the
26th of April Adams saw Bligh on deck he
looked angry and stopped near Fletcher
Christian mr. Christian Bligh said where
am I coconuts I had 50 yesterday and
there are only 20 here now where are
they do you know no sir Christian said I
don&#39;t know I never saw them I didn&#39;t
take them you know that Captain Bligh
looked at his tall young officer and
said nothing lie and Christian were once
friends Adams remembered but not now
Bligh was often angry Christian was
always worried afraid bly said mr.
Christian you took my coconuts I know
you did you&#39;re my second officer but all
you officers take my things god damn you
all at four o&#39;clock that morning Adams
saw Christian again it was a quiet night
and the ship moved slowly through the
water Christian had a piece of wood with
him and a bag his face was white in the
moonlight a young officer George Stewart
talk to Christian what are you doing
to christian Stewart asked I&#39;m in hell
christian said Bligh doesn&#39;t like me or
any of his officers I must leave the
ship leave what are you talking about
how I have some food in this bag and
wood and I can swim christian said we&#39;re
not far from the island of Taufua
perhaps I can swim there swim to 24 of
course you can&#39;t man do you want to die
it doesn&#39;t matter I can&#39;t stay here with
that man I&#39;m in hell I tell you every
day he shouts at me and it takes a year
to sail to England I must leave the ship
I understand Stewart said many of us are
afraid of Bly we don&#39;t like him but you
must stay you&#39;re our best officer listen
to me now Bligh was in bed when the door
opened Christian came in with three
sailors it was still dark bly opened his
eyes in the moonlight he saw the gun in
Christians hand what bly SAT up get out
damn you this is my hold him christian
said the sailors put Bligh&#39;s arms behind
his back and christian tied them with a
rope now sir come with us they took
Bligh out of his bed and up onto the
deck he wore a shirt but no trousers or
shoes there were ten or twelve men bear
with guns and small swords Christian
held Bligh&#39;s hands with the rope and
Adams stood behind Bly with a gun what
are you doing ly said angrily let me go
at once your be quiet adam said listen
to mr. Christian but I&#39;m not captain not
now this is our ship now christian said
Adams put the launch in the water the
launch was a small boat 7 meters long
Adams put it in the water next to the
ship right christian said thank you
Adams you stay with me Christian looked
at some other sailors he didn&#39;t like
them you men he said get into that boat
quickly now no fly shouted all of you
stay on this ship help me now he began
to run but Christian held the rope and
Adams held a knife to his neck do that
again Captain Bligh and you&#39;re a dead
man he said quietly at the front of the
ship Peter Heywood came up on deck
what&#39;s happening he asked he was afraid
be quiet Peter Christian said you stay
there get into the lawn shoe men he
shouted I told you slowly 18 sailors got
into the launch then Christian took
Bligh to the side of the ship now you
captain he said
over the side two men carried Bly over
the side of the ship then the sailors
through some bread into the launch with
a barrel of water a little meat bottles
of rum and wine some rope and sales and
some of the captain&#39;s books you see we
aren&#39;t going to kill you christian said
you can live on that for a week or two
but why are you doing this Christian fly
shouted angrily I&#39;m your captain and
your friend no you&#39;re not not now
christian said don&#39;t you understand I&#39;m
in hell with you here on this ship
you&#39;re going to be in Hell all your life
now christian because of this fly said
fly sat in the launch with 18 men
christian and the sailors watched him
from the back of the ship then they
opened a bottle of rum and laughed
england is that way Captain Bligh one of
the sailors said 30,000 kilometers to
the north forget England my friend adam
said I&#39;m thinking about Tahiti and those
beautiful women we&#39;re going to be happy
now on Tahiti with mr. Christian
Christian looked at Adams for a minute
but he didn&#39;t smile his face in the
early morning sun was white and cold
then he looked at the launch far away
across the sea with 19 men in it Tahiti
England or the bounty it doesn&#39;t matter
John he said I&#39;m going to live and die
in hell
chapter 3 in the launch the launch was
seven meters long and there were 19 men
in it Captain Bligh sat at the back of
the launch and looked at his men the
sides of the launch were only 30
centimeters above the sea mr. Hall look
at our food please bly said yes sir bly
looked away over the sea the bounty was
very far away now but there was a small
island tough were about 20 kilometres to
the west after some minutes mr. Hall a
young officer said sir we have 150 kilos
of bread two kilos of meat six bottles
of rum and 126 liters of water sir is
that all Bly asked we have a small sail
and some coats sir all said that&#39;s all
Thank You mr. Hall ly said it&#39;s not much
but we&#39;re going to tafawa so perhaps we
can find some more food and water there
Bly was afraid but he didn&#39;t want them
to see that the men were quiet they
didn&#39;t look angry next day they landed
at 24 they found
bread fruit bananas and coconuts but no
water a lot of Islanders came down to
the sea where is your ship they asked
eight sank Bligh said all our friends
are dead we need food and water the
Islanders laughed it was not a friendly
laughs they talked quietly more men came
soon there were nearly a hundred they
began to pick up stones get back into
the boat Bly said quickly now but the
Islanders killed one man with stones
when the launch went out to see the
Islanders came after it in their canoes
they threw stones at the sailors throw
the coats into the sea Bly said quick
the island has stopped and picked the
coats out of the sea then the canoes
went back to 24 we can&#39;t land on any
islands then lie said not without a big
ship and guns he looked at his men they
were quiet and afraid we must be very
careful with our food he said every man
can have a small piece of bread and
coconut today and a cup of water that&#39;s
all when it&#39;s cold we can have some rum
but don&#39;t worry remember I&#39;m your
captain listen to me and we can stay
alive yes sir then the youngest a boy
called Robert Tinkler said
I want to go home bly looked at him and
for a minute the boy was afraid because
Bligh was often angry then he saw a
small cold smile on Bligh&#39;s face to
England Robert yes sir well that&#39;s about
30,000 kilometers away so first let&#39;s
find Timor that&#39;s much nearer there are
Dutch ships there they can take us home
yes sir the boy looked happier how far
is it to Timor sir for a minute bly
didn&#39;t answer he looked away over the
cold green sea the wind was stronger now
and the sky was dark oh not far he said
slowly only about seven thousand
kilometres next morning the wind got
stronger and stronger and the launch
went up and down over Big Green Wave&#39;s
everyone was wet and white water came
into the launch the sailors used the
empty coconuts to throw the water back
into the sea at midday they ate five
small coconuts and drank some rum and
they ate some wet bread fruit in the
evening the wind and waves were strong
all night so no one could sleep next day
the bread was wet but they didn&#39;t throw
it away in the afternoon it rained and
they caught the water in
cups and coconuts but it rained all
night so everyone was cold and wet the
launch was small so they could not all
sleep most men SAT up all night on the
8th of May it was sunny the men took off
their wet shirts and trousers bly gave
them some rum coconut milk and 80 grams
of bread often he talked about New
Guinea Australia and team or there were
storms for the next two weeks sometimes
they saw the Sun for an hour but every
day it rained big green waves through
white water into the launch they were
always wet tired and hungry three times
they saw islands but they didn&#39;t go near
them they ate bad bread and old meat but
they had lots of rain water to drink
when they were very wet bly gave his men
some rum no one could sleep for more
than one or two hours but every hour bly
held a long rope over the side the rope
had not seen it the men watched
carefully the knots went behind the
launch and Bly looked at his watch we&#39;re
going quickly today bly told them and
wrote in a little book we&#39;re going about
160 kilometers every day he told his men
but we can&#39;t always sail
West because of the wind so I&#39;m sorry
but today we can only have 40 grams of
bread bad bread too said one man Purcell
yes but it keeps us alive ly answered
angrily then he laughed look up there he
said there was a bird on the front of
the launch its small yellow I looked at
them carefully two sailors opened their
hands very slowly the bird didn&#39;t move
one man put his hand on it the bird
moved away but at the same time his
friend caught the birds feet and killed
it the sailors laughed and shouted it
was only a very small black and white
bird but it was fooled good food I
caught it the first sailor said now you
didn&#39;t the other man said I did be quiet
bly said give it to me he cut the bird
with his knife and caught its red blood
in a cup the men drank the blood then
bly cut the bird into 18 pieces and put
them in front of him right he said friar
sit here with your back to the bird now
I have one piece of the bird in my hand
he held up a piece of its leg tell me
friar who shall have this leadwood friar
said all right
bly gave the piece tool Edward and
picked up a second piece and who shall
have this all all right no one was angry
because fryer couldn&#39;t see the pieces
everyone watched Bligh picked up the
bird&#39;s head and feet who shall have this
he asked why fryer answered everyone
laughed and Bly looked at the head and
feet sadly oh well he said I know it&#39;s
good for me slowly he began to eat them
that evening they caught a bigger bird
and ate that too next day they caught
one more everyone was happy why are all
these birds here the boy Robert asked
Bligh smiled because we are near land he
said on the twenty-eighth of May at
midnight they saw white water in front
of them the barrier reef Bly said a line
of rocks under water we must be careful
ships often sync here take down the sail
and move slowly we must find a way
through they sailed slowly near the
white angry water then after four hours
they found a way through behind the
barrier reef the sea was blue and quiet
they sailed quietly to a small island
they could sleep on the island and walk
about
they began to look stronger but they
were 2,000 kilometers from team or so
they could not stay long after six days
they went to see again west towards team
or the Sun was very hot and two men were
ill fly gave them some rum and the blood
of birds but they can&#39;t live much longer
in a little boat like this he thought
we&#39;re all tired and hungry someone is
going to die soon but it was not far now
every hour bly held the rope over the
side and wrote in his little book he
watched the Sun and the sea and the sky
and then on the 11th of June bly said
you cannot see it but south of us
there&#39;s a big island called team or they
laughed and smiled and sang next day
they saw the island green trees and
hills two days later they came to a town
called Khao pang there were some Dutch
sailors by the sea bly and his men
walked up to them who are you a Dutch
officer asked you look hungry and ill
where are you from I&#39;m Captain William
Bligh of the English ship HMS Bounty
these men are English sailors we left to
for 41 days ago kathua the Dutch
hast where is that it is a small island
about 7,000 kilometers away we came in
that small launch my god 41 days in that
the Dutchman looked at the launch and
for a minute he said nothing then he
asked did many of you die bly smiled oh
no only one and the island as on 24
killed him 17 men left her for with me
and 17 men are here now alive
chapter 4 the pandora on the fourteenth
of March 1790 Bligh and his men arrived
in England when he told the story of the
mutiny English people were very angry
they sent captain Edwards in the Pandora
to Tahiti on the twenty-third of March
1791 the Pandora arrived in Tahiti
captain Edwards and his men looked
carefully at the island they could see a
lot of trees and small houses but no
English ship then a small canoe came out
to the Pandora the three men in the
canoe shouted and smiled I think they&#39;re
English men sir a sailor said all right
captain edward said they can come on the
ship perhaps they can tell us something
the three men were brown and strong but
they wore English sailors hats and
trousers one of them a boy about 18
years old smiled at Edwards good morning
sir my name is Peter Hayward I am a
young officer from the bounty this is
mr. Stewart and Joseph Coleman a sailor
yes I see said Edwards three of you
where are your friends where is mr.
Christian and the bounty
haywood looked worried mr. Christian he
sailed away in the bounty sir a year ago
I think but we didn&#39;t go with them we
waited for you we aren&#39;t afraid I see
Edward said he looked at them carefully
all right then tell me your story what
happened after Christian put Captain
Bligh in the launch well sir Heyward
said we threw the breadfruit trees into
the sea and sailed here to Tahiti or to
the king of Tahiti was good to us and a
lot of men wanted to stay here but mr.
Christian was afraid we can&#39;t stay here
he said because a ship is going to come
from England so Otto gave us a lot of
pigs and goats and food and we sailed to
a different Island to buy some Islanders
from Tahiti came with us eight men nine
women and seven boys but the people of
tube oh I didn&#39;t like us and some of us
didn&#39;t like mr. Christian so mr.
Christian sailed the bounty back to
Tahiti and left 16 of us here and then
captain Edwards was excited what did mr.
Christian do he asked he sailed away in
the bounty sir I see and how many men
went with him nine sailors I think sir
but they took seven Tahitian men and 12
women too
I see Edward said he looked at them
angrily 16 men stayed on Tahiti and
three of you are here so where are the
other 13 are they waiting for me to on
the island ah well yes sir I mean Peter
Heywood stopped he was worried and
afraid they were here but they aren&#39;t
here now said George Stewart quickly he
put his hand on Peter Heywood&#39;s arm they
sailed away too oh did they captain
Edwards asked when Hayward and Stewart
both spoke at once for days two weeks
ago sir they said then they stopped
Edwards watched them I see he said
slowly first you are in a mutiny and now
you tell me things that are not true
sailor yes sir one of the Pandora
sailors answered put these three men in
Chains they are prisoners but Sir Peter
Heyward said we didn&#39;t run away we came
to tell you our story and mr. Stewart
has a wife a wife captain Edwards
laughed his shit home in England no sir
here mr. Stewart answered she&#39;s a
Tahitian woman her name is Peggy mrs.
Peggy Stewart and we have a daughter
Edwards laughed again a Tahitian woman
I&#39;m sorry for her but
worried she can come on the ship and see
you in your new prison look behind you
we have a wonderful prison for you and
your friends look the three sailors
looked behind them on the deck of the
Pandora was a wooden box about two
meters high and four meters long it had
a small door but no windows the Pandora
sailors put the prisoners in the box
with chains on their arms and legs
captain Edwards laughed there are you
happy now you can stay there all the way
to England but my wife my little
daughter Stewart said the door closed in
his face we didn&#39;t put Bligh in the
launch Christian did we came to tell you
everything Edwards laughed and Peter
Heyward said nothing captain Edwards
caught 11 more men and put them in the
Pandora&#39;s box too they&#39;re tahitian wives
and children came on to the Pandora and
cried but captain Edwards didn&#39;t open
the door for three months the Pandora
sailed to different islands and the
prisoners stayed in the box but Edwards
couldn&#39;t find Christian or the bounty
and so he began to sail home
near Australia the Pandora hits the
barrier reef water came into the ship
and the sailors couldn&#39;t stop it after
12 hours captain Edwards said we must
leave the ship get into the boats men
the prisoners could hear the noise
outside and water came in through the
door captain Edwards took three
prisoners out but then he closed the
door what about us Peter Heywood shouted
please captain open the door why are you
leaving us in here be quiet boy said
captain Edwards we&#39;re working hard now
the ship is sinking but we&#39;re going to
die we can&#39;t move George Stewart shouted
open the door but Edwards closed the
door and no one helped them outside the
first sailors got into the boats and
rode away inside the box the prisoners
hit the walls and shouted but they
couldn&#39;t move because of the chains
after an hour a sailor opened the door
and helped them out of their chains but
there was very little time all of them
got their legs free but some couldn&#39;t
get their arms free Peter Hayward was
nearly the last man to get out in the
sea he held on to some wood he saw
George Stewart and four other prisoners
they couldn&#39;t swim because of the chains
on their arms help me Peter Stewart
called but the sea took Stewart away
Peter hey would never saw his friend
again Peter Heywood landed on a small
island with some prisoners captain
Edwards and the Pandora&#39;s sailors they
had four boats but only one small barrel
of water and some bread like Captain
Bligh they sailed to the Dutch Island of
Timor then a Dutch ship took them to
England they arrived on the 19th of June
1792 Peter Heywood looked across the
water at the green hills and small
houses home he said quietly to a Dutch
sailor England is very beautiful you
know I left here five years ago are you
going to see your family the Dutchman
asked not yet Peter answered I must go
to my trial first and the punishment for
mutiny you know he stopped the wind
moved his brown hair the Dutchman put a
hand on his arm I know Peter he said
sadly the punishment for mutiny is death
chapter 5 death life and Thursday there
were nine captains at the trial Peter
Hayward stood in front of them and
talked about the night of the mutiny it
was four years ago he said I was a young
officer 15 years old when I came up on
deck Captain Bligh was mr. Christians
prisoner how could I help him I didn&#39;t
have a sword or a gun mr. Christian put
Captain Bligh and 18 men into the launch
one of the nine captain&#39;s asked did you
try to help Captain Bligh mr. Heywood no
sir I couldn&#39;t Christian and his men had
swords and guns I had nothing a
different captain asked did mr.
Christian do the right thing then what
do you think no sir of course not but
you didn&#39;t get into the launch with
Captain Bligh why not I couldn&#39;t sir it
was full there were 19 men in it it
nearly sank without me did you say
anything to Captain Bligh ah no sir I
didn&#39;t some men did but not me so mr.
Haywood you were an officer on the
bounty and you saw this mutant
but you did nothing you just stood and
watched is that right ah yes sir peter
Hayward was afraid now I was very young
Ben sir you were an officer an officer
must always help his captain wait there
the nine captain&#39;s walked out of the
room Peter waited for a long time his
mother and sister were with him but he
felt afraid then the captain&#39;s came back
and the oldest captain said Peter
Hayward because you did not help Captain
Bligh we say you helped the mutiny and
there is only one punishment for mutiny
death do you understand Peter&#39;s face was
white and he felt ill but he said
quietly yes sir I understand two days
later he saw the oldest captain again
there was a small cold smile on his face
mr. Heywood I have a letter from the
king the older sailors must die but
because you were a young boy on the
bounty the King says you can live you
can go mr. Heywood you are a free man Oh
sir thank you thank you very much Peter
Hayward lived from
years 20 years later he was a captain of
a ship like Captain Bligh Captain Bligh
went back to Tahiti and took some more
bread fruit trees to Jamaica after that
he sailed many more ships he was an
important man he died in 1817 but what
happened to the bounty and Fletcher
Christian for years no one knew then 20
years after the mutiny in 1809 an
American ship the Topaz visited a small
island called pitkin when the captain of
the Topaz came home he had an
interesting story and five years after
that in 1814 to British ships the Briton
and vertigus arrived pitkin was a small
island with no we&#39;re good for ships to
land but a canoe came out through the
white water to the British ships the men
from the canoe came on to the Britain
and looked for the captain sir thomas
stains good afternoon he said who are
you a tall young man answered I&#39;m
Thursday I&#39;m sorry captain stain said
what did you say my name is Thursday
answered the young man Thursday October
Christian I live on this island you are
welcome here would you like to come to
my village and eat with us mr. Adams
would like to see you well
thank you very much said captain stains
and kept in pip on from the Tagus can he
come to of course said Thursday he is
welcome the two captains got into the
canoe and Thursday and his friends took
it through big green and white waves to
the island near the beach was a small
village how many people live here
captain stains asked about forty said
Thursday here is our king john adams an
old man with white hair came towards the
two captains he wore trousers and an
English sailors shirt good afternoon he
said my name is John Adams of HMS Bounty
welcome to Pitcairn Island some old
women gave the captain&#39;s wonderful food
and John Adams told them his story when
the bounty left Tahiti Christian was
very worried a ship is going to come
from England he said they want to kill
me they must never find us so when we
landed here we took all the pigs and
goats and burned the bounty we stood by
the sea and watched then we made our
village but Christian was always worried
and afraid and it was difficult to live
here the Tahitian men didn&#39;t like the
English sailors there were ten English
men
7 tyche and men and 12 Tahitian women
when Christian took the wife of one of
the Tahitian men the Tahitian man killed
him then that Asian men killed most of
the English men they nearly killed me
but the women stopped them the women
killed the Tahitian men after that there
was one man alive on the island me but
there were nine women and some small
children this young man Thursday is
Fletcher Christians son oh I see said
captain stains so you were alone here
with nine wives John Adams smiled he
looked at tired but happy man the old
women near him smiled too well yes sir
he said but I&#39;m a good husband to them
and a good father to all these children
and of course now that these boys are
men they have wives to do all speak
English captain Pippin asked yes sir
english an Tahitian too we have our pigs
and goats and coconut trees and we think
about God every day sir you are very
happy captain stain said we are sir john
adams said all of us but he stood up
slowly I know why you are here you are
going
to take me to England with you I must
die their captain stains looked at him
the Pitcairn Islanders looked very sad
and some of the women began to cry what
you mean man captain stains asked well
captain I was in the mutiny against
Captain Bligh it was a long time ago but
I did it I must take my punishment but
my god captain stains looked at captain
Pippin of course the man is right he
said but we can&#39;t do this you&#39;re an old
man mr. Adams and you are happy here
your wives and children need you it was
20 years ago man people in England don&#39;t
talk about the bounty today and Fletcher
Christian is dead he is dead but I&#39;m not
John Adams said I helped him and I&#39;m
here now in front of you and this is
your home captain stain said you are an
old man you must die here not in England
sit down mr. Adams let&#39;s finish this
wonderful food all right captain john
adam said and thank you he sat down and
the Pitcairn Islanders smiled tell me
about Bligh captain stains said he&#39;s an
important man now you know but most
people like him why were you all angry
with him Adams thought for a minute he
looked up at the trees over his village
and at the smiling faces of his wives
and children bly he said well he was a
good sailor of course we were angry with
him but I can&#39;t remember why it&#39;s a very
long time ago on the twenty-sixth of
october 1788 the bounty arrived at
tahiti the islanders came to the ship in
big canoes with food the king of Tahiti
otto was friendly bly went to Otto&#39;s
house and gave him things from the King
of England Thank You captain Otto said
you are welcome here I must give the
King of England something too but he&#39;s a
rich man what would he like do you know
fly smiled it was an important question
my king is very rich auto he said but we
don&#39;t have any bread fruit trees in
England my king would like some for his
people in Jamaica can I take some on my
ship r2 laughed of course he said that&#39;s
easy take
lots of them my people can help you
England is small he said but we&#39;re going
to some much smaller islands Tahiti the
friendly Islands they&#39;re small but
they&#39;re very warm and beautiful a sailor
John Adams laughed that&#39;s right mr.
Christian sir he said good food warm Sun
blue skies and hot beautiful women too I
won&#39;t be quiet man someone shouted
Christian and Hayward looked behind them
they saw the captain william bligh he
was a small man with brown hair
Christian new Bligh well they were
friends but Bligh was a captain now so
things were different the bounty was his
first ship and it was very important to
him don&#39;t talk about women on my ship
Adams he said angrily be quiet and sail
this ship are you here yes sir said
Adams quietly now listen to me mr.
Christian and you too mr. Heywood oxford
bookworms stage one mutiny on the bounty
by Tim Vickery read by Gareth Armstrong
published and copyright Oxford
University Press 2007
chapter one from England to Tahiti it
was a cold day in December 1787 there
was a strong wind and a green sea three
men and a boy stood on the deck of the
little ship HMS Bounty behind them on
the land were some hills and small white
houses the ship moved slowly out to see
the boy Peter Heyward was 14 years old
he was a young officer and he was happy
and excited England looks very small mr.
Christian he said Fletcher Christian
smiled at him Christian was a tall young
man with black hair and a long tired
face mr. Christian look at those men
there they aren&#39;t working run and talk
to them quickly bly smiled again at
haywood in a happy ship the men must
work hard but the officers must work
harder do you understand boy the bounty
sailed south across the Atlantic for ten
days they were in a storm near Cape Horn
but they could not sail west because of
the strong west wind so they sailed east
to South Africa Tasmania and Tahiti
there were 33 sailors on the bounty
andale
officers Bligh was the captain Christian
was his second officer the ship was
often wet and cold but no one was ill
once Bligh gave the sailors some apples
but they would not eat them because they
were old and bad Bligh was very angry
damn you men he shouted apples are good
for you you eat them I say Bligh stood
very near them but he didn&#39;t speak
quietly all the sailors could hear him
I&#39;m the captain of this ship remember
that we&#39;re going 30,000 kilometers
through bad weather and very bad seas
and I don&#39;t want any accidents you are
officers so you don&#39;t talk to sailors
about women or drink or anything you
must work hard and your sailors must
work hard to do you understand me mr.
Christian yes sir said Christian but he
didn&#39;t look happy good and you mr.
Hayward yes sir the boy looked at Bly
afraid then fly smiled is this your
first time at sea boy yes sir well you
must work hard and listen to me one day
perhaps you can be a captain too would
you like that yes sir
of course Peter Haywood smiled right
then