What are you doing, Annie?
Nothing!
What's this?
'Dream date, make my
dream come true É '
Oh, how did that get there?
How sweet!
Hector!
Oh hi, Bridget.
And up!!
Oh well, keep going, Hector.
Aah I see Hector found Cindy's
one hundred and one top exercises then.
Yes!
Oh, good try Hector.
Cindy is so old fashioned,
I can teach Hector how to exercise!
Exercise with Cindy, no,
exercise with Bridget, yes É
But É !
It's OK, I can do it!
Music please, Annie.
OK. Follow me.
Arms up, touch your toes,
stand straight and
- one-two-three -four-five-six-seven-eight!
More energy please!
One-two-three-four-five-six-seven-eight
OK, faster still!
Left leg up!
Oh, my leg hurts!
Come on, keep it up!
Come on, come on, faster É
Oh, hi Nick,
we're exercising.
I can see.
Oh, phew, OK.
Let's get a drink!
Oh, I must check my emails.
Would you like some water, Hector?
Oh no, no, after you.
No, you first.
Oh, no, no, no, ladies first.
No, no, you first
No, you first.
OH, give it to me!
Oh, goody! Three messages.
Oh dear.
What's wrong?
Annie's been on the Internet - again!
The Internet?
To find a boyfriend!
Oh, let's see!
Oh no, don't look.
Oh come on Annie!
Oh, all right then.
Ugh!
OK, number two.
Mmm...
A taxidermist!
Oh, how horrible!
Oh Charlie, here boy!
It's OK, Charlie.
Annie, what is a taxidermist?
Erm, well it's,
it's a, ah, oh never mind.
Third time lucky.
Hope so.
Hmm...
Oh dear!
Oh, I'll never get a boyfriend!
Bridget always has a boyfriend.
Has she?
Annie, look, it's not what you write,
it's,
it's how you write it.
I bet I could get a girlfriend
on the Internet, no problem.
Well yes Nick you could!
I bet you could not!
I could!
OK,
what would you write?
I'm six foot tall.
Five foot eleven.
I have blonde hair.
Mousey brown.
I love animals.
Ha!
And fast cars,
and beautiful women.
I would write to you!
Would you?
Oh, come on Annie!
Let's go to the gym.
Oh Bridget no,
not more exercise!
See you later boys.
Oh and erm, Hector,
would you do my washing for me?
Washing? OK.
No problem.
Oh and Nick
will you spray my plant for me please?
The spray is in the bathroom.
No problem.
Nick.
What is a taxidermist?
Oh -well,
well it's,
never mind.
Finding  girlfriends
on the Internet is so easy.
OK, Hector!
Question one.
How do guys get girlfriends?
Girlfriends?
Yeah!
Girlfriends.
Oh,
oh no girlfriends, me.
Never.
What?
Never?
No girl É no girlfriends?
Wow! Man!
You, Nick,
you have had girlfriends?
Yeah, loads!
Ten?
Ten?!! Hah!
Hundreds!
Wow!
So I know what girls like.
They like fast cars,
they like money,
they like dancing.
Oh, I love dancing!
Like this!
No, dancing like this!
Hey?
Yeah, Hector, leave it to me.
Leave it to me, my friend,
I  have a plan!
Oh, Hector, Annie's plant.
Her garden spray is in the bathroom.
Oh.
Garden - gar-den É
Spray, garden spray.
Garden Romance, garden É
good!
Hmm!
Perfect!
Cold, hot, very hot. Erm, Nick.
Uh-huh?
Bridget's cold or hot?
Hah, very hot!
Ah.
Perfect!
Perfect, ha!
Hector,
we'll get lots of girlfriends now!
From now on it'll be
girls, girls, girls, girls!
Yo!
Hey!
Whoo!
Oh you really must...
...change
your after shave!
Oh, excuse me, come on,
let's go out and celebrate.
What's that smell?
It smells like a perfumery.
Oh, my plant!
Oh, empty!
Oh, my poor plant!
I don't believe it!
My perfume,
Nick!
Oh good, the washing's done.
What's the problem?
This is the problem!
Hector!
Wow!
What is it now?
We have six hundred and thirty three
messages!
Let's see.
OK, one moment.
These messages are all
for Hector and Nick
- and  they're all from girls!
I smell a rat!
Hmm!
And I think I know who is responsible!
Oh, Bridget!
Look at this!
What?
'See attached photo.'
Ha, cheats,
they glued their photo on this car!
Ha, what a joke!
What!
that's how they received six hundred
and thirty three messages from girls.
But they don't know they received
six hundred and thirty three messages,
do they!
No, they don't - now.
Let's go to the cyber cafŽ.
I have a plan.
The poor computer.
How many messages?
One hundred!
Two hundred!
Oh.
How many?
Erm, one.
Good!
One hundred!
Erm, no, no, no,
just one message.
Uh?
[Erm]
Dancers,
you mean...
É dancers?!
Yes, sort of.
Wow!!
They sound gorgeous!
Uh?
Ah,
ah-hah!
Cuddles and Bubbles
are coming here tonight
when they finish the show
at
- 10 o'clock!
Look,
7 o'clock, 8, 9, 10 o'clock!
Wait a minute!
It's 7 o'clock!
That's just three hours!
What am I going to wear?
What are you going to wear?
But Nick,
what about Bridget and Annie?
Aha!
It's not a problem!
Ah-ha-ha! Yes!
So, Nick, what should I say?
It's easy, relax.
Yeah, but you have had
a hundred girlfriends.
Yeah, well, when I said a hundred,
it's actually fewer.
É Fifty?
No.
Forty?
Thirty?
No.
Twenty?
Ten?
No.
Five?
Ttt.
Four?
Eee.
Three?
Eeee.
Two?
Tsss
One?
Tssss.
None!
Aaaah!!!
OK.
It's OK.
Hi.
Hi!!!
Hello, it's us.
Come on up.
So Nick, what do I say?
OK, we need a script.
Try this.
Your eyes are b l u e,
like the ocean.
Your ears are blue,
No!!
Eyes, ears, ears! Eyes!
Oh, oh, oh, OK, OK.
Your ey-es are blue,
like the ocean.
Good!
You smell...
of sweet É
You smell of sweat É
No! No!
Sweet, not sweat!
Oh, OK, OK.
OK, your hair is so soft.
Thank you, Nick.
No, No, her hair, her hair!
Oh, her hair!
Oh, oh!
Ready?
Good luck!
Oh,
Cuddles and Bubbles.
But we thought you were dancers.
Oh, you are dancers.
Dancing É dogs!
In É Woof, The Musical.
Ha, ha, hello, come in.
Come in.
Oh please, sit down.
Sit!
Stick to the script.
You smell so sweet.
Your ears are É
blue, like the ocean.
Eyes, eyes!
Eyes!
Are you a million-aire?
Psst, psst!
Am I a millionaire?
Are you a millionaire?
We are millionaires!
Good - good.
Well you can pay for these then!!
If you please!!
Your faces!
We are the dancers É
From the cyber cafŽ!
So you are millionaires, ay?
Oh what a trick to get girlfriends!
Millionaires, very funny!
With fast cars!
Good trick, ay!
But that is my car!
Oooow!!!
Oh, you smell so sweet!
And you do have beautiful eyes!
Or is it ears?
It's the landlady!
I'm off!
Quick, hide Hector!
Erm, in the bedroom!
Oh Bridget.
Yes.
Tell me.
What is a taxidermist?
Oh!!!!
Next time in EXTRA.
Hector wants to get a job.
Bridget and Annie have a surprise.
And guess who's coming to dinner.
EXTRA - don't miss it!