oxford bookworms stage one one-way
ticket by Jennifer Bassett published and
copyright Oxford University Press 1992
the girl with green eyes of course the
man in the brown hat said they&#39;re a good
policeman and there are bad policeman
you know you&#39;re right the young man said
yes that&#39;s very true isn&#39;t it Julie he
looked at the young woman next to him
Julie didn&#39;t answer and looked bored she
closed her eyes Julie&#39;s my wife the
young man told the man in the brown hat
she doesn&#39;t like trains she always feels
ill on trains oh yes the man in the
brown hat said now my wife she doesn&#39;t
like buses she nearly had an accident on
a bus once it was last year no no it
wasn&#39;t it was two years ago I remember
now it was in Manchester he told a long
boring story about his wife and a bus in
Manchester it was a hot day and the
train was slow there were seven people
in the carriage there was the man in the
brown hat the young man and his wife
Julie a mother and two children and a
tall dark man in an expensive suit the
young man&#39;s name was Bill he had short
brown hair and a happy smile his wife
Julie had long red hair and very green
eyes the color of sea water they were
very beautiful
the man in the brown hat talked and
talked he had a big red face and a loud
voice he talked to bill because bill
like to talk to the man in the brown hat
laughed a lot and when he laughed bill
laughs to Bill like talking and laughing
with people the two children were hot
and bored they didn&#39;t want to sit down
they wanted to be noisy and run up and
down the train now sit down and be quiet
their mother said she was a small woman
with a tired face and a tired voice I
don&#39;t want to sit down the little boy
said I&#39;m firstly here have an orange his
mother said she took an orange out of
her bag and gave it to him I want an
orange to the little girl said loudly
all right here you are said her mother
eat it nicely now the children ate their
oranges and were quiet for a minute then
the little boy said I want to drink I&#39;m
thirsty the tall dark man took out his
newspaper and began to read Julie opened
her eyes and looked at the back page of
his newspaper she read about the weather
in Budapest and about the football in
Liverpool she wasn&#39;t interested in
Budapest and she didn&#39;t like football
but she didn&#39;t want to listen to bill
and the man in the brown hat talk talk
talk she thought bill never stops
talking
then suddenly she saw the tool man&#39;s
eyes over the top of his newspaper she
could not see his mouth but there was a
smile in his eyes quickly she looked
down at the newspaper and read about the
weather in Budapest again the train
stopped at dawlish station and people
got on and got off there was a lot of
noise if this our station the little
girl asked she went to the window and
looked out no it isn&#39;t now sit down her
mother said we&#39;re going to Penzance the
little girl told bill for our holidays
yes her mother said my sister&#39;s got a
little hotel by the sea we&#39;re staying
there it&#39;s cheap pc yes the man in the
brown hat said it&#39;s a nice town i know a
man there he&#39;s got a restaurant in King
Street a lot of holiday people go there
he makes a lot of money in the summer he
laughed loudly yes he said again you can
have a nice holiday in Penzance we&#39;re
going to some toast or bill said me and
Julie it&#39;s our first holiday Julie
wanted to go to Spain but I like front
hasta I always go there for my holidays
it&#39;s nice in August you can have a good
pan there too Julie looked out of the
window where is Budapest she thought I
want to go there I want to go to Vienna
to Paris
to Rome to Athens her green eyes were
bored and angry through the window she
watched the little villages and hills of
England the man in the brown hat looked
at Julie you&#39;re right he said to Bill
you can have a good time on holiday in
England we always go to Brighton me and
the wife but the weather we went one
year and it rained every day morning
afternoon and night it&#39;s true it never
stopped raining he laughed loudly we
nearly went home after the first week
bill laughs too what did you do all day
then he asked Julie read about the
weather and Budapest for the third time
then she looked at the tall man&#39;s hands
they were long brown hands very clean
nice hands she thought he wore a very
expensive Japanese watch japan she
thought I&#39;d like to go to Japan she
looked up and saw the man&#39;s eyes again
over the top of his newspaper this time
she did not look away green eyes looked
into dark brown eyes for a long slow
minute after Newton Abbot station the
guard came into the carriage to look at
their tickets now then he said where are
we all going this trains late the man in
the brown hat said 20 minutes late by my
watch ten minutes
the guard said that&#39;s all he smiled at
Julie the tall dark man put his
newspaper down found his ticket and gave
it to the guard the guard looked at it
you&#39;re all right sir he said the boat
doesn&#39;t leave Plymouth before six
o&#39;clock you got lots of time the tall
man smiled put his ticket back in his
pocket and opened his newspaper again
Julie didn&#39;t look at him a boat she
thought he&#39;s taking a boat from Plymouth
where&#39;s he going she looked at him again
with her long green eyes he read his
newspaper and didn&#39;t look at her but his
eyes smiled the train stopped at totnes
station and more people got on and off
everybody&#39;s going on holiday bill said
he laughed it&#39;s going to be wonderful no
work for two weeks it&#39;s a nice quiet
townsend austell we can stay in bed in
the mornings and sit and talk in the
afternoons and have a drink or two in
the evenings hey Julie he looked at his
wife are you all right Julie yes bill
she said quietly I&#39;m ok she looked out
of the window again the train went more
quickly now and it began to rain bill
and the man in the brown hat talked and
talked bill told a long story about two
men and a dog and the man in the brown
hat laughed very loudly back that good
story he said
I like that you tell it very well do you
know the story about and he told bill a
story about a Frenchman and a bicycle
why do people laugh at these stories you
II thought they&#39;re so boring but bill
liked it then he told a story about an
old woman and a cat and the man in the
brown hat laughed again that&#39;s good true
I don&#39;t know how do you remember the
mall because Julie thought he tells them
every day I don&#39;t understand the little
girl said suddenly she looked at bill
why did the cat died Shh be quiet her
mother said come and eat you sandwiches
now that&#39;s all right bill said I like
children the man in the brown hat looked
at the children sandwiches hmm I&#39;m
hungry too he said you can get
sandwiches in the restaurant on this
train he looked at bill let&#39;s go down to
the restaurant egg I need a drink too
bill laughed you&#39;re right it&#39;s thirsty
work telling stories the two men stood
up and left the carriage the little girl
ate her sandwich and looked at Julie but
why did the cat died she asked I don&#39;t
know Julie said perhaps it wanted to die
the little girl came and sat next to
Julie I like your hair she said
it&#39;s beautiful Julie looked down at her
and smiled for some minutes it was quiet
in the carriage then the tall dark man
opened his bag and took out a book he
put it on the seat next to him and
looked at Julie with a smile Julie
looked back at him and then down at the
book famous towns of Italy she read
Venice Florence Rome Naples she looked
away again out of the window at the rain
two weeks innocent austell she thought
with bill in the rain after half an hour
the two men came back to the carriage
there are a lot of people on this train
bill sex do you want a sandwich Julie no
she said I&#39;m not hungry you eat them the
train was nearly at Plymouth doors
opened and people began to move a lot of
people get on here the man in the brown
hat said the tall dark man stood up and
put his book and his newspaper in his
bag then he picked up his bag and left
the carriage the train stopped at the
station a lot of people got on the train
and two women and an old man came into
the carriage they had a lot of bags with
them bill and the man in the brown hat
stood up and helped them one of the
women had a big bag of apples the bag
broke and the apples went all over the
carriage Oh down she said everybody
laughed and helped her to find the Apple
the Train moved away from Plymouth
station after a minute or two everybody
sat down and the woman gave some apples
to the children where&#39;s Julie bill said
suddenly she&#39;s not here perhaps she went
to the restaurant the man in the brown
hat said but she wasn&#39;t hungry bill said
she told me the little girl looked at
bill she got off the train plymouth she
said would you troll dark man i saw them
of course she didn&#39;t bill said she&#39;s on
this train she didn&#39;t get off yes she
did the children&#39;s mother said suddenly
I saw her too the tall man waited for
her on the platform he waited for her
build mouth was open but but she read
his newspaper all the time he didn&#39;t
talk to Julie and she never talked to
him they didn&#39;t say a word people don&#39;t
always need words young man the
children&#39;s mother said but she&#39;s my wife
Bill&#39;s face was red and angry she can&#39;t
do that he said loudly he stood up I&#39;m
going to stop the train everybody looked
at him and the two children laughed no
the man in the brown hat said no you
don&#39;t want to do that sit down and eat
your sandwiches my friend but can I
don&#39;t understand why did she go what am
I going to do
Bill&#39;s face was very unhappy after a
second or two he sat down again what am
I going to do he said again nothing the
man in the brown hat said he ate his
sandwich slowly go and have your holiday
in some toast or you can have a good
time there forget about Julie those
green eyes now he took out a second
sandwich and began to eat it I knew a
woman once with green eyes she gave me a
very bad time now you want to forget
about Julie south for the winter I never
stay in one country for a long time it
gets boring I like to move on see new
places meet different people it&#39;s a good
life most of the time when I need money
I get a job I can do most things hotel
and restaurant work building work
picking fruit in Europe you can pick
fruit most of the year you need to be in
the right country at the right time of
course it&#39;s not easy work but the
money&#39;s not bad I like to go south in
the winter life is easier in the Sun and
northern Europe can get very cold in the
winter last year nineteen eighty-nine it
was I was in Venice for october i did
some work in a hotel for three weeks
then
I began slowly to move south I always go
by train when I can I like trains you
can walk about on a train and you meet a
lot of people I left Venice and went on
to Trieste there I got a cheap ticket
for the slow train to Sofia in Bulgaria
this train goes all down through
Yugoslavia and takes a long time a day
and a half but that didn&#39;t matter to me
the train left wrist at nine o&#39;clock on
a Thursday morning there weren&#39;t many
people on it at first but at Zagreb more
people got on two girls went along the
corridor past my carriage they looked
through the door but they didn&#39;t come in
then an old woman came in sat down and
went to sleep the two girls came back
along the corridor and looked into the
carriage again the train left Zagreb and
I looked out of the window for about 10
minutes then I went to sleep too when I
opened my eyes again the two girls were
in the carriage they look friendly so I
said hello hi they said you&#39;re American
I said all Canadian right American the
taller girl said she smiled and you&#39;re
23 your name&#39;s Tom Walsh you&#39;ve got blue
eyes and your mom lives in
burnham-on-sea UK right how did you know
all that I asked
the second girl laughed she looked at
your passport it&#39;s in your coat pocket
oh right my coat was on the seat next to
me I took my passport out of my pocket
and put it back in my bag who are you
then I asked they told me Melanie and
Carol from Los Angeles USA they liked
Europe they said they knew a lot of
places Britain Holland Denmark Germany
France Spain Italy Yugoslavia Bulgaria
Greece I&#39;m going to Bulgaria now I said
for about a month then I&#39;m going south
for the winter cyprus or perhaps north
africa oh yes they said we love Bulgaria
sophia is a great town wonderful what do
you do about money I asked well you know
Carol smiled sometimes we get a little
job this and that but what about you
yeah come on Melanie said tell us about
you Tom Walsh with the blue eyes and my
mum and burnham-on-sea what are you
doing with your life hey so I told them
they were nice girls they were older
than me perhaps 27 or 28 but I like them
we talked and laughed for hours I told
them a lot of stories about my life some
of the stories were true some weren&#39;t
but the girls laughed and said I was a
great guy I asked them about both
area because I didn&#39;t know the country
they knew sofia well they said hey Carol
Melanie said we&#39;re staying in Baylor
palanca for a day or two but let&#39;s go
over to sow fear this weekend and me Tom
there we can meet him on Saturday night
at the hotel marmara yeah it&#39;s a good
hotel Carol told me cheap but good why
do you think tom great I said let&#39;s do
that the train was very slow we got to
Belgrade at six o&#39;clock in the evening
and a lot of people got off they were
only me and the girls in the carriage
Lynn the guard came and looked at our
tickets and went away again Carol looked
at Melanie hey Mel she said why don&#39;t
you and Tom go along to the restaurant
I&#39;m not hungry and I want to sleep for
an hour a foods very expensive on the
train I said I haven&#39;t got much money
just now I&#39;m going to get a job in Sofia
Oh Tom Melanie said why didn&#39;t you tell
us look you&#39;re a nice guy right we&#39;re
okay for money this week we can buy you
a meal of course we can Carol said and
look in Sofia we can take you to the
best restaurant in town it&#39;s a great
place we love it what could I say I was
hungry they had money I didn&#39;t so
Melanie and I went to the restaurant and
had a meal when we came back carol was
still alone
in the carriage Melanie put her feet on
the seat and went to sleep at miss some
more people got on the train and two old
men came into our carriage they looked
at Melanie&#39;s feet on the seat and talked
in loud voices Carol laughed a Melanie
opened her eyes and set up are we nearly
there she asked Carol and looked out of
the window yeah about half an hour I
think why are you getting off at Baylor
palanca I asked what are you going to do
there Melanie smiled find a cheap hotel
meet people take a look at the town you
know just for a day or two terrified but
there&#39;s nothing there oh well you never
know Melanie loft see you in Sofia right
on Saturday night the hotel marmara okay
eight o&#39;clock Carol said don&#39;t forget
now okay great I said see you there the
train came into Bella palanca and
stopped the two girls got off and stood
on the platform they smiled at me
through the window saturday eight
o&#39;clock Melanie shouted okay I called
they couldn&#39;t hear me because of the
noise in the station they smiled again
picked up their bags and walked away
nice girls I&#39;m going to have a great
time in Sofia I thought the train left
Yugoslavia and crossed into Bulgaria at
two o&#39;clock in the morning then the
train stopped at some village I don&#39;t
remember the name
I at an apple and looked out of the
window suddenly there were a lot of
policemen on the train everybody in the
carriage SAT up and began to talk what&#39;s
happening I said in Italian to the old
man next to me I don&#39;t know he said in
bad Italian perhaps they&#39;re looking for
somebody Luke the police are taking some
people off the train then two policemen
came into our carriage a tall thin one
and a short fat one they looked
everybody carefully and then they looked
at me again come with us please the fat
policeman said in English what me I said
why what&#39;s the matter and bring your bag
with you the toll policeman said I began
to ask a question but policeman never
liked questions from young men with long
hair so I stayed quiet picked up my bag
and went with him in the station
building there were a lot more policemen
and some people from the Train they were
all young people I saw some were afraid
some were bored the police looked in
everybody&#39;s bags and then the people
went back to the Train my two policemen
took me to a table your birth boards
please the fat policeman said and open
your bag they looked at my passport and
I opened my bag there was a young police
woman with red hair at the next table
she had a nice face so I smiled at her
and she smiled back
aha the tall policeman said suddenly all
my dirty shirts and clothes were out on
the table the policeman picked up my bag
and turned it over onto the table out of
my bag fell packet after packet of us
American dollars nice new dollars fifty
dollar moats impede packets a lot of
money my mouth opened and stayed open I
couldn&#39;t find my voice I was suddenly a
very interesting person and a lot of
police ran up to our table and stood
behind me fifty thousand a hundred
thousand a hundred and fifty thousand
there&#39;s two hundred thousand dollars
here the toll policeman said what an
interesting bag mr. Tong wash I found my
voice again quickly but it&#39;s not my bag
I shouted there was a big happy smile on
that policeman&#39;s face well he said it&#39;s
got your name on it look so i looked and
of course there was my name and yes of
course it was my bag so how did 200,000
US dollars get into my bag you cannot
bring a US dollars into this country the
fat policeman said he had very short
gray hair and little black eyes he
didn&#39;t smile once but I didn&#39;t bring
them I said quickly they&#39;re not my
dollars I never
them before in my life and there was a
lot of noise in the station I looked out
of the window and saw my train slowly it
began to move hey I shouted that&#39;s my
train the tool policeman laughed it was
a great day for him oh no he said you&#39;re
not getting back on that train you&#39;re
staying here with us in our beautiful
country he smiled happily so I never got
to Sofia on Saturday I was very unhappy
about that I wanted to have a little
talk with Melanie and Carol ask them one
or two questions you know you&#39;re a nice
guy tom see you in Sofia okay taking to
the best restaurant in town yeah great
and I never got down to Cyprus or North
Africa that winter oh well I live and
learn it&#39;s not an easy life in prison
but it&#39;s warm in winter and the foods
not bad and i&#39;m meeting some interesting
people there&#39;s a man from Georgia USSR
Boris his name is he comes from a place
by the Black Sea he&#39;s a great guy when
we get out of here he and I are going
down to Australia Brisbane perhaps or
Sydney get a job on a ship start a new
life yeah next year is going to be ok
Sahara&#39;s and the night train mr. Harris
like trains it was afraid of aeroplanes
and didn&#39;t like buses but train they
were big and noisy and exciting when he
was a boy of 10 he liked trains now he
was a man of 50 and he still liked
trains so he was a happy man on the
night of the fourteenth of September he
was on the night train from Helsinki to
all in Finland and he had ten hours in
front of him I got a book and my
newspaper he thought and there&#39;s a good
restaurant on the drain and then I&#39;ve
got two weeks holiday with my Finnish
friends in oulu there weren&#39;t many
people on the train and nobody came into
mr. Harris&#39;s carriage he was happy about
that most people on the train slept
through the night but mr. Harris like to
look out of the window and to read and
think after dinner in the restaurant mr.
Harris came back to his carriage and sat
in his seat next to the window for an
hour or two he watched the trees and
lakes of Finland out of the window then
it began to get dark so he opened his
book and began to read at midnight the
train stopped at the small station of
Ottawa mr. Harris looked out of the
window but he saw nobody the Train moved
away from the station into the black
night again then the door mr. Harris&#39;s
carriage opened and two people came in a
young man and a young woman the young
woman was angry she closed the door and
shouted at the man Carl you can&#39;t do
this to me the young man laughed loudly
and sat down mr. Harris
was a small quiet man he wore quiet
clothes and he had a quiet voice he did
not like noisy people and loud voices so
he was not pleased young people are
always noisy he thought why can&#39;t they
talk quietly he put his book down and
closed his eyes but he could not sleep
because the two young people didn&#39;t stop
talking the young woman sat down and
said and acquired her voice Carl you&#39;re
my brother and I love you but please
listen to me you can&#39;t take my diamond
letters give it back to me now please
Carl smiled no Elena he said I&#39;m going
back to Russia soon and I&#39;m taking your
diamonds with me he took off his hat and
put it on the feet Elena listen you have
a rich husband but I I have no money I
have nothing how can I live without
money you can&#39;t give me money so I need
your diamonds little sister mr. Harris
looked at the young woman she was small
with black hair and dark eyes her face
was white and afraid mr. Harris began to
feel sorry for Elena she and her brother
didn&#39;t look at him once can&#39;t they see
me he thought car Elena said her voice
was very quiet now and mr. Harris
listened carefully you came to dinner at
our house tonight and you went to my
room and took my diamond necklace how
could you do that to me my husband gave
the diamonds to me they were his
mother&#39;s diamonds before that he is
going to be very very angry and I&#39;m
afraid of him her brother laughed
put his hand in his pocket then took it
out again and opened it slowly the
diamond necklace in his hand was very
beautiful mr. Harris stared at it for a
minister to nobody moved and it was
quiet in the carriage there was only the
noise of the train and it went quickly
on through the dark cold night mr.
Harris opened his book again but he
didn&#39;t read it he watched cars face with
its hungry eyes and it&#39;s cold smile what
beautiful beautiful diamonds cars it I
can get a lot of money for these give
him back to me Carl Elena whispered my
husband&#39;s going to kill me you&#39;re my
brother please help me please Carl
laughed again and mr. Harris wanted to
hit him go home little sister Carl said
I&#39;m not going to give the Diamonds back
to you go home to your angry husband
suddenly there was a knife in the young
woman&#39;s hand a long bright knife mr.
Harris watched with his mouth open he
couldn&#39;t speak or move keep the diamonds
back to me Elena cried or I&#39;m going to
kill you a hand on the knife was white
car laughed and laughed what a sister he
said what a kind sweet sister no they&#39;re
my diamonds now put your knife away
little sister but the knife in the white
hand moved quickly up then down there
was a long terrible cry and Carl&#39;s body
fell slowly onto the seat the color of
the seat began to changed to red and the
diamond necklace fell from Carl&#39;s hand
onto the floor Elena&#39;s face was white oh
no she whispered Carl I come back
come back I didn&#39;t want to kill you but
card and dancer and the red blood ran
slowly over the floor Elena put her head
in her hands and again in the carriage
of the long terrible cry mr. Harris&#39;s
face was white too he opened his mouth
but he couldn&#39;t speak he stood up and
carefully moved to the door the young
woman was quiet now she didn&#39;t move or
look up at mr. Harris in the corridor
mr. Harris ran the guard was at the back
of the train and mr. Harris got there in
half a minute quickly mr. Harris said
come quickly an accident a young woman
OD ha her brother is his bed the guard
ran with mr. Harris back to the carriage
mr. Harris opened the door and they went
inside there was no dead body of a young
man there was no young woman no blood no
knife no diamond necklace only mr.
Harris&#39;s bags and his hat and coat the
guard looked at mr. Harris and mr.
Harris looked at him but mr. Harris
began but they were here I saw them she
the young woman she had a knife and she
she killed her brother a knife you say
the guard asked yes mr. Harris said
quickly a long life and her brother took
her diamonds so she ah diamonds the
guard said was the young woman&#39;s name
Elena he asked yes it was mr. Harris
said how do you know that do you do you
know her yes I know the guard said
slowly
he thought for a minute then looked at
mr. Harris Elena d sorrow Nellie he said
she had dark eyes and black hair very
beautiful she was half italian half
finish her brother was a half brother
they had the same father but his mother
was russian i think was had mr. Harris
stared the guard but she Elena she&#39;s
alive and where is she oh no said the
guard Elena de Sarenne le died about 80
years ago after she killed her brother
with a knife she jumped off the train
and died at once it was near here I
think he looked out of the window into
the night mr. Harris&#39;s face was very
white again eight years ago he whispered
what are you saying what she and her
brother but I saw them yes that&#39;s right
the guard said you saw them but they&#39;re
not alive they&#39;re ghosts they often come
on the night train at this time in
September I never see them but somebody
saw them last year a man and his wife
they were very unhappy about it but what
can I do I can&#39;t stop a Lena and Carl
coming on the train the guard looked at
mr. Harris&#39;s white face you need a drink
he said come and have a vodka with me
mr. Harris didn&#39;t usually drink vodka
but he felt afraid when he closed his
eyes he could see again Elena&#39;s long
knife and could hear her terrible cry so
he went with the guard to the back of
the train after the vodka mr.
us felt better he didn&#39;t want to sleep
and the guard was happy to talk so mr.
Harris stayed with the guard and didn&#39;t
go back to his carriage yes the guard
said it&#39;s a famous story I don&#39;t
remember it all it happened a long time
ago of course Elena&#39;s father was a
famous man here in Finland he was very
rich once but he had three or four wives
and about eight children and he liked a
good things of life so there wasn&#39;t much
money for the children Carl the oldest
son was a bad man people say he wanted
an easy life and money in his hand all
the time the train hurried on to Alou
through the Black Knight and the guard
drank some more vodka now Elena he said
she didn&#39;t have an easy life with those
three difficult men a father her brother
a husband one year she visited her
mother&#39;s family in Italy and there she
met her husband d Sara Nelly he was rich
but he wasn&#39;t a kind man they came back
to Finland and Karl often visited their
house he wanted money from his sisters
rich husband Elena loved her brother and
gave him some money but d sorrow Nelly
didn&#39;t like Karl and was angry with
Elena he stopped giving her money and
after that well you know the story now
yes mr. Harris said poor unhappy Elena
mr. Harris stayed with his friends in
for two weeks it were quiet weeks and
mr. Harris had a good holiday but he
took the bus back to Helsinki
the bus was slow and there were a lot of
people on it but mr. Harris was very
happy he didn&#39;t want to take the night
train across Finland again