This is the story of Bridget and Annie,
who share a flat in London.
They have a neighbour, Nick.
Nick fancies Bridget.
But Annie fancies Nick.
That's the way it is
until Bridget gets a letter from Argentina.
Stand by for Extra.
Is he stupid?
I told you...
Sorry. B.
Yes, John?
Yes, I got the cards
and the flowers and the chocolates.
Yes. And I got the cushion as well.
But it's finished. Sorry.
But please don't leave me.
-  Don't cry.
-  I love you so much.
Goodbye.
Oh, and happy birthday.
Ah, men!
Come on, Charley. Come on.
Post, Bridget. Charley and I have the post,
haven't we, Charley?
Give me the post, Charley.
Drop it, Charley.
Oh, good boy!
Telephone bill, gas bill, electricity bill.
What's this?
A parcel for you, Bridget.
Good. What is it?
Oh, it's from Mother.
'Bridget darling, this arrived for you
and I made you this.
'Love, Mummy.'
Oh, very you, Bridget.
Mother!
Ooh, this is from Argentina.
Argentina? Who from? What does it say?
Erm, it says, 'Hello, do you remember me?'
No.
'Seven years ago we was penpals.
'We was...' We were penpals.
Oh, yeah, now I remember. It's Hector.
Who's Hector?
He was my penpal seven years ago.
Oh.
'I speak English good now...'
I speak English good.
I speak English well now...
'..and I am coming to England.'
Ooh, Latin Americans!
'I would like to sleep with you.'
'Do you have a bed for me?'
Oh, he wants to stay here.
But, erm, what about the rules?
Ooh, a Latin American here.
Ooh, like Ricky Martin!
-  Tall, handsome...
-  Rich.
So, erm, when is he coming?
Oh, erm, let me see. It says...November 5th.
Oh, November 5th. But that's...
Today!
Oh, it's you, Nick.
Hi, babes!
-  Hello, Nick. How are you?
-  Great.
Nice muscles.
-  Here's your milk.
-  Our milk?
You mean our milk
you borrowed three weeks ago.
Oh, thanks, Nick.
I forget nothing!
Would you like a drink, Nick?
-  Uh- huh?
-  I said, 'Would you like a drink, Nick?'
Oh! Sorry.
No, thanks.
Oh, erm, Bridget's friend is coming.
-  Oh, yeah?
-  Uh- huh. From Argentina.
Wow! From Argentina!
-  What's she like?
-  She is a he.
-  Huh?
-  Not a girl, a boy.
Tough guy, eh?
Why don't I show you how to do it properly?
Nick, I've told you before,
nobody uses my bike. Nobody. Is that clear?
-  Well, why not?
-  Why not?
If you touch my bike again, you are out.
O- U- T, out. Clear?
What?
I said...
-  Hello.
I am called Argentina. I am from Hector.
You mean, 'I am called Hector.'
You are called Hector?
Oh, no, no, no. I am called Annie.
I am called Annie.
No. She means, 'I am called Hector.
I am from Argentina.'
You are from Argentina?
Come in.
Hello.
-  Hi, babes!
-  Hello, Nick.
I forget nothing.
Nobody uses my bike. Nobody. Is that clear?
-  Well, why not?
-  Why not?
I am called Argentina. I am from Hector.
My cars.
You play with cars?
Yes. You play...no.
I play with cars.
He plays with cars.
I read. I love the library.
Fascinating.
We go to the library too, don't we, Bridget?
Yes, it's great.
Good.
I live here.
You live in a museum, full of old things?
Old things? Yes, I have lots of old things.
I live in a museum.
OK, I live in a museum.
Well, thank you, Hector.
And now we'll show you the flat.
This is the bedroom.
Thank you.
Who- hey!
Where do you sleep?
Er, no, you don't understand.
We only have one bedroom.
One? I have 20.
20?
Yes, he lives in a museum, with 20 bedrooms.
Oh! Very funny, 20 bedrooms.
Well, you can sleep here.
Oh, thank you.
-  Oh, no, no, no, Hector.
-  Uh?
It's a bed.
A bed? Oh, wow...
Oh...
-  Here's a cushion.
-  Oh, thank you.
Oh, this of course is the TV.
But just relax. I must go to the bathroom.
Psst! Annie! Bathroom!
Now!
Oh, my goodness. What are we going to do?
He plays with toy cars.
He is not a sexy Argentinian.
But he is sweet.
And he is polite.
But those clothes!
He is so old- fashioned.
He must go.
Room service.
Hello. Who are you?
-  Oh. You are quick. Good.
-  Eh?
-  My luggage is downstairs.
-  What?
-  Bring it up, please.
-  What are you doing?
I pulled, you come. You are the butler.
The butler?
I am Nick. I live next door.
I am Hector.
Oh, Hector, from Argentina.
Yes, from Argentina.
Where are the girls?
-  The girls?
-  Yeah, Bridget and Annie.
Oh, they live here.
Yeah, I know. Where's Bridget?
Does she know you are here?
Bridget, she gave me this.
Hello, Nick. Oh, this is Hector from Argentina.
Yeah, I know.
-  Isn't he wonderful?
-  Wonderful.
-  Are you hungry?
-  Uh?
We'll buy your lunch.
What would you like to eat?
-  Fish and chips?
-  Oh, fish and ships!
Erm, Nick, Hector, make friends?
Nick, teach Hector some English.
Yeah, OK.
I'll teach Hector some English.
Oh, you are quick. Good.
I pulled, you come. You are the butler.
The butler?
She gave me this.
I'll teach Hector some English.
OK...this is the oven.
This is the oven.
Annie's dog sleeps in the oven.
So you say, 'Annie, the dog is in the oven.'
Annie, the dog is in the oven.
Great! Now Bridget.
-  Oh. Oh, dear.
-  Huh?
Well, Bridget likes strong men,
especially strong legs.
I am strong.
Yeah? Can you cycle 50 kilometres?
-  Yes.
-  No way.
-  Well, go on, then, show me.
Yes, look.
Adios, amigo.
Ah. Bridget, Annie, lunch.
Fish and chips.
Yes, lunch, Hector.
Look, Bridget, 50 kilometres.
Oh, Annie, the dog is in the oven.
What?
Hi. Everything OK?
Great!
I am... How do you say? Erm...
-  Dead.
-  Hot.
Hot. Yeah, I am hot. I need a...
-  Shower.
-  Yeah, I need a shower.
-  Be my guest.
-  Oh, thank you.
Right, that's it. He must go.
Why? He is so nice.
He used my bike.
Yeah, and he said that the dog was in the oven.
What a horrible joke.
Where is Charley? Charley!
-  What a bad, bad boy.
-  He must go.
-  Can he stay with you, Nick?
-  Uh- uh. Sorry, ladies.
-  Oh, please, Nick. You have a spare room.
-  No way. Not my problem.
-  He must go now.
-  But he's in the shower.
I don't care.
Hector, please come out,
we want to talk to you.
I like fish and chips, I...
Hector, please come out, we want to talk to you.
OK, one moment, please.
I like fish and chips...
Yes, you want me?
-  We think...
-  We...
We...we have a problem.
It's like this.
Go on, then, tell him.
Yes, Bridget?
Hector, the thing is...
Stay there. I'll talk to him.
Hector, can I have a word, please?
Ricky Martin!
Hector, is this you?
Yes, and my parents.
'The Romero family,
one of the richest families in Argentina.'
Who are these?
My...
-  Servants.
-  Yeah, my servants.
-  Your cars?
-  Yeah, my cars.
Hector, you are rich.
Why stay here?
I want friends. Good friends.
People like you for your money?
That's awful.
Erm... Listen, keep it a secret.
-  OK.
Perhaps he could stay here.
Yes. Poor boy.
Hector, come and stay with me.
I have two rooms.
-  Shut up, Nick.
-  Hector will stay with us, won't you, Hector?
Hector, come and...sit down.
Hector, please, call me Gigi.
Oh, Charley, there you are.
Oh, Annie, the dog is in the oven.
The oven?
Yes. Nick is a good English teacher.
Yes, a very good English teacher.
-  I'd love to see your photos again.
-  Oh, me too.
Oh, your sweet toy cars!
They are not toys.
Today Hector arrives and it's Bonfire Night.
Let's party!
-  What sort of music do you like?
-  Music?
Yeah, music. You know, soul, funk, dance.
Watch me. Like this.
Interesting.
I dance...like this.
I'll get it. I'll get it.
Hello.
Oh, yeah, that's great.
Sure. Come up.
-  It's the landlady!
-  The tarantula!
-  Quick, hide, Hector.
-  I'm off. I owe two weeks' rent.
Next time in Extra...
The flatmates go shopping for Hector.
Hector goes shopping for the girls.
But what happens
when Hector goes shopping for himself?
This is the story of two girls
who share a flat in London.
They have a neighbour, Nick,
who likes Bridget.
But Annie likes Nick.
That is until Hector arrives from Argentina,
and Hector is very, very handsome.
Stand by for Extra.
Oh. Argentinian.
Maybe...
Hector, please,
call me Gigi.
'Oh, Hector, call me Gigi.'
-  A.
-  Is Hector still asleep?
Yep.
Hector, wakey- wakey.
Come on. Rise and shine.
Sweet.
Good morning.
Oh, good morning.
No, no, no. Good morning.
-  Ah- ah- ah.
-  Oh.
Good morning.
Ah- ah- ah.
No, Hector.
-  I have a cold.
-  And so have I.
Oh, you have a cold, Bridget.
Yes, I have a cold.
Yes. We have a cold.
So let's begin again.
Good morning.
Oh, never mind.
Hector, would you like some...
new pyjamas?
Hector, please excuse me for a moment.
Pssst. Annie. Bathroom.
Now.
-  Good morning.
Is it fancy dress?
Fancy dress?
Yes.
Oh. Nice.
Hey.
Nice car, eh?
I have this car at home.
Wow. You have this car at home?
Girls must love you.
Girls?
-  No.
-  No?
Hector, can I tell you something?
OK.
The car looks good.
Yeah?
So you must look good too.
-  I look good.
-  No.
You don't look good.
But I can help.
OK.
Yes.
-  Hector's clothes are awful.
-  They're so old- fashioned.
I know. I'll take him shopping.
But, Bridget, you are so busy.
I'll take him shopping.
-  No, it's all right, I'll take him shopping.
-  It's no problem, I'll take him.
I said I'll take him shopping!
You need...
You need a...
Well, hi, babe.
-  Oh, it's you, Nick.
-  Oh, hi, Nick.
Hector has asked me what clothes to wear.
Yeah, right.
You need a look
like on a fast bike.
No, no, no, Hector, don't listen to Nick.
-  Listen to me.
-  OK.
You need a designer look.
No, no, no, Hector, that's not for you.
You need,
you need...a cowboy look.
-  No, no. A leather jacket.
-  A bandanna and a vest.
A denim shirt.
-  A motorbike.
-  Designer.
Cowboy.
Stop.
OK.
I will go shopping.
-  What?
-  On your own?
But...you need us.
How? What will you say?
Er...
It's OK. Leave it to me.
I am the shopkeeper, you are the customer.
-  Uh?
-  This is a shop.
-  I sell, you buy.
-  Oh, OK.
Ding- dong.
Good morning.
Can I help you?
Yes. I...
I would like...
Oh. I would like...
a jacket, please.
Trousers.
I would like a pair of trousers, please.
Oh, I would like a pair of trousers, please.
And...
a shirt.
No.
Shoes.
I would like a pair of shoes, please.
And a cat for my head.
I think you mean a hat.
This is a cat.
A cat? A cat for my head.
A cat for my head!
Hector. Come shopping with me.
-  Or me.
-  No, me.
-  He's my pen friend.
-  All right.
Me, you and you will go shopping for Hector
a little bit each.
I will go to the shoe shop.
And I will go to the clothes shop.
No, I'll go to the clothes shop.
OK. I'll just buy the shirt.
I'll buy the trousers.
Good.
Right. Let's go.
Oh, no. I completely forgot.
We need eggs, lemons and dog food.
Oh, it's all right. I'll do it online later.
'Eggs, lemons, dog food.'
Oh, well done, Hector.
Bye, Hector. Oh, and don't answer the phone.
It might be the tarantula.
OK.
Bye, Hector. Be good.
And if you can't be good, be careful.
-  Huh?
-  Never mind.
..new pyjamas.
I'll take him shopping.
Me, you and you will go shopping for Hector
a little bit each.
You need a cowboy look.
You need a look like on a fast bike.
Good morning, sir.
I would like...
a cat for my head!
A cat...
Oh. Room service.
Hello. I would like an egg for my head.
Lemons for my head!
-  Dog food for my head!
-  Who's that?
The tarantula!
I said, 'Who's that?'
-  Hello?
-  Where's Bridget?
Er... Where is Bridget?
Me.
I am Bridget.
I don't believe you.
Yes, I have a cold.
-  Atchoo! Atchoo!
-  Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, thank you. Atchoo!
Charley!
Is that a dog?
No, no, it's not a dog, it's a...
Annie. Yes.
Annie has a cold also.
Oh, poor Annie.
Thank you. Atchoo. Now goodbye.
Atchoo! Atchoo!
Ole.
I am Hector.
I speak English.
'Eggs, lemons, dog food.
'Eggs, lemons, dog food.'
Oh, hi. Good afternoon, Annie.
Good afternoon, Hector.
I bought this for you.
What is it?
Try it on.
Try...
it...
on.
Try...
it...
on.
Oh. Try it on.
-  Where's Hector?
-  In the bathroom.
Good. I'll give this to him.
-  It's OK, I'll give it to him.
-  No, it's all right.
Hector.
I've got something for you.
Oh. OK.
Come in.
Spoilsport.
Hector?
-  Hello?
-  Here are your clothes.
You will look so cool.
-  Cool?
-  Cool.
Cool.
Nice melons.
Melons? Who are those from?
I think Hector has been shopping online.
I'm really thirsty. I need a drink.
-  But we don't need any melons.
-  Well, he did try.
And he bought some eggs.
Yeah.
Just a few.
Nice melons.
Thank you.
Try...
it...
on.
I've got something for you.
So how did Hector do the shopping?
Hector ordered ten melons
instead of ten lemons.
Oh, an easy mistake. He did try.
Yes, he did try.
-  What about the eggs?
-  OK. Eggs.
You buy a dozen eggs, yeah?
Yep. A dozen is ten.
A dozen is 12, stupid.
I know.
Well, Hector has put the number 12 here.
Well, that's OK. That's one box.
No. He ordered 12 boxes.
144.
Now...dog food.
I can't wait.
OK. I'm ready.
-  We're ready.
-  Enter.
Do you like it?
Well?
Er... I like the shirt.
-  I like the sarong.
-  I like the shoes.
So...
am I cool?
Erm...
No.
I'm not cool.
Er...no.
So...I will go shopping.
Here we go again. Hector.
You can't go out there on your own.
You went shopping on the Internet.
Yes.
Your ordered melons instead of lemons
and too many eggs.
-  Have you ever been to a supermarket?
-  No.
My...
Who are these?
-  Servants?
-  Yeah. My servants.
-  Servants. Now I understand.
-  Come on, Hector.
-  I will teach you how to shop, Hector.
-  Till you drop.
Bridget and I will be the shopkeepers.
And you are our customer.
OK.
-  Good afternoon.
Can I help you, sir?
What would you like to buy?
Oh. I would like some...
Clothes.
Yes. I would like some clothes, please.
What size?
What erm, erm...
size?
I don't know.
I'll have to measure you, then.
Arms up, please.
Chest.
112 centimetres.
Chest, 112 centimetres.
And waist.
82 centimetres.
Waist.
And leg.
-  I'll do that!
-  No, it's OK.
I shall do that.
Eight...
y- seven centimetres.
Now, do you like these trousers?
Do you like this shirt?
Yes.
Good. That's erm...
£5,000, please.
OK.
No, no, no, Hector.
£5,000 is...
is...
8,000 dollars.
Yeah.
It's too much. It's too expensive.
Not for Hector.
So...
I am ready to go shopping.
-  Good luck.
-  Yeah. Good luck.
You'll need it.
Where's my lemon drink, Nick?
Nick, are there any more tissues?
All right. I'm coming as fast as I can.
OK.
Oh. I feel awful.
Me too. Nothing will make me feel better.
Can you get that, please, Nick?
Ah, it's only Hector.
Well?
Is it...cool?
Wow, man. Well done, you look great.
I would like a shirt, please.
Excellent. Oh, the clothes are super.
And a pair of trousers.
Oh. You are clever, Hector.
And a pair of shoes, please.
I have been shopping!
Oh, I'll get it.
Hello?
-  It's me.
-  Oh, hello.
It's the tarantula.
How are you?
-  Fine, thank you.
-  Oh, good, good.
-  How's your cold?
-  How's my cold?
-  Well, how do you know I have a cold?
-  You told me this morning.
Me.
-  I am Bridget.
-  I don't believe you.
Yes. I have a cold.
-  Thank you.
-  Oh, I'm sorry.
Yes. Silly me.
I told you this morning.
Why are 400 tins of dog food here for Annie?
Pardon?
I don't know.
-  How strange.
-  400 tins!
Yes, that's a lot of tins. I really don't know.
-  Can you ask Annie?
-  Yes, I'll ask Annie.
Goodbye.
The tarantula said
why are 400 tins of dog food downstairs?
400 tins?
Hector...
Next time in Extra...
Annie goes dating on the Internet,
and so do Nick and Hector.
But do they like their dates?
This is the story of Bridget and Annie,
who share a flat in London,
and the boys next door,
Nick and his friend Hector from Argentina.
Hector and Annie were in love,
but now things are not so good.
Bridget has given up on love,
And Nick -  well, his mum loves him!
Stand by for Extra!
Hector.
-  Yes?
-  Please could you pass the salt?
Yes.
Hector.
Yes?
Please could you pass the pepper?
Of course.
Hector.
Let me guess.
Can I pass the sugar, coffee, tea?
Actually, I was going to say we should talk.
So, now you want to talk to me!
It's only been a week!
-  I was hurt!
-  Well, you hurt me too.
-  I didn't go out with Eunice!
Yes, you did! And you stayed out
till three o'clock in the morning!
There were other people there, too.
-  Who?
-  People who work on the programme.
You mean other women
who work on the programme.
Yes, and men -  why not, huh?
I knew it!
So, who is she?
-  Who?
-  The other woman.
There is no other woman!
Huh!
Annie, listen.
Excuse me.
Hello. Hi, Debbie.
How are you? Good.
OK, that'll be OK. Perfect! See you then.
Bye.
So, was that her?
-  Who?
-  Debbie. The other woman!
That was Debbie from the make- up department,
confirming my call time for tomorrow.
Some excuse!
-  Hector.
-  Yes.
Please could you pass me your fork?
Here, I'm going.
You can have my dinner!
You should have seen Eunice's face!
She was furious!
When Eunice gets angry,
she is a very scary lady!
Hello.
Yes.
Excuse me. No, no, to her...
Bye, Bridget.
All right, Hector. Bye.
Hola, Lola!
-  Guess what?
-  Prince William wants to marry you?
I know that! No, I've got a promotion!
That's nice.
Nice? Nice!
It's fantastic! I am editor of Channel 9 Live!
Eunice is no longer my boss!
Is that Hugh Grant?
It's Bridget Evans here.
Call me Gigi, editor of Channel 9 Live.
Are we still on for lunch at Claridge's today?
Fab! Ciao!
Eunice is so jealous!
Now, that is good news.
Annie, what are you doing?
I'm doing my own editing.
Why are you cutting up
photos of you and Hector?
Because Hector is no longer my boyfriend.
Really?
Why?
Because he is having an affair!
Really?! Who with?
Well, I thought it was Eunice,
but now I think it's Debbie.
Well, I just heard him on the phone to Lola.
Lola? Who's she?
Ha! Eunice, Debbie, Lola!
He's women mad!
It's fantastic!
I am editor of Channel 9 Live!
Hola, Lola!
I didn't go out with Eunice!
Yes, you did! And you stayed out
till three o'clock in the morning!
So, was that her?
-  Who?
-  Debbie. The other woman!
Hi, Nick.
What are you doing?
I am not doing, I am being.
What are you being?
-  Can't you guess?
-  A man on the toilet?
A Sumo wrestler?
Can't you see? I am an egg.
Of course, you are an egg.
Now, what sort of egg am I?
Hard- boiled.
-  Scrambled.
-  Scrambled?
-  Fried.
-  Nearly!
Poached!
Yeah, of course. You are a poached egg.
Yeah.
Well, you're making a mess on your bed!
Anyway, why are you being a poached egg?
It's my new acting class.
Total Being.
What are you next week? A piece of wood?
-  A piece of wood?
-  Yeah! Then it would be wooden acting!
Anyway, can poached eggs talk?
Don't be silly! Of course poached eggs can't talk.
No, no, I mean,
when you are
'being' a poached egg, can you talk?
Yeah.
Anyway, I want to stop now,
my arms are hurting.
So, what do you want to talk about?
It is Annie.
She thinks I am having an affair.
-  Who with?
-  Eunice.
-  And Debbie.
-  What?
Two women, Hector!
You cheeky thing!
But I am not!
-  So tell Annie then.
-  I have but she doesn't believe me.
-  Why not?
-  I don't know.
Excuse me.
Hola, Lola.
I'll take this outside.
How are you, Lola?
So, it's not Eunice,
it's not Debbie, could it be - Lola?
Stop, please!
I knew it!
It had to be a selfish man- driver!
Please, I have a voucher.
I- I am sorry, I've started, so I'll finish.
Look, I am Zeus, why are you so angry?
I'm not. I am just doing my job - Zeus!
People park on yellow lines and then are
surprised when they get a parking ticket!
There was this one guy today -
'Please, I have a voucher.'
No excuse!
Mind you, he was quite cute.
Nick.
Nick, are you OK?
Bridget! Oh, it's you, Hector.
Well, there's something wrong with Nick.
-  Well, I could have told you that!
-  No, he won't speak, he won't move.
I know. He is being a poached egg.
-  A what?
-  For his new acting class.
Hi, Nick.
Let me guess.
You are being - a potato.
Do I look like a potato?
Yes. A couch potato!
What about a fish?
Yes, a frozen fish!
I am not a fish.
I...am...'Pain'.
You are a pain.
Yes, Nick is a pain!
No! I am 'Pain'.
Hurt, agony.
So, how was your first day as editor, Bridget?
What a day!
I had a very important meeting.
Big decisions to make.
Like which celebrities,
new programme ideas?
No, like which pen to use at my meeting?
Blue, black...
-  Which one did you choose?
-  Blue.
Bad choice.
You think so? Oh, no!
Eunice is so jealous of Bridget's new job,
she won't talk to anyone!
-  Not even you?
-  Not even me! It is great!
You don't want her to talk to you?
-  Really?
-  Really!
Oh, Annie, I hate it when we argue.
So do I.
-  I miss you.
-  I miss...
Hola, Lola.
Right. Two can play that game.
I am not doing, I am being.
A man on the toilet?
Yeah!
I am not a fish! I...am...'Pain'.
It's not Eunice,
it's not Debbie, could it be -  Lola?
Hola, Lola!
Look, I am Zeus. Why are you so angry?
I am just doing my job - Zeus!
-  Hello again.
-  Hello.
-  We meet again.
-  You're happier today.
Yes, I am now!
But I'm sorry...
I parked here, so you would come back.
You wanted to see me again?
You are so beautiful!
Well, I'm sorry
but I am going to have to give you...
-  No...
-  This!
My phone number.
Call me.
Who needs Hector?
Hi, Bridget.
What 'oh'?
I know -  Superman!
-  What?
-  I mean, Clark Kent.
You are being Clark Kent, for your acting class.
No. I'm not.
I'm long- sighted.
You're being long- sighted?
No.
I am long- sighted.
I need to wear glasses for reading.
They suit you.
Thank you.
So, why are you not at Channel 9 today?
I'm working from home today.
I've so much to do!
Bridget, what's the matter?
I can't do it! Eunice hates me!
Eunice hates everybody!
-  They all hate me!
-  No, they don't!
-  They all look at me!
-  Bridget, you are their boss.
I have to use the executive loo!
What's the matter with that?
I want to chat to all the girls!
Bridget...
you are one of the cleverest,
most beautiful women I know.
Really?
-  Well, who are the others?
-  What do you mean?
You said I was only one of the cleverest,
most beautiful girls you know.
Bridget! You can do this job.
Channel 9 needs you.
-  Thank you, Nick.
-  Hey, it was nothing.
You really look handsome in those glasses.
Hi, Annie.
Hi, Hector.
-  You look smart.
-  Yes, I am going to meet someone.
Annie, I have something to tell you.
Sorry.
Lola!
Vale. Si, si, ya voy.
Hasta luego.
'Annie, I have something to tell you.'
That he is going on a date with Lola!
That's what!
Nick, stop it! You're tickling me!
Hi, Annie. I didn't hear you come in.
Nick! Stop it!
Is everybody happy, apart from me?
Hello.
Zeus! Hi!
Well, of course I remember you!
A drink? Tonight?
Well, I'd love to.
Stop it! You're tickling me!
Zeus, meet my friends, Bridget and Nick.
-  Hi.
Well, hello, Zeus!
Annie, where did you find him?
Yeah, but he doesn't wear glasses,
though, does he?
We've had a lovely evening, haven't we, Zeus?
Wonderful, Annie.
Now I must say goodnight.
Please, first may I use your bathroom?
-  Certainly.
-  Thank you.
Zeus is such a gentle man.
He certainly is a man.
Hi.
Annie, I must talk to you.
What about? Your date with Lola?
My date with Lola?
Annie, Lola is a 60- year- old
chief executive for ATV.
-  What's ATV?
-  Argentinian Television.
And...
She wants me to return to Argentina
to present their number one show.
But I don't want to go.
I want to stay here - with you.
That's better.
Hector, this is...
Zeus, my new boyfriend.
We've had a lovely evening, haven't we!
Come on, I'll say goodbye to you downstairs!
So, Hector, will you take the job?
What do you think I should do, Annie?
So we must say goodbye
to our friends for now.
Will Hector stay, or go back to Argentina?
Will Annie go with him?
And will Nick ever give up on Bridget?
Extra - will the story continue?!
This is the story of Bridget and Annie,
who share a flat in London,
and the boys next door,
Nick and his friend Hector from Argentina.
Hector works for Channel 9.
Annie is getting jealous.
Bridget has seen it all before.
And Nick just wants to have fun.
Stand by for Extra.
Hello, Nick. Have you lost a button?
Hi, Bridget.
I'm just...
practising.
Practising what?
I am going to join the SAS.
The Special Air Service?
-  Yeah.
-  You?
What's so funny?
Nick, the SAS is for tough guys,
real men who are fit.
They're highly trained.
I was in the Scouts.
You...
were in the Scouts?
Annie.
Nick's going to join the SAS.
That's wonderful, Nick.
Don't you need special training?
It's OK, he was in the Scouts.
Hello.
Here in the National Camping Exhibition...
There's Hector.
..it is all tents, tents, tents.
In every shape, size and colour.
And Eunice.
-  And we will be showing you the best...
-  And the worst of camping.
So, stick around.
Back to studio.
Shall we go and try out some sleeping bags
now, Hector?
Shall we go and try out some sleeping bags,
Hector?
Calm down, Annie, it's only a television report.
I know but, well,
he's been working with Eunice a lot recently.
And?
And, well, I'm just worried that he...
well, that she...
You know.
Annie, don't be silly.
You've got nothing to worry about.
Although...
Hector is a good- looking man.
Yep, and she's a good- looking woman.
Incoming, Broad Sword calling Danny Boy,
Broad Sword calling Danny Boy...
I was watching that.
Not any more. Go on, it's late.
Back to your own tent.
What's so funny?
You.
A Scout.
Yeah, so?
I can just imagine.
Trying to light fires.
Jessop, you cheat.
Helping old ladies across the road.
Tying knots.
-  What was that?
-  I didn't hear anything.
Hello, Hector.
Good evening, Annie.
Don't you mean 'good morning'?
Where have you been?
You know, for a couple of beers.
Who with?
With the lads.
So when did the lads start wearing
ladies' perfume?
I forgot, Eunice was there too.
So what did you talk about?
Tents.
Tents?
You talked about tents all night?
Where? In her tent?
Or yours?
Annie. Annie...
I am going to join the SAS.
I was in the Scouts.
Shall we go and try out some sleeping bags
now, Hector?
Where have you been?
When did the lads start wearing
ladies' perfume?
Yes! I've got it!
It was my turn for the toy.
No, you've got the Incredible Hulk.
So I get two turns.
-  Hey, Nick.
-  Yeah?
What do you think of Eunice?
Well, she isn't an English rose.
No, I don't think she is a flower.
No, it's a saying.
An English rose -  a sweet, pretty girl.
-  Like Annie.
-  No.
Eunice is not a sweet, pretty girl.
No. Eunice is more...
What is that plant that grows all over walls
in England?
Honeysuckle.
Wallflower.
-  Ivy?
-  Yeah, ivy.
Eunice is more like English ivy.
-  What do you mean?
-  Well, she...
Likes dancing?
No, she...
She's all over you?
Do you like it?
I see trouble ahead.
What's so funny?
Come on.
Share the joke.
It's Hector.
Hector came home late last night, is that it?
He was out with Eunice.
Don't worry about Eunice.
She likes flirting, that's all.
This will cheer you up.
Look what I found.
It's pictures of us when we were Brownies.
-  And you're wearing the Brownie uniform.
-  It still fits.
Look at all your badges.
What was the Brownie law?
A Brownie Guide thinks of others
before herself...
And does a good turn every day.
Remember the Brownie law, Annie.
OK.
Hello, Hector. How are you?
Fine.
Did you have a good night's sleep?
What was left of it.
Dib- dib, dob- dob.
What's all this, then?
It is the Brownie salute.
That's not a salute.
This is a salute.
-  What do you think, Hector?
-  Well, both salutes are nice.
-  Brownies.
-  Or Scouts.
-  Scouts.
What are you talking about?
What are Brownies? Biscuits?
When Bridget and I were little girls,
we were Brownies.
We went camping, we sang songs.
We were given badges for good work.
Brownies are for girls.
In the Scouts we survived.
It was just like being in the SAS, wasn't it, Nick?
Yeah.
So what are all those badges for?
This one is for first aid.
And what is second aid or third aid?
First aid is for helping people who are hurt.
How hurt?
Like if they can't breathe.
Shall I demonstrate, Bridget?
Go ahead, Annie.
Lie down, please, Hector.
Now, this is called the kiss of life.
Sounds good.
It means I breathe into your mouth.
And if you still can't breathe, I do this.
Well, that is...
And I keep doing this until you can breathe.
Are you breathing yet?
Yes, yes, yes, I can breathe.
And that is my good turn for the day.
Now, Nick,
bites and stings.
No, thanks.
Of course, when I was in the Scouts,
I went camping.
So did we.
Ah, but this was proper camping, survival.
What? Like the SAS?
We had to live off the land.
What? No tins of baked beans?
No.
So could you do a survival test?
Yeah, no problem.
Yeah.
Right, then.
We will give you a survival test.
Great.
What is a survival test?
You'll see.
Just be prepared.
Ready for your survival test, boys?
-  Certainly am.
-  OK. Test number one.
The jungle is full of horrible things
that creep and crawl.
And some that wriggle everywhere.
Especially...
worms!
OK.
Test number two.
Food.
You have run out of food,
so you have to eat whatever you can find.
Open very wide, please.
Ready?
Beetles!
OK.
Test number three.
Pain.
I haven't touched you yet.
I'm sorry, boys,
you have failed the survival test.
But in the jungle
it is going to be different.
Yeah, we were just pretending.
It wasn't real.
What? Like real camping?
-  Why don't we do it?
-  Do what?
-  Let's go camping.
-  We haven't got a tent.
Well, Hector can get us a tent
from the National Camping Exhibition.
Well, isn't tomorrow
the last day of the exhibition?
Yeah.
And you and Eunice will be doing another report.
Well, then, you can buy a tent
and come home early.
You'll miss your drinks after work.
Shame.
What do you think of Eunice?
I see trouble ahead.
Lie down, please, Hector.
That's not a salute.
This is a salute.
Ready for your survival test, boys?
Certainly am.
Worms.
Beetles!
Let's go camping.
In the jungle it is going to be different.
You will wake Annie.
Hey, I have an idea.
I must show you to Annie.
You know, I have a better idea.
Come, come.
Come. You too, come, come.
Nick.
Nick, wake up.
No more beetles!
-  Hector.
-  Nick.
-  What's going on?
-  I've got it.
-  Got what?
-  The tent.
That's nice.
-  Come on, let's put it up.
-  What?
The tent.
Hector.
-  Have you seen the time?
-  No.
It's three o'clock in the morning!
-  Is it?
-  Yeah.
Really?
Wait a minute.
Where have you been?
For a couple of beers.
And a dance.
What's that on your collar?
Paint.
Pink paint. That's nice.
When Annie wakes up,
she is going to be cross with me.
If she sees that on your collar, she will be.
Have you been dancing with Eunice?
Yes.
You are dead.
But...when Annie sees that I bought the tent...
she is going to forgive me.
At three o'clock in the morning?
Late- night shopping.
It is OK, Charley, it is me, Hector.
Where shall we put it?
Here.
In the middle.
Guy ropes.
What?
-  Guy Ropes, who is he?
-  No.
Guy ropes.
Ropes called guy ropes.
Somewhere here.
-  Look.
-  That's them.
Tie them to the furniture.
There. That is it.
Right, let's go to bed.
What? What's this?
Who put that there?
Hi, Annie. I've bought you a tent.
What is going on?
Well, do you like your tent?
Anyone for camping?
It's so cold.
I'll warm you up.
Did somebody say something?
I want a hot drink.
We can't even make a fire.
And there's no water left.
How long have we been here?
It feels like ages.
It's so creepy.
Yeah. Very creepy.
Are you tired, Hector?
Did you have another late night with Eunice?
So who's going to go outside
and get us some water?
Well, I won't.
Well, I won't either.
All right, I'll go,
but if I'm not back in ten minutes,
you can have my Action Man collection.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Off you go.
Morning, Nick, dear.
Thought you and your friends
would like a nice cup of tea.
Thanks, Mum.
Thanks, Mrs Jessop.
Next time in Extra...
Bridget gets a new job.
Hector receives a phone call from Lola.
And Annie is looking for trouble.
It's not Eunice. It's not Debbie.
Could it be Lola?
This is the story of Bridget and Annie,
who share a flat in London,
and the boys next door, Nick,
and his friend Hector fro Argentina.
Hector and Annie are in love.
Bridget likes to party and party.
And Nick will do anything
to earn some money.
Stand by for Extra.
I love this time of year.
Sleigh bells, mince pies,
presents under the tree!
What? Easter?
No, silly! Christmas!
I'm going to show you what
a traditional English Christmas is like.
Starting with...mistletoe.
Mistle-toe?
It's an English tradition.
When you stand under it,
you can kiss someone.
But I am not under any mistletoe.
You are now.
Oh, you poor things!
You're stuck together again.
Don't worry, I can help!
There, panic over!
- Right, I'm off.
- What?
Another television party?
Not a party, three more parties.
And that's just tonight.
But you've been to a Christmas
party every night for two weeks.
I know.
It's so difficult being so popular.
First, there's a champagne party
at the Savoy,
then at nine o'clock
I'll get a taxi to the Ritz
and get changed on the way...
What? In the taxi?
Naturally.
And then at 1 1 :30
I'll get a taxi to Annabel's.
Annabel - who is she?
Annabel's - the night club.
Will you change your clothes
in the taxi again?
And there I hope
I Will meet a young, handsome man.
An early Christmas present!
I hate Christmas!
Did you have a bad day
at the grotto, dear?
- Nick, is that snow?
- No.
Well, what,s that on your beard then?
I was holding this baby...
when suddenly...
- Christmas!
- But children Love Christmas.
- Is the money good?
- Yeah.
Well, stop complaining then!
Hector and I are going to have
a lovely Christmas, aren't we?
Christmas is all about
parties and presents!
So, Bridget, have you got your
Christmas stocking ready?
She's taking her stockings off
in the taxi!
Don't wait up.
What is a Christmas stocking?
On Christmas Eve,
you hang up your Christmas stocking
and a big, Jolly Father Christmas comes
and fills it up with presents!
Who put that sleigh there?
My sleigh! I forgot!
Mind my leq.
Right, right...
Whoa! Not too fast!
I feel terrible!
- Poor Bridget. Are you in pain?
- No.
But what about the parties?
I can,t go like this!
I could take you dancing!
Christmas is cancelled!
- Is that it?
- Yeah, crackers are great!
So, what else
do you have at Christmas?
Turkey, Christmas pudding, mince pies.
Mince pies. How do you make them?
It's just pastry and mincemeat.
- Mincemeat?
- Yeah, it's traditional
It's sultanas, raisins and spices.
It's mince...
- Meat.
- Yeah.
Listen to this.
What do you get
if you cross a chicken with a clock?
- I don't know.
- An alarm cluck!
An alarm cluck!
I don't get it.
One a cluck, two a cluck...
A clock?
Mistle-toe?
It's an English tradition.
When you stand under it,
you can kiss someone.
I was holding this baby...
when suddenly...
It's so difficult being so popular.
My sleigh! I forgot!
Mince pies!
First, the pastry!
And now the minced meat
from the best butcher!
They smell good, don't they, Charley?
Well, I've finished
all my Christmas shopping.
Oh, madam!
Refreshment? Mince pie?
Mince pies? Hector, you are clever.
I followed the re-ceep.
- Pee.
- Mince pee?
No, no, no. Re-ci-pe.
Re-ci-pe.
Good choice, madam. Merry Christmas!
Something wrong?
Delicious...Delicious.
You know, Hector,
Christmas is all about sharing.
Would you like some, Charley?
It's Saint Nicholas!
What happened to your beard?
One Christmas candle,
one small child...
Mince pies, yummy!
With best mince from the best butcher.
Hector. What did you put in the pies?
Minced meat - from the best butcher.
This is mincemeat.
This is minced meat.
Isn't it the same thing?
- Not quite.
- Delicious!
I've got an idea!
Let's make this a special Christmas,
just for Bridget.
Night-night.
Hey, Bridget.
- Do you want to come carol singing?
- Who is Carol?
Carols are Christmas songs.
You knock on people's doors
and sing to them for money.
- Let's do it!
- For charity!
For poor little children.
Some children have no Christmas.
Just like me.
And your job as Santa Claus
is so important.
You help children
to believe in Christmas!
Yes, you're right, Annie, I do.
My job is important!
I help children to believe!
Right, let's go!
I'll go, only if we can sing Abba songs.
And that Will make you happy?
Here, have a mince pie.
All right.
Away in a manger...
Dog in a manger more like! Good night!
Silent night...
I wish you were - all night!
We Three Kings of Orient are
One on a scooter, one in a car...
Get Iost!
Merrlly on high...
Get 'em, Gnasher!
Come all ye faithful
Joyful and tri...
Hi, Annie. I like the tree.
Thank you. It's nearly finished.
Please, use these. My decorations.
Oh, sweet, Hector.
- Are they from Argentina?
- No.
Oxford Street.
- Aren't they great?
- Great.
Hi, Nick.
How was your Iast day as Santa Claus?
Great! Such nice children.
One of them
let me play with his binoculars!
Really?
And I've just finished
my Christmas shopping.
- But the shops are shut now.
- No.
The petrol station was open.
Look I've bought my mum this.
A map of Watford.
- But your mum doesn't live in Watford.
- I know.
She might go there one day, though.
I bought shampoo for my sister.
Car shampoo.
Yeah. And aftershave for my dad.
I like the tree...but I Love these!
I've got some too.
It was the Iast day of the grotto today,
so they were throwing these away.
Can you believe it!
No!
Perfect.
Well, it might make Bridget Iaugh.
Why?
I know. If Bridget can't go to her parties,
let's have a party here!
- When?
- Oh, I don't know.
In about 15 minutes?
Look at the Christmas tree!
I know. It makes me want to cry too.
What's the point of having Christmas
if I can't go to my Christmas parties?!
Now Christmas just makes me cry!
Bridget, cheer up.
Tomorrow is Christmas Day.
Have you got your stocking?
Yes.
And I've got mine!
What are you hoping for? A motorbike?
Yes! Why not?
The only thing
that Will make this Christmas worse
is if you invited all my friends round
for a surprise party to cheer me up.
Surprise!
And now the minced meat,
from the best butcher!
They smell good, don't they, Charley?
We Three Kings of Orient are
One on a scooter, one in a car...
Good night!
Joyful and tri...
Surprise!
Hang on, I,m coming!
- Merry Christmas!
- Hello, Bernard. Merry Christmas.
I'm sorry,
we had a little party Iast night.
I'm here for dinner.
Isn't it a bit early?
Ten o'clock, time for a sherry.
- Bernard, where's your mother?
- At church.
Well, I'll just go and get dressed.
To Bernard, Love from Annie.
Sherry. Thanks, Annie.
Nearly finished this one.
To Bridget, Love from Annie.
A flea collar? I haven,t got fleas!
I'm sorry, Bridget, wrong label.
It was meant for Charley.
Is she sure it was meant for Charley?
To Bridget, from Hector.
Thank you, Hector. You shouldn't have.
What To Wear At Christmas Parties.
I bought it before you...
I've got a little something for you, Nick.
Gorilla -
because you are the original man.
It smells like a gorilla.
Well, you should know.
I wonder what this could be.
Merry Christmas, sugar plum.
Merry Christmas, snuggly-puppykins.
One heart, forever.
This Will stop it!
Bridget, nothing Will stop
my Love for Hector.
Well...
I just called to say Merry Christmas!
Hector.
Bridget, what has happened to you?
- I had an accident.
- Oh, what a pity!
You've missed some fabulous parties -
especially at the Beckhams'.
Elton John is a very naughty boy!
Still, never mind,
there is always next year.
OK, must dash.
Off to a top restaurant for lunch.
- Eunice?
- Yes?
Before you go, have a mince pie. Nick?
I shouldn't...but it's Christmas.
It's true, there is a Santa!
And she's a woman! Wait for me!
I want to tell you
what I really want for Christmas!
- Can you smell something?
- Yeah.
Is something burning?
I forgot - the turkey!
Water, water! We need water!
Not on me! On the turkey!
Move! Move!
There. The fire is out.
Anyone for turkey?!
Shall we just have pudding?
No mince pies, thanks.
I have another surprise for you.
Another English Christmas tradition.
Chocolate log. One slice or two?
Next time in Extra...
Nick wants to join the SAS,
Bridget and Annie
train the boys for action
and why is Hector home so late?
Hello, Hector!
This is the story of Bridget and Annie,
who share a flat in London,
and the boys next door,
Nick and his friend Hector from Argentina.
Hector and Annie love each other.
Nick loves babes and motorbikes
and Bridget loves make- up,
mirrors and chocolate.
Stand by for Extra.
It's time for Can You Live Without...?
And here's someone
you just can't live without.
It's Marty!
But what Sharon doesn't realise
is we've got a camera in the bathroom.
That's disgusting.
She must know that we can see her.
I think it is quite clever.
And what are Paul and Mandy doing
in the living room?
They're kissing. They're kissing.
They're not kissing. They're whispering.
What? Do you call this whispering?
Let's think of another name for it.
Paul and Mandy said they could live
without kissing for 24 hours.
And look, they've failed.
Paul and Mandy lose points for that.
We caught them kissing.
See you after the break.
Can You Live Without...?
is sponsored by Clouds Toilet Tissue.
Well, I couldn't live
without kissing Hector for 24 hours.
Why don't you try?
Hector, I wish you'd stop chewing gum.
-  I'm not chewing.
-  Yes, you are. You're always chewing.
No...
I bet you couldn't stop
chewing gum for 24 hours.
Well, yes, I could.
And, anyway, you suck your thumb.
I do not.
Well, only when I'm stressed.
-  I've had an idea!
-  Oh, no!
We could be contestants
on Can You Live Without...?
We could do it. It's just 24 hours
of giving up our favourite things.
It would be easy.
Think of the prize money.
And Marty Ross presents it.
He would come to my apartment again.
-  Oh, no!
-  Oh, Marty.
He's got such good taste.
And this is fantastic. Original.
What happened to Marty?
He said he needed time away from me
to really appreciate me.
-  So he dumped you, then.
-  He did not!
Anyway, Bridget,
are you feeling persuasive?
Of course.
I'm always feeling persuasive.
Well, it's time to persuade Marty
that we want to go on
Can You Live Without...?
And then Marty can make it happen.
I'll try.
Mr Ross to Studio B, please.
-  Hello, Marty.
-  Hello...
-  Bridget!
-  Bridget?
Bridget, Eunice's researcher.
We had dinner last month.
That Bridget. What do you want?
I've got something to say.
Well, I'm not the father.
-  No! Nothing like that.
-  Well, what is it, then?
My friends and I want to be contestants
on Can You Live Without...?
I wish I could help you, but it's not
my decision, it's the producer's.
Now, I must go.
-  You can't help me? That's a shame.
-  Yes, it is.
Because I'd hate for the newspapers
to see this.
Or this.
Where did you get them?
Don't you remember?
I'm Eunice's researcher.
I research.
I wish I could help you,
but it's not my decision,
it's the newspapers'.
All right, all right.
I'll see what I can do.
It's time to persuade Marty
that we want to go on
Can You Live Without...?
Hector, I wish you'd stop chewing gum.
Because I'd hate for the newspapers
to see this.
Or this.
We could do it. It's just 24 hours
of giving up our favourite things.
It's time for Can You Live Without...?
And here's someone
you just can't live without.
It's Marty!
Hello, darlings.
Do you want to spend
the next 24 hours with me?
-  Yeah!
-  Correct answer!
Yes, let's see what the people
who live here...can live without.
But it looks like
they live without anything anyway.
Well, let's meet the contestants.
You first, pretty lady. What's your name?
You already know my name, Marty.
We have a pretty joker here.
Don't get smart, sweetie.
This is my show, photo or no photo.
-  Bridget.
-  Good luck, Bridget.
-  And who do we have here?
-  Hello.
My name is Annie
and I'm Hector's girlfriend...
and I love Charley, my dog.
So, which one could you live without?
Enough said!
And this is Hector.
So, Hector,
Annie loves her dog more than you.
Mind you, Hector does sound
like a dog's name, doesn't it?
Here, Hector! Here, boy!
Don't bite!
And, last of all and least of all...
it's...
Hello? Is anybody there?
I know, you're a fish.
Hi. I'm Nick.
Hi, Nick. And what do you like?
Bananas!
Baboons. You like baboons!
You are a baboon.
You're a small baboon.
No, it's not baboons.
You like babes!
Sorry, this is Nick and he likes babes.
Well, let's get on with it.
As usual, each of these contestants
has picked one thing
that their flatmates
cannot live without for 24 hours.
Bridget...
You must live without chocolate...
mirrors...and make- up.
Annie, you must live without...
touching Hector, sucking your thumb...
and, most of all,
you must live without Charley.
Hector, you must live without...
touching Annie and chewing gum.
Nick, you must live without...
talking about babes
or talking about motorbikes.
And all of you must live without
television, magazines and music.
24 hours of living without starts now.
Come on, Charley.
You're coming with me.
Don't forget -  I'll be watching.
No television!
No touching.
If you touch, we lose points
and we won't win a big prize.
No make- up. What must I look like?
And no mirrors!
Look at that guy.
He looks like a monkey at the zoo.
So how will they do? Top points
could mean a holiday in the Caribbean.
But if they fail, they lose points
and their prize holiday could be this.
Of course, we might give them one or two
temptations to make interesting television.
Join me after the break.
You must live without touching Hector.
Nick, you must live
without talking about babes
or talking about motorbikes.
24 hours of living without starts now.
I think it's going to rain.
-  Do you?
-  I agree.
Manchester United are doing well.
-  Are they?
-  I agree.
I think it's going to rain.
Weather and football -
is that all you can talk about?
Well, yesterday I met this really cute b...
Don't say it! Do not talk
about babes or motorbikes.
Careful!
Bridget, no mirrors. You lose ten points.
But it's not a mirror, it's a kettle.
Don't argue!
You lose another ten points.
Well, it's all quiet now.
What about some temptation?
Hector, what is in your mouth?
Nothing.
-  Are you chewing gum, Hector?
-  No.
No, he's not. He's chewing this.
Open.
That was from the Red Sea.
It cost a lot of money.
I could kill for some chocolate.
This should be fun!
'Bridget.
'I love the show, love from...
'Orlando Bloom.'
Orlando Bloom...watching me!
I hope you didn't hear me say that.
What do I look like?
What are you doing, Annie?
I'm talking to Charley.
Annie, you must live without Charley.
You lose ten points.
What?
Hector...
- Don't move!
-  What is it?
It's OK, just don't move.
I'm not going anywhere.
What Hector doesn't know is that
we've put that spider on his jumper.
This is wonderful TV
Think, think!
One minute.
That's better.
Now, we'll just
brush this little fellow off.
Don't touch it!
It's OK.
I'm sure it's not poisonous.
How do you know?
Anyway, if you touch me,
we will lose points.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
OK.
Now...stay still.
Don't move!
Hang on a minute!
Hector, this is a toy.
I knew that.
Hector, you were so funny.
Marty has played a trick on us.
Yeah, very funny.
Who's a cross boy?
Things are getting really hot now
and they've still got over 12 hours to go.
You know, Hector,
I really think we can do this.
We can win that holiday.
Hello, Annie.
Bridget, what are you doing in there?
I'm...just reading the electricity meter.
Come here.
Why are you wearing dark glasses?
I don't want Orlando to see me
without make- up.
Bridget! Is that chocolate?
No.
But they're from Orlando!
No chocolate, Bridget.
You lose 100 points.
Nick has entered the building!
Nick!
Yes! Annie and Hector touched.
They lose 200 points.
-  What?
-  It was an accident.
And best of all, Nick,
you can't live without motorbikes.
So you lose 500 points.
No, no, no, no!
You said no talking about motorbikes,
actually, big nose!
Yeah, Marty.
So thanks for the present.
You can keep your holiday.
What? You can't do that.
Baby, fancy a ride?
Yeah!
Hector, this is for Marty.
Or should I say...Martina?
So, Marty, if you want the bike,
come and get it.
Sorry, Marty, we can live without you.
Goodbye.
And, Marty, I think your audience
will love this picture of you.
Oh, no!
Come on, Annie.
We have lots of catching up to do.
Hector, catch me!
Next time in Extra...
Nick plays Santa while Hector
and Annie play under the mistletoe.
and Annie plays under the mistletoe.
This is the story of Bridget and Annie,
who share a flat in London,
and the boys next door,
Nick and his friend Hector from Argentina.
Annie cares about animals.
Hector cares about Annie.
Bridget mostly cares about herself.
But Nick doesn't care very much about anything.
Stand by for Extra.
Bridget Evans?
Annie Taylor?
Detective David Hunt
of the Metropolitan Police.
Could I have a word with you, please?
So we went to the restaurant
and it was a very good vegetarian restaurant,
and I had the peppers
and Hector had the mushrooms,
which was very nice
because Hector doesn't like mushrooms,
so I said to him that it was good for him to try.
Annie!
And then afterwards we went for a lovely walk
and it was such a beautiful evening
and the birds were singing...
Annie! Will you shut up?
Sorry.
You have been talking non- stop
for 20 minutes.
I know. It's...
It's because I'm doing a sponsored silence
for the charity Pigs With No Parents.
Sponsored...silence!
So why are you talking?
It doesn't start till ten o'clock, so if I talk
a lot now, then I won't have to talk later.
Anyway, what's wrong with your mouth?
Nothing.
Have you got a spot?
I'll call an ambulance!
No, but I am going to see my beautician later.
What for?
Just for a check- up.
A check- up? But you go to the dentist
for a check- up, for your teeth.
Exactly.
I'm going to the beautician's to check...
Check that you are beautiful?
Of course not.
I don't have to check I'm beautiful, do I?
Hey, Nick! Do you like my new clothes?
Nick!
Nick! What is the matter?
You can tell me.
You have a toothache.
Then if you have a toothache,
you must go to the den...
Can't I say the word 'den...'?
OK, I won't say the D- word.
I call him 'plumber'.
OK, so when did you last see the plumber?
That's not too bad, five months ago.
Five years ago?
When you were five years old?
It is going to be a big job!
He'll need a big drill.
Come on.
The girls must know a good plumber.
Do you want a sweetie?
Sweets are bad for your teeth. Come on.
Hi, sugar plum.
Hello, snuggly puppykins.
Nice clothes. New?
Yeah. Thanks.
Is Nick rehearsing for the pantomime?
No, he has a toothache
so he must see the plumber.
No, no, no, Hector.
For a toothache, he must see the dentist.
I know that, but Nick doesn't like the D- word.
'Dentist'.
So I'm calling the dentist a plumber.
So do you know a good plumber?
A plumber? What for?
Nick has toothache.
Well, he doesn't need a plumber.
He needs a dentist.
Yes, Hector, we have
the number of a very good plumber -  Julian.
Julian!
He's so gentle.
He's so married!
Hi, Julian.
Listen, we have an emergency here.
What are the symptoms?
Shaking, squealing...
Yeah, just a toothache.
You can?
Thank you. Bye.
Sorted. He'll see Nick now.
OK, come on, Nick.
Come on. Come on, Nick.
Come on...
Come on, Nick.
Julian looked in my mouth once.
He said, 'Bridget, you've got wonderful teeth.'
With a mouth that big,
I'm surprised he didn't fall in.
Hello.
Who's this?
Bernard?
Hello, Bernard.
You've been what?
Robbed?
When?
When you were in the bath?
All your clothes?
And your keys?
Poor Bernard.
Listen, you must call the police, OK?
OK. Bye.
Poor Bernard.
It's ten o'clock!
My sponsored silence starts now.
He'll need a big drill.
If I talk a lot now,
then I won't have to talk later.
Have you got a spot?
I'll call an ambulance!
All your clothes?
And your keys?
Bridget Evans?
Annie Taylor?
Detective David Hunt
of the Metropolitan Police.
Could I have a word with you, please?
Why not?
You can't speak? I'm sorry.
You can speak.
Are you trying to be funny with me, young lady?
One word. Three syllables.
First syllable...
Sit.
Seat?
Chair?
Second syllable.
A? E?
I? I.
T.
Chair- I- T.
Chair- I- T?
You're being silent for charity!
But which charity?
Cow? Dog? Cat?
Pig?
Got it! Pigs Without Parents!
Is this man bothering you, Annie?
Because if he is,
I am going to show him some Argentinian...
Detective David Hunt
of the Metropolitan Police.
..respect.
-  And you are?
-  Hector Romero.
I suspect you're not English?
He is a very good detective.
And you are?
Nwiff?
He's just been to see the plumber.
-  The plumber?
-  Yes, he had a toothache.
But you don't go to the plumber
when you've got a toothache.
-  You go to the den...
-  Biscuit?
Dentist.
Anyway, I'm here to investigate a robbery
of Bernard Reynolds'...
Somebody has stolen Bernard!
There's been a robbery
of Bernard Reynolds' clothes.
Who would want Bernard's clothes?
So I'm investigating everybody in the building
because someone
has stolen Bernard Reynolds' clothes.
Where were you last night?
I was with Annie.
-  Annie...
-  It's OK.
She can't speak for chair- I- T.
Anyway, what about Nwiff?
I...
Show me, Nick.
I went to Leo's Bar.
I had a beer.
There was a beautiful girl.
And a motorbike?
You were with a young woman on a motorbike?
Motorbike. Registration?
Name of young woman?
He wasn't with her.
The young woman
was on television on a motorbike!
I saw that! Very nice!
Gee, I'm getting good at this.
Bridget Evans?
Annie Taylor?
Detective David Hunt
of the Metropolitan Police.
Could I have a word with you, please?
Chair- I- T?
Got it! Pigs Without Parents!
What about Nwiff?
Motorbike. Registration?
Name of young woman?
There you are!
Hello, Mr Reynolds.
Well, have you caught them?
-  Who?
-  The robbers.
The robbers who stole my clothes.
Yes. My investigations are going very well.
You have a cold, Bernard?
You need some clothes?
What a week! First, Mum went away
to play bingo all weekend.
Bingo?
Two fat ladies, 88.
Clickety- click, 66.
Anyway, and then someone stole my clothes.
Bingo!
Digestives! My favourite.
You must be Miss Evans.
And this is Sherlock Holmes!
Bridget.
I'd like to ask you a few questions.
Bernard's wearing my dressing gown!
What are you staring at?
Nothing.
Is there something wrong with your top lip?
No.
Yes, there is. It's bright red.
It doesn't show, does it?
No, no, no.
They told me in the salon no one would notice.
Thank you.
I wanted perfect lips, but I didn't have
enough money, so a student did them.
What, a butcher student?
There, there. You're still very pretty.
Am I? Really?
Really.
Where were you last night?
-  Looking in the mirror.
-  All night?
Yes, all night.
How can anyone spend all night
looking at themselves in the mirror?
Bridget would.
I think that someone here
is not telling the truth
and I think that someone is you.
But I told you. I was with Annie.
Annie hasn't said she was with you.
That's true.
She can't speak.
She is doing
a sponsored silence for chair- I- T.
It doesn't matter. Did you go out at all?
-  Yes.
-  Where?
-  Shopping.
-  Shopping?
For what?
Some new clothes.
These new clothes?
Now, let me get this straight.
You need some new clothes
and Mr Reynolds' clothes have been stolen.
So what does that tell me?
Yes, but I...
Why buy new clothes
when you can steal somebody else's?
Yeah!
Do these look like Bernard's clothes?
They could be. My colour.
Oh, no! I spoke!
You! You made me speak!
Hello? Yes, he's here. I'll get him.
Bernard, it's your mother.
Hello, Mum. You're back.
How was bingo?
Mum, someone stole my clothes.
OK.
Right, I'm off.
Mum's back. She's cooking my tea.
Bernard, what about your clothes?
It's OK. She's got them.
-  What?
-  What? What?
She put them in the washing machine
before she went to bingo.
Mum!
So Bernard's clothes
were in the washing machine all the time.
Well, yes, as I suspected.
That's another case solved. I'll be off, then.
No, you won't!
What?
You owe me £120 for Pigs With No Parents.
You made me speak!
Well, will dollars do?
Next time in Extra...
The girls enter a game show.
And guess what Hector finds on his jumper.
And guess what Hector finds on his Jumper.
This is the story of Bridget and Annie,
who share a flat in London,
and the boys next door,
Nick, and his friend Hector from Argentina.
Bridget and Hector work for Channel 9.
Annie works for the environment.
And Nick works as little as possible.
Stand by for Extra.
It's Friday, it's seven o'clock.
Yes, it's time for an evening with Marty Ross.
And here's Marty!
Hi, darling, Marty Ross here.
Let's spend this evening together.
Let's spend this afternoon together.
Marty! Hi.
I was just writing notes for your show.
You like what you see?
Marty, you're so funny.
Is Lady Macbeth in?
-  Who?
-  The dragon. Eunice.
No.
Marty, you're so funny.
Has Eunice got me tickets
for Damian Pollasco's latest exhibition yet?
Who?
Damian Pollasco.
The most important artist this century.
He's so raw,
so angry.
Of course he is. Silly me. I forgot.
Good old Damian.
Anyone who is anyone
will be there tomorrow night.
So of course I must be there.
Yes.
So tell the dragon if there are no tickets,
I will not present Saturday's show.
But you must, Marty. You're the star.
But if there are tickets,
then I will take her out to dinner.
In fact, I'll take anyone out to dinner
who gets me those tickets.
Anyway, must go. I've got fans to ignore.
Well? Carry on.
Hi, darling, Marty Ross here.
Let's spend this evening together.
What a professional.
So if I get tickets for Damian Pollasco,
I get dinner with Marty Ross!
Who do I know? Who do I know?
I know! Dave! He's crazy about me.
Hi, Dave. It's Bridget.
I've got a little favour to ask you.
Is anybody home?
Annie, is that you?
Is that Ziggy? I think you should let her out.
No, it's OK. We're seeing
what it's like to be a battery chicken.
A chicken that runs on batteries?
-  No.
-  No!
A chicken that is kept in a small box
to lay her eggs. Poor thing.
But isn't Ziggy a bit...
No. It makes it more real, doesn't it, Ziggy?
Tomorrow there is a big Farm Animal
Freedom Protest in Trafalgar Square
and we will be demonstrating.
-  Demonstrating what?
-  What it's like to be a farm animal.
Sounds exciting.
Boggy and Moss are coming from Manchester.
Boggy and Moss?
Boggy and Moss
are very, very serious eco- warriors.
Eco- warriors?
They fight for the environment.
And you two will help us prepare.
Won't you, boys?
Bye.
Good old Dave. I knew he'd help me.
He just can't resist me.
Now...Marty.
Hi.
Hi, Marty. It's Gigi.
-  Gigi?
-  Bridget.
-  Bridget who?
-  Bridget. Eunice's researcher.
-  Have we met?
-  Well, only about one hundred times.
Listen, I've got two preview tickets
for Damian Pollasco.
Oh, that Bridget. How could I forget you?
How about meeting for drinks
at your place first?
I'd...love to...
but it's just a simple loft- style apartment.
Well, I'm sure it's very arty.
I can tell a lot about a woman from her art.
They call me Arty Marty, you know.
And if I like your art, Bridget,
maybe dinner afterwards?
Marty! What a surprise! I'd love to.
See you tomorrow, baby.
-  Bye.
-  Ciao.
Dinner with Marty,
dinner with Marty, dinner with Marty!
What shall I wear?
My flat! Arty?
Annie, look at this flat.
Sorry, Bridget.
Right, I've got 24 hours.
-  I think you should let her out.
-  No, it's OK.
Boggy and Moss
are very, very serious eco- warriors.
And you two will help us prepare.
I've got two preview tickets for Damian Pollasco.
They call me Arty Marty, you know.
And what is going on this time?
Hi, Bridget. I'm feeding Hector cornflakes.
Really? And why?
He's a turkey.
Yes, of course he is.
Turkeys are made to eat lots for Christmas.
Well, we all eat lots at Christmas.
No, it's cruel.
It's to make them fat for humans to eat.
Let me guess. He is a baby cow?
Nearly. He is a veal calf. Poor thing.
We're preparing
for our Farm Animal Freedom Protest.
No, you're not.
You're preparing this flat
because Marty Ross is coming for drinks.
Not Marty Ross?
Hey, darling, let's spend the evening together.
Shut up, Nick. Go back to your bottle.
So this preparation, what is it?
I want this flat to look
like the coolest art gallery in London.
The Tate Modern.
-  The Tate Modern?
-  No furniture.
I want 21st century. I want art.
So how are you going to do this?
I'm not going to do it.
You are.
I must get my beauty sleep.
See you in the morning. Have fun.
Well, I'm not doing it.
Come on, Nick. It won't take long.
I'll give Ziggy the keys to your flat.
OK, let's get on with it.
There! That's better.
Marty will love it.
The things I do for Bridget's love life.
What about Bridget's love life?
Right, I'll be back with Marty at six o'clock,
so, Annie, I want nibbles...
-  Nibbles?
-  Nuts, crisps.
Hector, you prepare the drinks.
And Nick...
try to be more interesting.
Now, don't let me down.
I want 21st century. I want art.
Yeah...
I'll show her interesting.
I'm taking the day off work today.
No, you're not.
We've got lots to do before tonight.
Bridget's nibbles?
No! The Farm Animal Freedom Protest.
Boggy and Moss are coming here
and I want you to look after them, Hector. OK?
Come on, Ziggy.
Interesting?
I'll show you interesting, Bridget Evans.
Interesting, interesting!
No, too Picasso.
No, too sporty and stupid.
Yes! This is the one.
No.
Don't be ridiculous.
Nearly. Not quite.
Bingo!
Poor thing.
We're preparing
for our Farm Animal Freedom Protest.
I want 21st century. I want art.
Hey, darling, let's spend the evening together.
Shut up, Nick. Go back to your bottle.
Oggy? Moth?
Excuse me, I am... Nuts...
Come in, come in.
Please...sit down.
So, you are Annie's friends?
I am Annie's boyfriend.
Would you like a drink?
You would? You wouldn't?
Tea? Coffee? Sugar?
It is my phone.
I know you know it is a phone,
but it is ringing, so I must...
Excuse me.
Annie, I'm so happy you rang.
Hector, I'm in the ladies' toilets
in Trafalgar Square.
Have Boggy and Moss arrived yet?
Yes.
Annie, they are a bit...
Aren't they sweet?
Yes, very sweet.
It is just that they...
All right, chaps? Won't be a minute.
It is just that they are a bit scary.
Hector, don't be so silly.
Tell them to come to Trafalgar Square now.
Great.
You found something to eat. Good.
You like them?
Good, good, good.
Annie says you can go to Trafalgar Square. Now.
It is the phone again.
Phones ring, don't they? They...
Excuse me.
Hello.
Hello, Hector. Did you get the nibbles?
The nibbles. The nibbles.
Yes, of course, Bridget.
Well done, Hector. I knew I could rely on you.
That was Bridget, Annie's fr...
Now am I interesting?
Do I look that bad?
This is interesting!
What shall I do? It was Boggy and Moss.
Look, don't worry. We can tidy this up.
Look. See? Look.
Yeah, that looks much better.
-  Still, at least I've brought the drinks.
-  And I have the nibbles.
-  What?
-  The nibbles.
Very good.
Oh, no! Boggy and Moss ate them.
Look at this!
Tastes good.
See? Bridget won't even notice the mess.
Marty, you're so funny.
Anyway, here is my humble home.
Mr Ross, I'm a huge fan.
What is that?
It's a pigpen. We stole it from a farm lorry.
What a shame, no pig.
Boggy and Moss are bringing her later.
-  This place...
-  This place is very...
I'm so angry!
..angry. I love it!
Yes. Yes, it's my angry art phase.
All my own ideas, you know.
-  Cocktail?
-  Nibble?
And this is fantastic. Original?
Very original.
Very Damian Pollasco. I love art.
They call me Arty Marty, you know.
Is it...for sale?
The man's an idiot. He wants to buy a wall.
Much too expensive.
Much too precious.
Name your price.
Can you deliver them to me tomorrow?
Sure. No problem.
Nick, what's this cocktail called?
It's an Arty Marty.
It's rich, sickly and very thick.
Nick, your date is here.
Of course she is.
Next time in Extra...
Nick goes to the dentist.
Annie can't speak.
And why does an inspector call?