Previously on "Arrow"...
Maybe I'm finally ready
to admit that I still have
feelings for you, too.
No! Malcolm is planning
to level the Glades!
My father, he told me
that he failed the city,
but I never knew
what he meant until now.
Merlyn's plan is what I returned
from the island to stop.
Oh, no!
You can survive this.
Make it home.
Make it better.
Right my wrongs.
Dad?!
Survive.
No! No!
I hope I didn't hurt you.
At least I can properly thank you
now for saving my life.
If I only knew
how you were
spending your nights...
My hope is that I can
explain everything to you
to help you understand.
You murdered my father!
You sentenced me
to that island,
to five years of hell.
I am truly sorry
for what happened to you.
You know I have
lost people.
Yeah, your wife.
Do you really think
that you're honoring
Tommy's mother
by destroying
the Glades?
As surely as you believe
you're honoring your father
with this hood.
Not a day goes by
I don't miss your father.
You'll see him soon.
You can't beat me, Oliver.
Yes, you're younger.
You're faster,
but you always seem
to come up short against me.
Want to know why?
Because you don't know,
in your heart,
what you're fighting for.
What you're willing
to sacrifice, and I do.
No one can stop
what's about to come.
Not even the Vigilante.
The plane's holding steady
at 33,000 feet.
That's the range
for missile intercept, sir.
Lock missile one
on target.
Missile one locked
on the jet's heat trail.
Prepare to launch
on my mark.
Yes, sir.
Fire! Fire the missile now!
I take back every joke
I made about you sticking
a tracking device in your boot.
* Arrow 1x23 *
Sacrifice
Sync & corrections by Saman 22
Felicity's
at Queen Consolidated.
She's still going through the data
she pulled off Merlyn's network.
Did she find
anything?
Yeah, the design
schematics
of the earthquake
generator.
So we can shut it down.
Assuming
we find it in time.
Yeah, Felicity,
I got him.
Thank God.
Is he ok?
Mostly.
Ok.
I'm on my way.
Miss Smoak.
Where are you off to
in such a hurry?
Please.
Take a seat.
You know, I think
I'd rather stand.
You're not exactly
a hardened criminal, are you?
No, I'm not
any kind of criminal.
What do you call
computer hacking?
A hobby?
That I do not engage in.
Hey, I got a whole mess
of computer gobbedly gook
that I don't understand,
but it says otherwise.
I had my tech guys
go through your computer
at Queen Consolidated.
You used it to hack into
blackhawk squad security
to research arrows shipped to
a company called Sagittarius
and to analyze a water
sample to tie back
to a Vertigo drug lab.
These are all cases
involving...The Hood.
Tell me, Felicity.
What am I thinking?
Saved by the bell.
Excuse me.
Hello, Detective.
It's funny
you should call.
I got your trusty sidekick sitting
right in front of me.
I don't have a sidekick.
When I need help,
I call you.
Malcolm Merlyn plans to level
the Glades with a manmade earthquake
using technology
from Unidac Industries.
What?
Now you're just
trying to have some fun with me.
I don't know what
Merlyn's timetable is,
so you need to evacuate
the Glades immediately.
Get as many people
to safety as you can.
Whatever you think
of me, Detective,
please...believe this.
Sounds like you have
bigger problems than me.
Don't leave town.
You know...
I used to think the Vigilante
was a criminal, too,
but it seems to me,
whoever he is,
he's willing to sacrifice
an awful lot
to help the people
of this city.
Kind of makes him
a hero...
Doesn't it?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Look who it is.
My best friend in life.
Hey, buddy.
I took your advice,
you know.
I went to Laurel's,
to fight for her.
So imagine my surprise
seeing you there,
kissing her.
I'm sorry.
No, you're not.
Something's happening,
and it involves your father.
Keep my father
out of this.
Our fathers.
They aren't the men
we thought they were.
They made a plan together...
to destroy the Glades.
Do you have any idea
what you sound like right now?
Your father's going to do it.
Because he thinks
it will avenge your mother's death.
Do not talk about
my mother!
The difference
between us, Tommy,
is that I didn't find out the truth
about my father
until it was too late.
But you've always known,
deep down,
you have always known
the man he is.
I wish you would have
died on that island.
We need to reprogram
the missile.
I don't know how to reprogram
a missile launcher!
I do.
Watch out!
Oliver, put the chip in.
Make it quick,
I got a comm stat meeting in five.
I don't want to be late for
my own funeral.
I've got it under
good authority
that Malcolm Merlyn
is planning on leveling the Glades
using some kind
of earthquake device
made by Unidac
Industries.
Who's your source
in all this?
The Vigilante.
He called me.
Has been
for the last few months,
he's been helpful
on some cases.
You asked for the task
force to catch him.
You swore to me you'd bring him in.
I know.
I swore to uphold the law,
because the law is steady,
the law is unchanging,
the law needed to be protected.
But what are laws, rules,
if they don't protect people?
Now listen, I know,
I'm throwing away my career
by telling you this,
but I am willing to sacrifice
catching this guy
if it means saving people's lives!
Please.
You're suspended.
Leave the gun and your badge
with the duty sergeant.
Lieutenant...
Suspension or incarceration.
You choose.
No more lies, Mom.
The Undertaking.
We need to stop it.
Everything I have ever
said or done
has been to protect you
and your sister.
What about all those
people in the Glades?
I'm not their mother.
I spoke to Malcolm.
You what?!
He could have killed you.
He killed your father.
No, he didn't.
After the "Gambit"
went down,
dad and I both made it
to the life raft.
And then we drifted,
for days.
In the end,
there wasn't enough
food and water
for both of us.
So he shot himself
in the head.
I don't want to hear this.
He sacrificed himself...
So that I could live.
Do you really think
that I could
go on living
knowing that
you sacrificed
thousands more
in my name?
Mom.
Please.
You have to help me
stop Malcolm.
We need to know
where the device is.
Malcolm.
How can I help you?
I see.
Yes, thank you
for calling.
What is it?
Malcolm's accelerated
his timetable.
The Undertaking is...
Is happening tonight.
Where you going?
Somebody in this family
needs to put an end to this.
Whatever the cost.
Hi.
Hey.
I woke up and you were gone.
I'm really sorry
about that.
Oliver, I'm trying
not to think
that our history's repeating;
That you're scared again.
No.
That's not it.
Then will you tell me what's
going on with you?
There are so many things
that I have wanted
to tell you
for so long.
I never told you what
happened to me on the island.
You didn't have to.
I can see that
it changed you.
That's the thing.
Laurel, it didn't.
Those five years
didn't change me.
They just...
They scraped away
all the things that I wasn't,
and revealed the person
I always was,
which is the person...
That's who you always saw.
I don't know how you saw it,
but you did.
Nobody in my life
is who I thought they were...
Except you.
Laurel, I need you
to do something for me.
Stay out of the Glades tonight.
Why?
You'll know soon.
One way or the other.
I have to go.
It's over.
Laurel and me, I mean.
She's with Oliver,
again. Always.
I'm sorry, Son.
Yeah, and he said
you wanted to nuke
the Glades or something.
You know,
it's funny,
scotch doesn't make it
any more believable.
Maybe after your jihad,
we can grab
some steaks.
It's true, Tommy.
It's the reason
I closed your mother's clinic.
I didn't want
to see it leveled.
What?
I have something
I'd like you to listen to.
The night
your mother died,
she called me.
I awoke to a voicemail
from her.
Dad...
Her final gift to me.
Malcolm,
I'm in trouble.
I told--I told him
to take everything.
My money...my ring.
Turn it off.
They shot me.
I screamed for help,
but no one would come.
No one would come.
Malcolm, I don't want
to die alone.
She bled out into the pavement
while people passed,
did nothing.
Your mother
built her clinic in the Glades
because she wanted
to save this city.
It can't be saved.
Because the people
there don't want it to be saved.
So you kill them all--
Yes!
They deserve to die!
All of them!
The way she died.
The Undertaking
is happening tonight.
Oliver, Felicity
may have found something.
This symbol is a map of the old
subway tunnel system.
That's what got us
thinking the Undertaking
is connected to the Glades.
What if it's more
specific than that?
What do you mean?
If I had a machine
that could trigger
an earthquake in an otherwise
geologically stable area,
where would I position it?
Underground.
Yeah.
This is a U.S.
geological survey
of the tectonic plates
running underneath Starling City.
This red line here
is a known fault
that runs right below
the Glades.
About a mile, the fault
runs underneath the old
Tenth Street subway line.
Dollars to donuts, the seismic
device is somewhere along there.
I know where it is.
Now is not a good time.
Yeah, understate much?
Mom has a whole bunch
of reporters here.
She's holding a press conference
or something.
What channel?
Ah, it looks like
all of them.
Felicity, pull up
the local news, please.
My name is
Moira Dearden Queen.
I am the acting CEO
of Queen Consolidated.
And God forgive me,
I have failed the city.
For the past five years,
under the threat for my life
and the lives of my family...
I have been complicit
in an undertaking
with one horrible purpose--
to destroy the Glades
and everyone in it.
I realize now
that my family's safety
will mean nothing
if I let this
dreadful act occur.
But you need to know
that the architect
of this nightmare...
is Malcolm Merlyn.
No!
Yes, and I have proof
that he has killed dozens
in pursuit of this madness.
Adam Hunt, Frank Chen,
and my husband...
Robert.
Please.
If you reside in the Glades,
you need to get out now.
Your lives and the lives
of your children depend on it.
Please.
I don't understand.
I'm sorry. I love you.
I love Roy.
Roy?
He lives
in the Glades.
I can't leave him there.
Sweetheart--Thea!
Moira Queen, you're under arrest
for conspiracy.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you in a court of law.
You have the right
to an attorney.
Is it true?
Did you kill
all those people?
I did what I had to do.
Freeze!
Malcolm Merlyn,
you are under arrest.
Dad, no!
Please, Dad.
Stay back.
I don't want to hurt you.
You can't.
And you can't stop me.
Oliver, I'm sorry.
Don't be.
She gave those
people a chance.
I thought Merlyn
broke your bow.
I have another.
I was going over
the device schematics.
The device can be set
for a timed detonation
or can be remote activated
by a mobile transmitter.
Something Merlyn
could have on him.
Listen, Oliver,
if we can just
get our hands
on this transmitter,
maybe we don't need
to track down the device.
It's too big
of an "if," Diggle.
I need you
in the subway.
Find the device,
disarm it.
So you can take on
Merlyn by yourself?
I have to.
Oh, he'll kill you, Oliver.
I know.
He's beaten me twice.
And I don't know
how to stop him.
Ok. Well, how about this time,
you bring along something
you didn't have the last time
you two fought--
Me.
I can't let you.
I can't let you do this
by yourself, man.
Oliver, you are not alone,
not since
you brought me into this.
Us into this.
Besides, army regulations--
a soldier never lets
a brother go into battle alone.
I'm out of bows.
I got my gun.
I guess it's up to me
to do the dismantling.
This whole area
is ground zero.
I want you
out of here.
If you're not leaving,
I'm not leaving.
Besides, if I don't
deactivate the device,
who will?
You were right.
I need one more
thing from you.
Yeah? What do I got
left to give?
I know where Merlyn
is keeping the device.
It's in an abandoned subway
station near Puckett Street.
How do you know?
That's where
his wife was murdered.
I need someone I can trust
to deactivate the device.
We have a mutual friend
that I think could...
Talk you through it.
She says you care
about the people of this city,
that it needs you.
Right now, Detective...
It needs you.
Earlier today, Moira Queen,
CEO of Queen Consolidated,
admitted to a conspiracy
to destroy the Glades.
Everyone within a five mile
radius is asked to evacuate.
Please leave the area
immediately.
Evacuation centers
have been set up in Starling City.
Looks like we missed him.
Shado!
Slade!
Boy, I should
have figured.
You couldn't
save the day...
without making a mess.
Where's Shado?
I thought
she was with you.
Actually...
She's with me.
Let her go!
It's over, Fyers!
Let her go.
Amazing.
A two year operation undone
because a young playboy happened
to wash up on the shore,
and now here you are--
a killer.
You wanted
nothing more than to leave this island,
and now you can.
I can call in a rescue ship,
you can go home.
Tell me, Mr. Queen.
Are you prepared
to sacrifice your freedom...
For her?
Guess so.
Tommy.
Tommy. Tommy!
Oliver.
Where's your father?
Ohh. I don't know.
You were right.
You were right about him.
Oliver.
Are you going to kill him?
Get to safety.
Looks like a false wall.
Welcome, gentlemen.
I've been waiting for you.
I wanted to see you
watch your city die.
Where's
the transmitter?
Somewhere I can
easily get to it.
I doubt it.
You'll be too dead.
Aaah!
Stairs. Go, go.
So tell me--
are you ready to die?
You found it yet, Detective?
Not exactly sure
what I'm looking for.
Do you want me
to describe it to you?
No, I've got it.
You should see something
that looks like a circuit board.
Pull it out.
Do you see a timer?
Seven minutes.
Ok. Well, the good news is,
this is going to be
a paperweight in three.
What do you got there, grandpa?
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Back off!
Learn how to count, jerkwad.
There's three of us.
Oh, is that right?
'Cause I only count one.
With a gun.
Where did you learn
how to do that?
I guess I have wicked aim.
What?
I went to your house.
Yeah, I figured I'd run for my life
with everyone else.
Did you--did you
come to rescue me?
Yeah.
Come on.
There are three wires--
you need a green one,
a yellow and one blue.
Cut the blue.
All right,
I got it, I got it.
Oh, my God.
No, no, no, no, no!
There must be some sort
of anti-tamper safeguard.
Hold on. I'm going to try to
figure out how to override it.
Not enough time.
There's not enough time!
Just hold on!
Not enough time.
Laurel.
Dad, don't worry,
I got your message,
and I did not
come into work today.
Save it, kiddo,
we both know you're there.
But listen--you got to
get out of the Glades.
You got to get out of
the Glades right now! Ok, please.
Dad?
Right now, Laurel!
Daddy,
you're scaring me.
Sorry, but I'm not...
I'm not going
to make it.
What?
What?!
You have to promise me
one thing, Laurel.
You're not going
to die along with me.
You have to go on
with your life.
After your sister died,
I pushed people away,
I became like a ghost.
I didn't think I had
the right to live
when my baby girl
didn't.
Promise me
you're not going
to make the same
mistakes as I did.
Where are you?
Promise me, Laurel.
Promise me.
I promise.
I love you, honey,
now and forever.
I love you.
Dad!
Detective Lance?
I need you to listen to me
very carefully.
You do know how dangerous
it is to text and drive,
right? It can wait!
No, it can't. I'm trying to find us
another route out of here.
Let me. It's not
worth the risk.
Roy!
Help me out! Help me out!
Help me out!
Roy, stop! Roy!
The device is about
to go off any second!
I can't leave
anyone behind.
I know you think
you have something to prove.
But you're not the Vigilante!
I can't do this
unless I know you're safe.
Then you better
haul ass out of it.
Don't struggle.
It's over.
There was never any
doubt in the outcome.
Don't worry. Your mother
and sister will be joining you in death.
Survive.
Thank you
for teaching me
what I'm fighting for.
But my father taught me how.
Come on!
Oliver,
Lance did it.
It's over.
If I've learned anything
as a successful businessman,
it's...
Redundancy.
Felicity...
there's another device.
There's two of them!
What the hell's
happening?!
Ok, that's enough.
Ohh!
I turned
the damn thing off!
Merlyn had a second device!
My daughter! Laurel!
She's at CNRI!
Run!
Laurel!
Oliver?
Are you ok?
Yeah.
The damage seems
to be contained
on the east side,
past Wells Street.
Laurel.
Are you going
to be ok?
Go, go, go.
Help!
Please! Help me!
Tommy!
What are you doing here?
I kind of figured that you might
come back to CNRI.
You came here for me?
I love you.
Get up! Go!
I'm right behind you!
Laurel! Laurel!
Dad! Dad!
Oh, thank God.
No!
No! Laurel!
No, you can't!
Tommy!
You can't!
It's too late,
it's too late.
Tommy!
Ah, Tommy.
You're going to be fine.
Another thing...
We got to disagree on.
Tommy...
Is--is Laurel safe?
Is Laurel safe?
I tried to get her out of here.
Yeah, yeah, you did.
You saved her.
I'm going to get you
out of here.
You're going to be fine.
Stop.
I'm sorry.
No. Don't apologize.
I was angry.
And I was jealous. I--
I am my father.
No.
No, you're not.
Did--did you kill him?
No.
Thank you.
No, no!
Tommy!
It should have been me.
Open your eyes, Tommy!
Open your eyes.
Sync & corrections by Saman 22
www.tvsubtitles.net
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Oh, my God!
Run, run!
No, no, no, no, no!
Oh, come on, man!
I'm just trying
to make
an honest living!
There's nothing honest
about what you do!
Who supplies you with Vertigo?
Tell me now and you live.
Please!
They'll kill me!
Whoever you fear...
Fear me more!
Okay, okay!
We call him The Count,
that's all I know.
I swear to God!
Hey!
Get me down
from here!
Find what you're looking for?
Took down three Vertigo
pushers tonight, Diggle.
Last one finally knew a name.
The Count.
The Count?
That's worse than The Hood.
You're not going
back out there.
I'm not done
for the night.
Whoever this Count is,
he has a lot of blood on his hands,
and it is long past time
he started paying.
Well, slow down, I think
you're missing the point here.
What?
Thea.
Her hearing's
in a few hours.
You think she cares more
about some drug lord
getting his
just desserts,
or you being by her side
when she needs you the most?
Hey, we should
get going.
Judges don't
appreciate the value
in being
fashionably late.
Got any other tips?
Let the lawyer
do all the talking.
They'll give you
a pad and paper
but do not play
tic tac toe.
Judges don't
appreciate that, either.
Come on, Speedy.
I know, I know.
Keep on trying
to get up and go,
but...
just don't.
I wish dad were here.
I'm here.
We should leave now, Thea.
Ms. Queen.
Thea, over here.
Can we get a comment?
Just one comment!
Thea, are you
going into rehab?
Miss Queen, are you being
dispelled from Balliol Prep?
Are you worried
about the outcome?
Docket ending 1-10-5-6,
People vs. Thea Dearden Queen.
Possession
of a controlled substance,
driving under the influence
of a controlled substance.
Counselors, I understand
you've reached a plea agreement.
We have, Your Honor.
Given that my client
is a juvenile,
the people have generously
agreed to probation.
Juvenile?
Says right here she's 18.
She is 18 now,
Your Honor,
but at the time of arrest,
she was still two days shy
of her 18th birthday.
Ms. Queen
has no priors.
Well, just because
Ms. Queen's family
sweeps her priors
under the rug,
doesn't mean they don't exist.
You get your client off,
and you help your boss
avoid dealing with the drug
that's sweeping across
our city like the plague.
Everyone wins, except us,
the people of Starling City.
Your Honor,
with all due respect--
Ms. Queen,
like it or not,
you are now the poster child
for this menace.
Maybe if people see
that the Queen family
can't get away
with using Vertigo,
they'll think twice
before using it themselves.
The plea arrangement
is denied.
This case will
proceed to trial.
They can't do this.
That man cannot send
my daughter to prison.
What are our options?
An interlocutory appeal.
But trial judges have discretion
to reject plea agreements.
I think you might want to
prepare yourself for the possibility
that this isn't going
to go our way.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Queen.
I'll get to work
on the appeal.
Well, so much for the best
criminal defense attorney in the city.
Thea, we will handle this,
I promise.
Like you promised Walter
you'd always stay faithful to him?
I feel better already.
That's enough!
Don't worry.
Sounds like you won't
have to be putting up
with me much longer.
What, does she not realize
how serious this is?
She took drugs.
She drove. She could have
killed someone, or herself.
I know.
All that judge is looking for
is someone to make
an example of.
What does it have to be her?
Maybe it doesn't.
Listen, I have to go
do something.
Are you going
to be okay?
I'm not the one facing prison.
You working
for them now?
Why are you
doing this to me?
I thought
we were friends.
Or...something.
I mean, why'd you bother
keeping me safe
if you were just going
to hand me over to them?
Just get me out of here.
I can't.
Hey! Don't leave me here!
I came back for you!
Do you hear me?
? Arrow 1x12 ?
Vertigo
Original Air Date on January 30, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Hi. Looking
for Detective Hall.
I was told
he works in Vice.
Oliver?
McKenna Hall.
Hi.
Here I was,
expecting a middle aged guy
in a bad suit...
And I got McKenna Hall.
I live to surprise.
Well, I remember.
What was that club
that you got us kicked out of?
The Club Deville?
Okay, in my defense,
there was no sign
that specifically said
you had to keep
your clothes on.
So, a cop?
I guess you're not hitting
the party circuit anymore.
I still go to raves.
I just go
undercover now.
And I have to dress
slightly more appropriately
to hide my badge and gun.
Right.
So what do you need
with a vice cop, Oliver?
Vertigo.
Right. I saw your sister on TV.
I'm sorry.
The judge is trying
to make an example of her.
So I was thinking,
if you could find the person
selling the drugs,
it make take some
of the heat off Thea.
Easier said than done.
Did some digging
and came up with a name.
Um, The Count?
Oliver, we've known
about The Count for months.
Oh.
I wish this
was thicker,
but we really don't
have much on him.
Love to say we're
going to catch him
before your sister's
trial, but it's highly unlikely.
Oh, I am late
for my shift.
Well, if you hear
of anything about this guy,
just...let me know?
I always loved how much you cared
about your sister.
But leave the policing
to the police, okay?
Okay.
What did Queen want?
He's an old friend,
sister's jammed up.
Anything else,
Sergeant?
No.
You need a tailor.
You know about
the hood guy.
He just
cornered me, man.
The hood guy?
I didn't
say anything.
Oh, I know.
You can't divulge secrets
you don't know.
But...
examples must be made.
Vertigo,
in its purest form.
When injected directly
into the bloodstream,
it affects the thalamus
region of your brain.
Which is where all
of the information
from your pain receptors
is collected.
No doubt you're in
excruciating pain.
But actually, you're not.
You just think you are.
I've seen it last for days,
until finally
the heart gives out.
One bullet left.
Now, you can use
that bullet to shoot me
and take your revenge,
or...you could
shoot yourself.
It's your choice.
The Hood.
Coming for me.
Interesting.
I'm learning you're not much
of a morning snuggler.
And I'm learning that
you don't like to wake up
at any hour
that ends in a.m.
That's true. Yeah.
So if you're busy
being a lawyer all day
and I'm managing
a night club all night,
when exactly do we get
to see each other?
Hmm.
I got it. Stay.
Hey.
Hey, how--
how is Thea holding up?
She's doing okay.
Thank you.
Um...Actually, I--
I came to talk
to Laurel.
Yeah.
Hi.
Thank you for coming
to court yesterday.
Yeah, of course.
But I don't think
the judge is willing
to move off his position.
Taking a hard line
against criminals is
a platform for his reelection.
I need you to talk
to your father.
He's inside the system,
and...maybe he cashes in
a chip with Judge Brackett,
gets him off throwing the book at Thea.
Oliver, I don't--
Laurel, I am working
on something on my end,
but...
If it doesn't work out,
this is my best chance
to help my sister.
Please.
I'll see
what I can do.
But no promises.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Absolutely not.
Dad, I know
how you feel about Oliver.
Then why would you even
ask me to do this.
Because Thea,
she's only 18 years old.
Which makes her an adult.
She can take her medicine.
It's about time someone
in the Queen family did.
What about
the Lance family?
A young girl
acting out,
engaging
in reckless behavior,
does that sound
familiar?
Laurel,
don't go there.
Thea, she's just like
I remember Sarah.
That is not how
I remember your sister.
That's because
you remember her
the way that you
wish she had been,
not the way that
she actually was.
She's not the Saint that
you make her out to be.
I know she was arrested
for shoplifting
and I know
you made it go away.
Well, maybe
if I let her go to jail,
Queen wouldn't have had her
on that damn boat.
Dad, you make it sound
like he kidnapped her.
For so long,
you and I have blamed Oliver
for Sarah's death,
but Sarah's
to blame, too.
When I look at Thea,
I see Sarah's
potential in her.
And her flaws, too.
Yes, Thea made
a mistake.
But she's been
through a lot.
She lost a father
and a brother.
She doesn't need prison.
She needs help.
So please...
I'll make some calls.
I've seen a fair amount
of Cyrillic back in Afghanistan
left over
by the Soviets.
Is this Russian owned?
This is the not
so hidden headquarters
for the Starling City
chapter of the Bratva.
Diggle...
Whatever I say,
whatever goes down,
just go with it.
Zdravstvuyte.
Good to see you.
Long time.
Particularly
for Bratva captain.
I was trying to figure out
where to put my interests.
I decided on pharmaceuticals.
I don't mean aspirin.
A wise choice.
Mepheodrone would be a good
investment for you.
It's the newest thing.
I was thinking Vertigo.
Newer thing.
Tough market, Vertigo.
Only one seller.
I know.
I was hoping you could
do me a favor
and arrange a meeting.
He's difficult man.
And he does not
like new friends.
This is everything
the police have on him.
Tell him it's a gift.
I will see
what I can do.
Provided you do
favor for me.
Vse chto ugodno.
It is unusual
for an American
to hold such
a position of esteem
in our organization.
Mr. Queen.
Anatoli Knyazev.
He speaks
very highly of you.
He should.
I saved his life.
What did he do?
Something
I told him not to.
Now the favor.
Kill this man for me,
and I will believe
your interest
in our organization
is genuine.
And then I will arrange a meeting
with The Count.
Oliver...
Hey, shut up!
What are friends for?
I'm out of the gates
now. What's going on?
Are we getting
out of here?
Where are you taking me?
While I admit that bout
was particularly one-sided,
would anybody else
like to give it a try?
The point of these little
gladiatorial distractions
is to strengthen
unit cohesion.
To that end, I think
our newest recruit
ought to be afforded
the opportunity
to try his hand.
I can't believe
you just killed that guy.
You really have
a low opinion of me.
Whoa! That's a neat trick.
You going to teach me
that one day?
No.
What are you doing?
You need to arrange
a new identity for this guy.
Get him out of the city.
Right, so your Ruskie pal
draws out The Count,
vigilante takes him down.
No, Diggle,
because then the Bratva
would know that I used them,
and that relationship is too valuable.
I do the meet
with The Count as myself,
let him leave, then we follow him
to his hideout.
Just that easy, huh?
Well, I will still need
my trust bodyguard.
Fantastic. Looking forward
to my new and exciting career
as a drug dealer.
He's a captain.
And he has money.
Are you interested?
Hmm.
Let's say...yes.
My father was able
to get Judge Brackett
to back off
his hardline stance.
Your father hates me.
No.
My father hates him.
Look, nobody asked you
to get involved.
I did.
The judge has agreed
to a sentence
of 500 hours
of community service
and two years of probation.
Provisional on the appointment
of someone to act in loco parentis.
In loco what?
It means that
the court will appoint
an individual to assume
responsibility for you.
Me.
I say thanks,
but no thanks.
Thea!
You don't actually
have a choice.
Oh, actually, I do.
See, I'm 18 now and I can make
my own decisions.
So I decide not to be
your ex-girlfriend's office monkey.
Well, if you change
your mind, then.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Thea...
You're in real trouble,
and rightly so.
Doing drugs
and driving?
It is beyond stupid. That is
a good deal that Laurel got you.
Why aren't you
jumping at it?
I already have a mother.
So...
you're going
to go to jail
and it will ruin
the rest of your life.
No.
I want to ruin mom's life.
She's a liar and a cheat.
I mean, deal with, Ollie.
You can pretend
all you want to
that she's a saint,
but I hate her.
And she betrayed dad.
So you're just--you're going
to go to jail to spite her?
Thea...
Mom didn't cheat on dad.
He cheated on her.
Is that the best
you can come up with?
Dad wasn't the man
he said he was.
On "The Queen's Gambit"
right before he died,
he admitted to me
that he failed us.
You.
Me. And mom.
That he wasn't the man
he said he was
and that he just wished...
he wished he had more time
to right his wrongs.
I don't believe you.
Yes, you do.
Leave me alone.
How dare you.
She was old enough
to know the truth.
Oliver, the Russians called.
The meet is set.
It's tonight.
You know why
they call him The Count?
When he was
developing this drug,
he experimented
on the homeless.
Prostitutes, runaways.
The police
would find their bodies,
puncture marks
on their neck,
like a vampire.
You should not be in such a hurry
to meet this man.
Thank you for this.
But I'm not
overly concerned
about the SCPD.
Now, I understand
you gentlemen
wish to participate in
the feel good business.
Yes.
And why is that?
Well, I am opening
a nightclub,
and I'd like my customers
to have a little...
something extra.
Well, as it happens,
I'm looking
to expand my brand.
A good wine's value is measured
by its vintage.
The number of years
it took to ferment.
Vertigo is measured
in lives.
56 people died
to perfect this high.
Believe me when I say
that they did not
die for nothing.
The cops!
We've been set up!
Let's get out!
Go! Go!
SCPD! Put your weapons down!
Down!
Oliver!
Hey!
No witnesses.
Get out of the car!
Keep it.
Yeah, we got to go.
Steps. Let's go.
Oliver!
Drink.
Wait!
Mornin'.
How you feeling?
I feel like
I'm getting
the worst hangover
of my life.
That coming from a guy who spent
most of his twenties in a hangover,
that's really saying something.
You think
you can uncuff me?
Not going to kill you.
Promise.
Ahh.
You're standing.
That's pretty impressive.
The Count only got you
with half a dose,
but you still sweated out
a small swimming pool coming down.
The Count.
Any chance our friends
in SCPD took him down?
None at all, but we did
manage to get this.
Think we should analyze it.
Listen, Oliver, maybe you need
to give it a few hours.
A near drug overdose isn't something
you just walk away from.
Neither is Thea.
What's wrong?
Is everything
okay with Thea?
This isn't about your sister,
this is about you.
Last night we got a call
from a C.I.,
busted up a drug sale between
a big time dealer and the Russian mob.
"We"? I thought
you worked Vice.
Joint task force. Vertigo's
got everybody holding hands.
Like I said...
Last night,
drug deal gone south.
An eyewitness
put you at the scene.
Whoever he is,
he's mistaken.
Yeah?
I saw you, Oliver.
Is this true?
I was checking
into The Count.
He's the guy who
sold drugs to Thea.
And I figured if I could find out
what he looked like,
then I could give your sketch artist
something to go on.
So I paid a low-life
with a Russian accent
an obscene amount
of money to arrange a meeting.
And? Did you get eyes on him?
No.
All right, are you pressing charges
against my son?
You get involved
in this again,
you'll see the inside
of a cell,
and unlike last time,
you will not see the way out.
Detective.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for what
you did for Thea.
My daughter asked me
for a favor and I did it.
And that's the end of it.
Hope you don't think
I sold you out.
No. Just doing your job.
What on earth
were you thinking?
I was trying to help.
By running around
with the Russian mob
and a murderous
drug dealer?
Are you out
of your mind?!
Mom, look,
the real reason
that you're upset
is because I told Thea
the truth about dad.
She never needed
to know that.
Yes, I did.
I'm old enough
to know the truth, Mom.
It wasn't about
your age.
It was about preserving
your memory of your father.
He loved you.
No matter his faults,
he loved you.
I said that I wished
you had died
instead of him,
but...you still
didn't say anything.
Why?
One day,
I hope you're lucky enough
to have a daughter,
and you'll know why.
I'm so sorry for what I said.
I know, I know.
Now what?
Like you said,
we analyze the Vertigo.
It's in liquid form,
which means it contains water.
So maybe we can
trace back to where
in the city The Count is...
cooking up this garbage.
Hey, we need
to get you to a hospital.
No.
Oliver, God knows
what was in that drug.
It could be causing
permanent damage.
Felicity.
Hey, they said
you'd be up here.
You look like something
the cat dragged in.
Not that there are cats
in this building.
Well, once a cat did get in,
but a guard tazed it.
It smelled like fur and static
in here for like a week.
Ahem.
Would you mind stepping
away from the window for a moment?
I have a little bit
of a hangover.
Sounds like you need
a bloody Mary and a pretzel,
not the I.T.
Department.
Actually, my buddy Kevin
is starting
an energy drink company.
He says it's fantastic
for curing hangovers,
but I am very particular
about what it is
I put in my body.
I've noticed.
I said, not noticed.
Right?
I'm trying to find
a secret recipe.
Could you please
do a spectroanalysis
of the sample
and find out exactly
where in the city it's made?
If it's an energy drink,
why is it
in a syringe?
I ran out of sports bottles.
Okay.
Your B.S. stories
are getting worse.
I'm well aware.
Looks like Felicity
came through.
The solvent used
in the Vertigo sample
was run off water originated
within a ten block radius
of where East Glades
meets the bay.
Nothing there except
for an old juvenile detention center
abandoned about three years ago.
Cutbacks.
You can't go out there,
though, Oliver.
You're still suffering
the after-affects of the Vertigo.
Did you hear The Count?
He's taking
this drug citywide.
If we don't stop him now,
this becomes an epidemic.
I can stop you from leaving.
Try.
Oliver, you hit this
and you can leave.
I'm glad you came
to your senses.
You should always
remember one thing, Dig.
What's that?
I don't need the bow.
My C.I. swears
this is the place.
Bring your men
up on the flank.
Okay, this way.
Follow me.
He's here!
He who?
The Hood!
Looks like we're not
the only guests.
You should have stuck
to your depraved elite.
I am merely providing people
with what they want.
I am providing
a public service!
So am I.
Enjoy the fruits
of your labor.
Freeze! Put down the needle!
Or I will shoot you!
Put down the syringe.
He deserves this!
Not according to the law.
The people that think
you're a hero,
people like my daughter,
if they could see you now...
You're no hero.
You're what I always
said you were--
a killer.
Get him!
Get me an ambulance. Now!
Juvenile delinquent
reporting for duty.
Since you lost
your driver's license,
I'll pick you up at 5:00.
6:00.
We have a lot of work
for her to do.
Well, then, let's say
7:00 just to be safe.
Is it too late
to choose jail?
Yes.
I need you to go
through these files
and pull out all the documents
dated March 2007.
Do you think
you could do that?
I think I can.
I know I messed up.
I really appreciate
this, Laurel.
We are going to make
an upstanding citizen
out of you yet, speedy.
Thank you.
And this will be good for her,
having a role model,
somebody better than me.
Oh, you're not so bad.
And besides, it'll be nice
to have her around.
I got to take this.
Excuse me.
Hello?
We got The Count.
Bust up his lab,
got him on everything
from drug trafficking
to homicide.
He'll be gone
for a long while.
That's great, thanks.
It was great
seeing you, Oliver.
You, too.
See ya.
He's still critical.
I've never seen
anyone OD
on this much Vertigo
and live.
There's just
no way of knowing
what kind of damage
has been done to his brain
and nervous system.
Or if its irreparable.
Shengeun...
Survive.
Hi.
Thanks for meeting me.
I was...nervous
to come to your house.
Okay...
The thing is,
I've been debating
whether or not
to share this
with you for weeks.
Can I trust you?
I'm not an idiot.
You've dropped some fairly
ridiculous lies on me,
and...yet I still feel
like I can trust you.
Why is that?
I have one
of those faces.
Sorry.
Yes.
You can trust me.
Then I have something
to show you.
Have you ever
seen this before?
No.
Where'd you get it?
From your stepfather.
From Walter.
Um...
Well, where did
he get it?
He said he found it
in your house.
That it belongs to your mother.
Walter thought
she was hiding something.
Something more, and...
He wanted me to look into it,
but then he vanished.
I think this list might have cost
Walter his life.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.OpenSubtitles.org
www.tvsubtitles.net
Sync and correction by GeirDM
www.addic7ed.com.
The name
of the island they found me on
is Lian Yu.
It's mandarin for "purgatory."
I've been stranded here for
5 years.
I've dreamt of my rescue every
cold black night since then.
For 5 years, I have had
only one thought, one goal...
survive...
Survive and one day return home.
The island held many dangers.
To live, I had to make myself
more than what I was,
to forge myself into a weapon.
I am returning not the boy who
was shipwrecked
but the man who will bring
justice to those
who have poisoned my city.
My name is Oliver Queen.
Oliver Queen is alive.
The Starling City resident
was found by fishermen
in the North China sea
5 days ago,
5 years after he was missing
and presumed dead
following the accident at sea
which claimed
"The Queen's Gambit."
Queen was a regular
tabloid presence
and a fixture at
the Starling City club scene.
Shortly before
his disappearance,
he was acquitted of assault
charges stemming
from a highly publicized
drunken altercation
with paparazzi.
Queen is the son of Starling
City billionaire Robert Queen,
who was also on board but
now officially confirmed
as deceased.
20% of his body
is covered
in scar tissue.
Second-degree burns
on his back
and arms.
X-rays show at least
12 fractures
that never
properly healed.
Has he said anything
about what happened?
No. He's barely
said anything.
Moira, I'd like
you to prepare yourself.
The Oliver you lost
might not be
the one they found.
Oliver.
Mom.
Oh...
My beautiful boy.
I've got it.
Your room is exactly
as you left it.
I never had the heart
to change a thing.
Oliver.
It's damn good
to see you.
It's Walter...
Walter Steele.
You remember Walter,
your father's friend
from the company.
It's good to see
you, Raisa.
Welcome home, Mr. Oliver.
Mr. Merlyn phoned. He wants
to join you for dinner.
Wonderful.
Oliver?
Did you hear that?
Hey, sis.
I knew it.
I knew you were alive.
I missed you so much.
You were with me
the whole time.
Come on, Laurel. We're
lawyers, not miracle workers.
We can't win this.
If we can't win
a class-action suit
against a man who
swindled
hundreds of people out
of their homes
and life savings,
then we're not fit
to call ourselves
a legal aid office.
And if we
go bankrupt
in the process,
we won't be
a legal aid office.
Hunt has an army of
lawyers, and they're
ready to bury us.
You and I against an army.
I love those odds.
Why do you
hate me?
And in other news,
details
as to the castaway story
you've all heard about...
the son of a very
wealthy billionaire
will soon become
a legendary story.
Jessica now
has more details
and the complete
castaway story.
"The Queen's Gambit" was
last heard from more
than 5 years ago.
Mr. Queen
has reportedly confirmed
he was the only survivor
of the accident
that took the lives of
7 people, including
local resident Sarah Lance.
Survived by her sister,
Laurel...
After 5 years,
everything that was once
familiar is now unrecognizable.
The face I see in the mirror
is a stranger.
The storm's
a category 2.
The captain's
recommending
we head back.
All right.
Inform the crew.
Are we in trouble?
One of us is.
Ollie?
Where do you keep
the bottle opener
on this thing?
I'll be there in
a minute, Sarah.
You know, son,
that is not
going to finish well
for either of them
or for you.
What did I tell you?
Yachts suck.
Tommy Merlyn.
I missed you, buddy.
Ok. What else did
you miss?
Super bowl winners... Giants,
Steelers, Saints, Packers,
Giants again.
A black president,
that's new.
Oh, and "Lost," they
were all dead...
I think.
What was it like there?
Cold.
Tomorrow, you and me,
we're doing the city.
You've got a lot
to catch up on.
That sounds like
a great idea.
Good. Then I was hoping
to swing by the office.
Well, there's
plenty of time for all that.
Queen Consolidated isn't
going anywhere.
Oh, I am
so sorry, Mr. Oliver.
Dude, you speak Russian?
I didn't realize you took
Russian at college, Oliver.
I didn't realize
you wanted to sleep with my
mother, Walter.
I didn't say anything.
She didn't have to.
Oliver...
Walter and I are
married,
and I don't want you
to think
that either one of
us did anything
to disrespect
your father.
We both believed that
Robert, like you, was,
uh, well, gone.
It's fine.
May I be excused?
Hey, don't forget
about tomorrow, buddy.
1, 2, 3.
It's getting closer.
That's not
very scientific.
What would you know
about science,
Mr. Ivy league
dropout?
I happen to know a lot
about science.
I know about
fermentation.
I know biology.
Laurel's gonna kill me.
Oh, she's so gonna kill me.
Your sister
will never know.
Come here.
Ha ha!
Ok, that one was
really close.
Sarah, we're
gonna be fine.
Sarah?
Sarah!
Oliver!
Sarah! Sarah!
Gus?
No! No!
No! Dad, she's out there!
She's not there.
Sarah!
She's gone.
Oliver, wake up. Oliver?
Oliver!
I'm sorry. I'm so...
I'm so sorry.
Oh, it's ok, Oliver.
It's all right,
sweetheart.
You're home.
Where did you
get these?
Roxies. Thank you,
daddy's ACL tear.
Ollie.
No one's called me
that in a while, Speedy.
Worst nickname ever.
What, always chasing
after me as a kid?
I thought it fit
pretty well.
Maybe it still does.
See you at school, Speedy.
Sorry about her.
I have something
for you.
You did not come back
from a deserted island
with a souvenir.
It's a Hozen.
And in buddhism,
it symbolizes
reconnecting.
I kept it in hopes
that one day,
it would reconnect
me with you.
A rock!
That is sweet.
You know, I want
one of those
t-shirts that says
"my friend was
a castaway, and all I got
was this crappy shirt."
Don't let him get you
into too much trouble.
You just got back.
Take it slow.
Ahem.
The city awaits.
Have you noticed how hot
your sister's gotten?
Because I have not.
# it's been
a long night... #
Your funeral blew.
Did you get lucky?
Fish in a barrel.
They were so sad...
No.
And huggy.
And I am counting
on another target
rich environment
for your welcome
home bash.
At my what?
You came back from
the dead.
This calls for
a party.
You tell me
where and when.
I'll take care
of everything.
And this city's
gone to crap.
Your dad sold
his factory
just in time.
And why'd you want
to drive through
this neighborhood
anyway?
No reason.
So what'd you miss
the most,
steaks at the palm,
drinks at
the station,
meaningless sex?
Laurel.
Everyone is happy
you're alive.
You want to see the
one person who isn't?
Laurel, I just got this
from Hunt's lawyers.
They filed
a change of venue.
We are now in front
of Judge Grell.
Hunt funded Grell's
reelection campaign.
Mm-hmm.
He's got Grell in
his back pocket.
You know, it's fun
being your friend.
I get to say "I told
you so" a lot.
No. Adam Hunt is
not smarter than we are.
No, he's just richer
and willing to commit
multiple felonies.
We don't need to go
outside the law...
"to find justice."
Your dad's favorite
jingle.
Hello, Laurel.
You went to law school.
You said you would.
Yeah. Everyone's proud.
Adam Hunt's
a heavy hitter.
You sure you want to get
in the ring with him?
Five years and you want
to talk about Adam Hunt?
No. Not really.
Why are you here, Ollie?
To apologize.
It was my fault.
I wanted to ask you
not to blame her.
For what?
Falling under your spell.
How could I possibly blame
her for doing the same things
that I did?
I never meant to...
she was my sister.
I couldn't be angry
because she was dead.
I couldn't grieve because
I was so angry.
That's what happens when
your sister dies
while screwing
your boyfriend.
We buried an empty coffin...
Because her body was at
the bottom of the ocean
where you left her.
It should have been you.
I know that it's too
late to say this,
but I'm sorry.
Yeah, I'm sorry, too.
I'd hoped that you'd rot
in hell a whole lot longer
than 5 years.
How did you think that
was gonna go, Tommy?
About like that.
Ok, so we took care
of that. Good call.
Now we can make up
for lost time.
If you're not
too sick of fish,
I suggest we find
some leggy models
and eat Sushi all
day. What do you say?
What're they doing?
What the hell?
Hey!
Here, son. Drink.
What the hell
are you doing?!
That's all
we've got.
If anybody's making it
out of here,
it's gonna be him.
I'm so sorry. I thought
I'd have more time.
I'm not the man you
think I am.
I didn't build
our city.
I failed it.
And I wasn't
the only one.
Mr. Queen.
Mr. Queen!
Did your father
survive that accident?
I ask the questions.
You give me the answers.
Did he make it
to the island?
Did he tell you anything?
Yes, he did.
What did he tell you,
Mr. Queen?
He told me
I'm gonna kill you.
You're delusional.
You're zip-cuffed
to that chair.
Not anymore.
You killed that man.
You don't have
to do this.
Yes, I do.
Nobody can know my secret.
So that's your story.
A guy in a green hood
flew in and single-handedly
took out 3 armed kidnappers.
I mean, who is he?
Why would he do that?
I don't know. Find
him and you can ask.
Yeah. What about you?
You see the hood guy?
I saw...
Just movement.
Everything blurry.
I was kind of out of it.
Yeah.
It's funny, isn't it?
One day back,
and already somebody's
gunning for you.
Aren't you popular?
Were you able
to identify the men?
Scrubbed identities,
untraceable weapons.
These were pros.
Yeah. Well, they
probably figured you'd
pay a king's ransom
to get your boy back
or a Queen's ransom,
as it were.
After all, a parent
would do anything
to keep
their child safe.
I don't find your
tone appropriate, Detective.
If Oliver can think
of anything else,
he'll be in touch.
Thank you,
gentlemen,
for coming.
Your luck never seems
to run out, does it?
You are different.
Not like you to read
a book.
I missed you, Raisa.
No kitchen on
the island.
No. No friends either.
Hey.
Thank you.
Do I really seem different?
No. You're still
a good boy.
Oh, I think we both
know I wasn't.
But a good heart.
I hope so.
I want to be the person you
always told me I could be.
Oliver, I want to
introduce you to someone...
John Diggle.
He'll be accompanying
you from now on.
I don't need a babysitter.
Darling, Oliver's
a grown man.
And if he
doesn't feel he needs
armed protection...
Yeah, I understand,
but this is
something I need.
So...
What do I call you?
Diggle's good.
Dig if you want.
You're ex-military?
Yes, sir.
105th airborne
of of Kandahar,
retired.
Been in
the private sector
a little more than
4 years now.
I don't want there to be
any confusion, Mr. Queen.
My ability to keep
you from harm
will outweigh
your comfort.
Do we have
an agreement?
Sir?
Sir!
The abduction was unexpected.
It forced me
to move up my plans,
but what I told
the police was true.
The man in the green hood
was there in that warehouse,
and he's just beginning.
The suit alleges
that Hunt committed
multiple acts of fraud
and theft
against the city's
underprivileged.
Laurel Lance, an attorney
for the city necessary...
Adam Hunt...
his crimes go deeper
than fraud and theft,
but he's been able to
bully, bribe, or kill anyone
who's gotten into his way.
He hasn't met me yet.
You remind Grell I put
him on the bench,
I can take him off.
I will turn him into
a cautionary tale.
Yes, Mr. Hunt.
And this attorney
Laurel Lance...
you said she wasn't gonna
be a problem anymore.
I told you to fix
that situation.
Why are you
still here?
Unh!
Get in the car!
Hey. You missed.
Unh!
Aah!
Unh! Aah!
What? What?
Just... just tell me
what you want.
You're gonna transfer
$40 million
into Starling city
bank account 1141
by 10 P.M. tomorrow night.
Or what?
Or I'm gonna take it,
and you won't like how.
If I see you again,
you're dead!
He was wearing a hood,
a green hood,
and he had
a bow and arrow.
What, you don't
believe me?
That maniac put two
of my men in the hospital.
Well, thanks
for your statement.
We'll put out an APB
on... Robin hood.
Hey, pal.
I'm not some grocer who got
taken for his register.
I go to the front
of the line.
Now he said he would be
back here by 10 P.M.
Make sure
you're here first.
You can coordinate with Mr. Drakon,
my new head of security.
All right. Well, uh,
thanks for your time.
It looks like Queen
was telling the truth.
Yeah. Well, there's a first
time for everything.
This hooded guy comes looking
for trouble, he'll find it.
Put on your
seat belt, sir.
Wouldn't want you
to miss your party.
# This beat's
for all my freaks #
# Time to lose my mind #
# 'cause I work damn hard #
# So I'll play damn hard #
# Lost in the night #
# 'cause I work damn hard #
# So I'll play damn hard #
# I, I, I, I work-ork-ork
damn har-har-har-hard #
# I, I, I, I #
Everybody, hey!
Man of the hour!
Whoo! And, ladies, please give
this man a proper homecoming.
# We are the champions #
Thank you very much,
everybody!
Ollie, Ollie,
Ollie, Ollie.
I missed Tequila!
What the hell's
going on out there?
It's across
the street.
Party for the guy that got
rescued off that island...
Oliver Queen.
Hey. Does he wipe
for you, too?
Now by my rough estimate, you
have not had sex in 1,839 days.
As your wingman,
I highly recommend
Carmen Golden.
Which one is she?
The one who looks like the
chick from "Twilight."
What's "Twilight"?
You're so better off
not knowing.
Back in a minute.
Ollie, hey!
This party is sick.
Who let you
in here?
I believe it was
somebody who said,
"right this way,
Miss Queen."
Well, you shouldn't
be here.
I'm not 12 anymore.
No. You're 17.
Ollie, I love you,
but you can't come back
here and judge me,
especially for being
just like you.
I know that it couldn't have been
easy for you when I was away...
away? No. You died.
My brother
and my father died.
I went
to your funerals.
I know.
No, you don't.
Mom had Walter,
and I had no one.
You guys all act
like it's cool,
let's forget about
the last 5 years.
Well, I can't.
For me, it's kind of
permanently in there,
so I'm sorry
if I turned out
some major
disappointment,
but this me is
the best I could do
with what I had
to work with.
Let's bounce.
You have
the fun dip?
Yeah. It's right...
no. I... I must have
dropped it.
Oh! Oh.
You're here.
Tommy. He made the
point that we have
too many years
between us
to leave things the
way we left them.
Is there someplace quieter
that we could go?
Yeah.
I'm sorry about saying that you
should have been the one who died.
That was wrong.
If I could trade places
with her, I would.
About Sarah.
There's something that
I've been afraid to ask,
but I need to know.
Ok.
When she died...
Did she suffer?
Sarah!
Aah!
No.
I think about her
every day.
Me, too.
I guess we still have
one thing in common then.
I can't believe
I'm gonna say this, but...
If you need someone
to talk to
about what happened
to you, I'm here.
Something wrong?
I asked somebody
to do something.
They didn't do it.
Laurel...
You always saw
the best in me.
Right now, that's
what you're doing,
looking at me,
and you're wondering
if that island
changed me somehow,
if it made me
a better person.
It didn't.
Stay away from me.
Otherwise...
I'm just gonna
hurt you again,
but this time,
it will be worse.
Got to roll.
I got 5 years of
debauchery to catch up on
you know what, Oliver?
You're wrong. That
island did change you.
At least now
you're honest.
Something I can
help you with, sir?
I just wanted a second
to myself.
I would believe you,
Mr. Queen,
if you weren't
so full of crap.
Party's this way.
It's locked.
You two cover
the elevator.
Hang back and be ready.
Stay in the corners
and stay alert.
It's past 10:00.
He's never getting
in here.
All's clear.
Yeah.
Unh!
You missed.
Really?
Hunh!
He's here!
All units, converge!
Aigh!
Go right, go right.
On me.
Lay down your weapons,
or we will open fire!
I repeat, lay down
your weapons.
Tell me
you saw that.
Ok. Let's go. Move.
# Girls, girls, girls #
# Hot babes #
Cut it.
Search the building
roof to basement.
Find him!
Starling City police!
The party's over, kids.
Oh, Mr. Merlyn. Imagine my
shock at finding you here.
Did you roofie anyone
special tonight, huh?
Detective!
It's a private party.
Yeah? Well, there was an incident
at Adam Hunt's building tonight.
You know anything
about that?
Who's Adam Hunt?
He's a millionaire bottom feeder, and I'm
kind of surprised you aren't friends.
I've been out of town
for... A while.
Yeah. Well, he just got attacked
by the guy with the hood,
the guy that saved
your ass the other day.
The hood guy.
You didn't find him?
I'm gonna offer
a reward.
Hey, everybody.
$2 million to anybody
that can find a nut bar
in a green hood.
Did you even try
to save her?
Ok. Let's go, partner.
Did you even try
to save my daughter?
Sarah wouldn't want this.
It's not.
Partner, let's go.
It's all right.
Let's go.
It's way too quiet
in here!
This is a party!
Some coincidence, I mean, you
asking to have your party here,
and Hunt getting robbed
right next door
and by the same guy who
rescued us at the warehouse.
If I were you,
Tommy,
I'd just be glad
you're alive.
What happened to you
on that island?
A lot.
What the hell
are you talking about?
$40 million doesn't
just up and vanish!
Untraceable?!
It is $40 million!
Find it!
How did he do it?
There's not enough
for all of us.
Save your strength.
You can survive
this, make it home,
make it better,
right my wrongs,
but you got to live
through this first.
You hear me, Ollie?
You hear me, son?
Just rest, dad.
No.
Dad?!
Survive.
No!
If hypothetically
$50,000 magically appeared
in your bank account,
it might be best
for you not to
speak about it...
To anyone... Ever.
God bless you, too.
I just got a very
grateful phone call
from one of our clients
against Adam Hunt.
Me, too. Heh.
It looks like Starling
City has a guardian angel.
By the way, your
cute friend's here.
You left the party
pretty quick last night,
even after I made sure the bar
was stocked with Pinot Noir.
It wasn't really
my scene.
I thought maybe you and Oliver
went mano-a-mano again.
I saw you two
head out.
There's nothing between
Oliver and I, not anymore.
Here I thought the only thing
between you and Oliver was us.
I wouldn't exactly characterize
us as an "us," Tommy.
Then what would
you call it?
A lapse.
That's quite
a few lapses...
your place,
my place,
my place again.
Oh, come on, Merlyn. We
both know that you're not
a one-girl type of guy.
Depends on the girl.
I have to go
back to work.
Dinah Laurel Lance always
trying to save the world.
Hey. If I don't try
and save it, who will?
# Let's get out of here #
# won't you come along? #
She says the island changed me.
She has no idea how much.
There are many more names
on the list,
those who rule my city
through intimidation and fear.
Every last one of them will
wish I had died on that island.
The police failed to identify the
men I hired to kidnap Oliver,
and they never will.
Should we arrange
another abduction?
No.
There are other ways of finding
out what my son knows.
Sync and correction by GeirDM
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net