Hector.
Yes.
Please could you pass the salt?
Hector.
Yes.
Please could you pass the pepper?
Of course.
Hector.
Let me guess. Can I pass the sugar, coffee, tea.
Actually I was going to say we should talk.
So now you want to talk to me!
It's only been a week!
I was hurt!
Well you hurt me too.
I didn't go out with Eunice!
Yes you did! And you stayed out 'till three o'clock in the morning!
There were other people there too.
Who?
People who work on the programme.
You mean other women who work on the programme.
Yes and men, why not? Eh?
I knew it!
So, who is she?
Who?
The other woman.
There is no other woman!
Annie, listen. Oh,
excuse me.
Hello. Ha, ha-ha, hi Debbie. And how are you? Ha-ha. Good.
Erm, OK, that'll be OK, perfect, see you then. Bye.
So was that her?
Who?
Debbie. The other woman.
That was Debbie from the make-up department,
confirming my call time for tomorrow.
Oh! Some excuse!
Hector.
Yes.
Please could you pass me your fork?
Here, I'm going. You can have my dinner!!
You should have seen Eunice's face! Ha-ha-ha! She was furious!
When Eunice gets angry, she is a very scary lady!
Hello.
Yes.
Excuse me. No, no...To her... Erm,
bye, Bridget.
Oh. All right Hector. Bye.
Hola, Lola! Ah!
Guess what?
Prince William wants to marry you?
I know that! No! I've got a promotion!
That's nice.
Nice? Nice? It's fantastic! I am editor of Channel 9 Live!
Eunice is no longer my boss!
Is that Hugh Grant?
It's Bridget Evans here. Call me Gigi, editor of Channel 9 Live.
Are we still on for lunch at Claridge's today?
Oh, fab! Ciao!
Eunice is so jealous!
Now that is good news.
Annie, what are you doing?
I'm doing my own editing.
Why are you cutting out photos of you and Hector?
Because Hector is no longer my boyfriend.
Really? Why?
Because he is having an affair!
Really?!! Who with?
Well, I thought it was Eunice, but now I think it's Debbie.
Well I just heard him on the phone to Lola.
Lola? Who's she? Hah! Eunice, Debbie, Lola, ha, he's women mad!!
Hi Nick.
What are you doing?
I am not doing, I am being.
Oh. What are you being?
Can't you guess?
A man on the toilet?
A Sumo wrestler?
Can't you see? I am an egg.
Oh, of course, you are an egg.
Now, what sort of egg am I?
Hard-boiled.
Scrambled.
Scrambled?!
Fried.
Nearly!
Poached!
Oh yeah. Of course, you are a poached egg.
Yeah!
Well you're making a mess on your bed! Ha-ha-ha!
Anyway, why are you being a poached egg?
It's my new acting class. Total Being.
Oh, what are you next week? A piece of wood?
A piece of wood?
Yeah, then it would be wooden acting!
Anyway, can poached eggs talk?
Don't be silly! Of course poached eggs can't talk.
No, no, I mean,
when you are 'being' a poached egg, can you talk?
Oh yeah!
Anyway, I want to stop now, my arms are hurting. Ah! Agh!
So, what do you want to talk about?
It is Annie
She thinks I am having an affair.
Who with?
Eunice.
And Debbie.
What?
Two women, Hector! Ha! You cheeky thing!
But I am not!
Oh, so tell Annie then.
I have, but she doesn't believe me.
Why not?
I don't know.
Oh, Excuse me.
Hola, Lola. Ha!
I'll take this outside.?
How are you, Lola
So, it's not Eunice, it's not Debbie, could it be - Lola?
Hey, hey, stop, please!
I knew it! It had to be a selfish man driver!
Please, I have a voucher.
I, I'm sorry, I've started, so I'll finish.
Look I am Zeus, why are you so angry?
I'm not. I am just doing my job - Zeus.
People park on yellow lines and then are surprised when they get a parking ticket! Ha!
There was this one guy today - 'please, I have a voucher.' Ha!
No excuse!
Mind you, he was quite cute.
Nick, Nick, are you OK?
Bridget.
Oh, it's you, Hector.
Well, there's something wrong with Nick.
Well I could have told you that!
No, he won't speak, he won't move.
Oh, I know. He is being a poached egg.
A what?
For his new acting class.
Hi Nick.
Let me guess. You are being...
... a potato
Do I look like a potato?
Yes. A couch potato!
What about a fish?
Yes, a frozen fish!
I am not a fish. I am pain.
You are a pain
Yes, Nick is a pain!
No, I am pain. Hurt, agony.
So, how was your first day as editor, Bridget?
What a day! I had a very important meeting.
Big decisions to make.
Oh, like which celebrities, new programme ideas?
No, like which pen to use at my meeting. Blue, black …
Oh, which one did you choose?
Blue.
Oh …
Bad choice.
You think so? Oh no!
Eunice is so jealous of Bridget's new job, she won't talk to anyone!
Not even you?
Not even me! It is great!
You don't want her to talk to you? Really?
Really! Oh, Annie, I hate it when we argue.
So do I.
I miss you.
I miss …
Hola Lola. Ha-ha. …
Right. Two can play that game.
Hello again.
Hello. We meet again.
You're happier today.
Yes, I am now! But, I'm sorry.
I parked here, so you would come back.
Oh. You wanted to see me again?
You are so beautiful!
Oh, well, I'm sorry, but I am going to have to give you...
... this, my phone number.
Call me.
Who needs Hector?
Hi Bridget.
Oh!
What 'oh'?
I know, Superman.
What?
Erm, I mean Clark Kent.
You are being Clark Kent for your acting class.
No. I'm not. I'm long sighted.
Oh. You're being long sighted?
No. I am long sighted. I need to wear glasses for reading.
They suit you.
Oh, ah, thank you.
So why are you not at Channel 9 today.
Oh, I'm working from home today.
There's so much to do!
Bridget, what's the matter?
I can't do it! Eunice hates me!
Oh, Eunice hates everybody!
They all hate me!
No they don't!
They all look at me!
Bridget, you are their boss.
I have to use the executive loo!
What's the matter with that?
I want to chat to all the girls!
Oh, Bridget, you are one of the cleverest, most beautiful women I know.
Really?
Well who are the others?
What do you mean?
You said I was only one of the cleverest most beautiful girls you know.
Bridget! You can do this job.
Channel 9 needs you.
Thank you, Nick.
Hey, it was nothing.
You really look handsome in those glasses.
Oh, hi Annie.
Oh, hi Hector. You look smart.
Yes, I am going to meet someone.
Oh, Annie, I have something to tell you.
Oh, sorry.
Oh, Lola! Vale. Si, si, ya voy. Hasta luego.
'Annie, I have something to tell you.'
Yes, that he is going on a date with Lola! That's what!
Nick, stop it! You're tickling me!
Oh hi Annie, I didn't hear you come in!
Oh Nick! Stop it!
Is everybody happy, apart from me?!
Hello.
Zeus! Hi! Well of course I remember you!
A drink? Tonight? Ah, I'd love to.
Stop it! You're tickling me!
Zeus, meet my friends, Bridget and Nick.
Hi - HI!
Well hello Zeus!
Annie, where did you find him?!
Yeah, but he doesn't wear glasses though, does he? Eh?
We've had a lovely evening, haven't we, Zeus.
Wonderful, H-Annie. Now I must say goodnight.
Please, first may I use your bathroom?
Certainly.
Thanks.
Zeus is such a gentle man.
He certainly is a man.
Hi.
Annie, I must talk to you.
What about? Your date with Lola?
My date with Lola?!!
Annie, Lola is a sixty year old chief executive for ATV.
What's ATV?
Argentinian Television.
And...
she wants me to return to Argentina to present their number one show.
But I don't want to go.
I want to stay here - with you.
That's better.
Erm, Hector, this is …
Ohh, ohhh!
Hector, stop being such a baby.
But it hurts!
I haven't touched you yet.
Ohhh.
Now stay still. You will just feel a little needle prick.
Oh, go on then. Hurt me, do it!
Hector!
Ohhhhh.
I've done it.
Huh?
I've removed the splinter.
Huh? Oh, er, yes, I knew that. I was joking.
What is it, are you scared of needles?
Who, me? Don't be silly.
But it was a very painful splinter.
OK, so if you're not scared of needles, would you have a tattoo?
A tattoo?!
Yes, yes, I would.
Go on then, tough guy.
OK, I'll have one if you have one.
OK. OK, it's a deal.
Oh, by the way, Hector...
I had this done this morning.
But then, a deal is a deal, isn't it?
I - want a word with you.
Tough guy, eh?
Yeah. What do you want?
I - don't. I don't. I... keep forgetting this bit:
I - don't - like - your - face.
OK, so is this for television or theatre?
Nope. This is real. This is me.
And you are...?
Can't you guess?
Guys, you are looking at Muscles.
Where?
No, no, no. It's my new name. I am the new man on the door at Ice.
What, you're a bouncer?
What is a bouncer?
It's someone who throws people out of night-clubs.
Uh-uh-uh. I am an entry executive.
So you throw people out of the club.
Yeah.
Yeah. Nick, my granny could beat you up.
Ah!
But if your granny came to Ice and caused trouble,
I would have to ask her to leave.
Besides, I'd have Knuckles, Cruncher and Muncher to back me up.
Who?
The other bouncers.
Yeah, right.
Hi, sweetie.
Has someone died?
No, not yet.
Why are you dressed in black then?
Because, baby, you are looking at the new man on the door at Ice.
You are on the door at Ice?
But that's.., but that's wonderful news! What shall I wear?
I'll call the girls to find out what they're wearing.
The thing is, Bridget, if your name's not on the guest list, then you can't come in.
Nick, if my name's not on the guest list, then you can't come home.
Hello? Oh! Hi!
Yup, that's right. I start on Friday.
OK, baby! No probs. Leave it with me. Ciao!
My mum. She wants me to do some gardening for her.
Hector, I've just won...
What are you doing?
Oh, just looking for a number.
Oh, I see.
Well, I just wondered if you wanted to share my chocolate with me before Bridget sees it.
Oh yeah! Great! Thanks.
Annie?
Huh?
Did I tell you about the time three people tried to fight me?
All at once?
Yup.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Oh, well, go on.
Well, three of them, they came at me...
Oh, you poor thing! And what did they want?
My sweets.
Oh. And how old were you?
Six.
And they were...?
Five, three and two.
Hector! Two years old! They were babies!
Yeah, but the Sanchez sisters were really tough!
Oh, Hector, you are sweet.
Annie.
Hmm?
Do you think I should be more macho?
Oh, Hector. You don't have to be a tough guy for me.
I love you just the way you are.
Oh, Annie.
Come on, let's eat this chocolate before Bridget finds it.
Oh, please, let me.
Oh. Oh! Ooh, you're so strong! Oh!
Ow!
What is it?
You are standing on my foot.
Wimp.
Ah, hi, Nick.
Oh, hi. Hey, listen to this.
"Bouncer of the month is Alex Smith
who last year stopped 955 people from going into his club."
What is the name of the club?
Er, it doesn't say. It shut down last week. Not enough people were going there.
Nick.
Huh?
What is a wimp?
Huh! Well, it's not... Ha-ah-ah …
Annie just called me a wimp.
Yeah.
I want to be a tough guy, like you.
Huh?
Can you teach me? Please?
Of course. I was born like this,
but I can try to help you, Hector, I can try.
Great. Why don't you show me how to be a bouncer.
At - it - tude.
Yeah, like this.
Are you looking at me?
Hey, great!
So who am I looking at when I say that?
Anyone who is looking for trouble.
Aha!
And how do I know they are looking for trouble?
You just know.
Look.
What is this?
Bridget's old toys!
What are they doing under your bed then?
I was looking after them for her.
Anyway, look, here, this is the club.
You - cannot - come in.
Let me in!
Are you looking at me or chewing a brick, eh?
'Cause either way, you'll lose your teeth.
Huh?
You know - brick, teeth, chew - cha-cha-cha-cha!
Ah, very good!
You are a very scary guy. Hmm!
Look! It's handsome Nick! Ohhh! Ohhh!
Look at his muscles. Hmmm!
Hellooooo! You are looking lovely tonight.
Mwah! Mwah! Mwah! Mwah! ....
Leave my boyfriend alone!
It's OK, Bridget. I'm just doing my job ...
If your name's not on the guest list, then you cannot come in.
Huh!
Hmm!
Please could I have your name, sir?
What do you want that for?
Be...
...cause if your name's not on the …
guest list, you cannot come in.
And what are you going to do about it, pip-squeak?
I … I …
… Shall be a good boy! Aah-aah!
Didn't you hear what the man said?
He said, "Go. Disappear. Vanish. Evaporate - now!"
OK, I'm going!
Sorry you had to see that, Bridget.
Course I had the situation completely under control.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, Bridget, why are you here?
Hmm, what? Oh, I've brought you some sandwiches.
Oh, Bridget, how nice of you. Huh!
Where are they?
Where are what?
The sandwiches.
Oh, I must have left them behind. Never mind! So...
who's here tonight?
I'm afraid I can't tell you. It's confidential. Ha-ha-hum.
OK, well, there's the usual crowd - Heidi, Kate, Naomi - oops! Sorry, Bridget!
I have work to do.
Good evening, ladies! Could I have your names, please?
Thank you. Just one more thing.
Bridget?
Arms up, please, ladies.
Hmm, you see, hmm, very nice.
Thank you.
Thank you very much, ladies. Have a great evening.
All part of the job.
OK, Nick. So when is it my turn? I want to go in!
Oh, Bridget, Bridget, Bridget. I promise. As soon as I can arrange it, I will, hmm?
Look, there's a big Latino night next week.
J-Lo will be coming. Leave it to me.
Oh, thank you, Nick!
Oh-oh …  Stand back. I need to take control.
Good! Everything is under control.
Annie?
Hmm?
About the tattoo.
Hmm.
Er-hmm. Look.
Oh! You did it!
Ohh, and Hector, what a wonderful tattoo!
Oh, I don't know what to say! Oh!
Oh, it was nothing.
And I mean it, Hector and Annie forever.
Oh, and look! Charley likes the tattoo as well.
Oh, Charley!
Oh, Hector!
Oh!
Oh, pl-ease. I've just eaten!
Bridget, look. Hector has had a tattoo done just for me!
Oh, isn't it romantic?
Hec-ne-ver. Hec-ne-ver?
It doesn't sound very romantic. What does it mean?
What happened? It's coming off!
Oh. Charley has licked it off.
It's a fake. Hector, you wimp!
Hi, Nick.
What's the joke?
I am.
Oh.
Listen, J-Lo is coming to Ice tonight,
so we need extra bouncers, so you will be working with me on the door!
But I...
And tell Bridget and Annie they are on the guest list.
OK, tough guy?
OK.
Good evening, ladies! You are looking lovely tonight.
Oh, Hector, you look so handsome. I'm sorry I laughed at your tattoo.
Annie, Annie, Annie, I am on duty.
Is J-Lo here yet?
She's here.
Oh, goodie! I love mixing with the stars.
Hi.
She's cute. Hi, gorgeous.
What did he say?
Nothing.
Was he...?
Erm....
Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh.
What are you looking at?
I am looking at you looking at her.
I can look at her.
Not when I am looking at her looking at you.
I think you mean: Not when I'm looking at you looking at her.
That is what I said!
You know what? I tell you I'm gonna buy her a drink, OK?
What did he say?
I think he said he's gonna buy her a drink.
Oh, Hector, no.
Right, that is it! I am going in!
No, Hector, don't. Please...
Oy, you! Leave my girl alone!
Nick! Nick! His mate is chatting up Bridget.
Right, that's it! I'm going in!
Oy, you! Leave my girl alone!
Muscles, you're fired! And so is your friend!
That was great!
I didn't even see J-Lo.
See, Hector? I knew you weren't a wimp.
Next time in EXTRA,
Annie is revising for her exams,
Bridget has a make-over
and guess who is coming to stay?
EXTRA, don't miss it!
… Erm, Zeus, my new boyfriend. We've had a lovely evening, haven't we!
Come on, I'll say goodbye to you downstairs!
So Hector, will you take the job?
What do you think I should do, Annie?
So we must say goodbye to our friends for now?
Will Hector stay or go back to Argentina?
Will Annie go with him?
And will Nick ever give up on Bridget?
EXTRA - will the story continue?!
Well, there you go!
Is he stupid?!
Yes, John!
Yes, I got the cards and the flowers
and the chocolates.
Yes, I got the cushion, as well.
But it's finished. Sorry!
[John on the phone]
But please, don't leave me!
Don't cry!
Oh, goodbye!
Oh, and happy birthday!
Ah! Men!
Come on Charley, come on.
Post, Bridget.
Charley and I have the post.
Haven't we, Charley?
Give me the post, Charley.
Drop it, Charley.
Oh, good boy!
Oh, telephone bill, gas bill, electricity bill.
Oh.
Ah, what's this?
Mmm, a parcel for you, Bridget.
Oh, good.
What is it?
Oh, it's from mother.
Oh, ‘Bridget darling, this arrived for you
and I made you this. Love Mummy.’
Oh, ho-ho, oh very you, Bridget!
Mother!
Ooh, this is from Argentina.
Argentina. Who from? What does it say?
[Erm], it says
‘Hello, do you remember me?’
No.
‘Seven years ago we was pen pals.’
‘We was’ -  we were pen pals.
Oh yeah, now I remember, it’s Hector!
Who’s Hector?
He was my pen pal seven years ago.
Oh...
‘I speak English good now.’
I speak English good.
I speak English well now –
‘and I am coming to England.’
Oh, Latin Americans!
‘I would like to sleep with you.
Do you have a bed for me?’
Oh, he wants to stay here! [Oh]. Ah, ha, ha.
But [erm] what about the rules?
Ooh, a Latin American here,
ooh, like Ricky Martin!
Tall, handsome, rich!
So [erm] when is he coming?
Oh [erm] let me see.
It says ‘November 5th.’
Oh, November 5th.
But that’s …
Aaaah!!!
Oh, oh it’s you Nick!
Hi, babes!
Hello Nick. How are you?
Gr-eat.
Nice muscles.
Here’s your milk.
Our milk.
You mean our milk you borrowed
three weeks ago.
Oh, thanks Nick.
[Speaking in a mock Italian accent]
I forget nothing!
Would you like a drink, Nick?
Uhh.
I said, would you like a drink, Nick?
Oh!
Sorry. No thanks.
Oh, erm, Bridget’s friend is coming.
Oh yeah.
Aha. From Argentina.
Wow! From Argentina!
What’s she like?
She is a he!
Huh?
Not a girl, a boy.
Oh.
Tough guy, ay!
Why don’t I show you
how to do it properly!
Nick, I've told you before.
Nobody uses my bike, nobody,
is that clear?
Why not?
Why not!!!
If you touch my bike again,
you are out! O-U-T, out!
Clear!
What?!
I said …
Hello.
I am called Argentina.
I am from Hector.
You mean ‘I am called Hector.’
You are called Hector?
Oh, no, no, no, I am called Annie.
I am called Annie.
No! She means ‘I am called Hector,
I am from Argentina.’
You are from Argentina!
Oh,
come in!
My cars.
You play with cars?!
Yes, you play, no?
I play with cars.
He plays with cars!
I read.
I love the library.
Fascinating!
We go to the library, too.
Don't we, Bridget!
Yes, it's great!
Good.
I live here.
You live in a museum?
Full of old things?
Old things?
Yes, I have lots of old things.
I live in a museum.
OK. I live in a museum.
Well, thank you Hector and
now we’ll show you the flat.
This is the bedroom.
Thank you.
Who-hey!!
Where do you sleep?
[Erm] no you don’t understand,
we only have one bedroom.
One?
I have twenty.
Twenty?
Yes, he lives in a museum,
with twenty bedrooms.
Oh! Ha-ha-ha, very funny,
ha, twenty bedrooms!
Well, you can sleep here.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, no, no, no, Hector!
It’s a bed.
A bed?   Ah, oh …
Here's a cushion.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, this of course is the TV.
But just relax, I must go to the bathroom.
Psst! Annie! Bathroom!!
Now!
Oh my goodness,
what are we going to do?
He plays with toy cars!
He is not a sexy Argentinian.
But he is sweet.
And he is polite.
But those clothes!
Oh, he is so old-fashioned.
Mm, he must go.
Room service.
Hello. Who are you?
Oh, you who are quick, good
Ay?
My luggage is downstairs.
What?
Bring it up, please.
What are you doing?
I pulled, you come,
you are the butler.
The butler?!
I am Nick, I live next door.
Oh, I, … I am Hector.
Oh, Hector, from Argentina.
Yes, from Argentina!
Where are the girls?
The girls?
Yeah, Bridget and Annie.
Oh they live here.
Yeah, I know.
Where’s Bridget?
Does she know you are here?
Bridget, she gave me this.
Oh.
Hello Nick!
Oh, this is Hector from Argentina.
Yeah, I know.
Isn’t he wonderful!
Wonderful.
Are you hungry?
Uh?
We’ll buy your lunch.
What would you like to eat?
Fish and chips?
Oh, fish and ships!!
[Erm] Nick, Hector, make friends.
Nick, teach Hector some English.
Yeah, OK,
I’ll teach Hector some English.
OK, this is the oven.
This is the ov-en.
Annie’s dog sleeps in the oven.
So you say
“Annie! The dog is in the oven!”
Annie, the dog is in the oven!
Gr-eat!
Now, Bridget.
Oh, oh dear.
Well Bridget likes strong men,
especially strong legs.
Well I am strong.
Yeah?
Can you cycle fifty kilometres?
Yes.
No way!
Well go on then, show me.
Yes, look!
Adios, Amigo!
Ah, Bridget, Annie, lunch!
Fish and chips!
Yes, lunch, Hector.
Look Bridget, fifty kilometres.
Oh, Annie,
the dog is in the ov-en.
What?
Oh!
Hi, everything OK?
Gr-eat!
Pouf!
I am, how do you say?
Dead!
Hot.
Hot.Yeah,
I am hot, I need a ..
… Shower.
Yeah, I need a shower.
Be my guest!
Oh, thank you.
Right, that’s it!
He must go!
Why?
He is so nice.
He used my bike!
Oh!
Yeah, and he said that
the dog was in the oven!
What a horrible joke!
Where is Charley?
Charley!
What a bad, bad boy.
He must go!
Can he stay with you, Nick?
Ah-ah, sorry ladies.
Oh please Nick,
you have a spare room.
No way, not my problem.
He must go now!
But he’s in the shower.
I don’t care!
Hector, please come out,
we want to talk to you.
I like fish and ships, I …
Hector, please come out,
we want to talk to you.
OK, one moment please!
I like fish and chips!
Yes, you want me.
We think we...
… We, we,
we have a problem.
It’s like this.
Go on then, tell him.
Yes, Bridget
Hector, the thing is …
Stay there, I’ll talk to him.
Hector, can I have a word please?
Oh …
Ricky Martin!
Hector, is this you?
Yes, and my parents.
The Romero family.
One of the richest families
in Argentina.
Who are these?
My …
… Servants.
Yeah, my servants.
Your cars?
Yeah, my cars.
Hector, you are rich!
Why stay here?
I want friends, good friends
People like you for your money?
That’s awful!
[Erm] listen, keep it a secret. Sshh.
OK!
Perhaps he could stay here.
Yes – poor boy
Shut up, Nick.
Hector will stay with us,
won’t you, Hector.
Hector, come and – sit down.
Hector please, call me Gigi!
Oh, Charley, there you are.
Oh Annie, the dog is in the ov-en.
The oven?
Yes, Nick is a good English teacher.
Yes, a very good English teacher!
I’d love to see your photos again.
Oh, me too!
Oh, your sweet toy cars!
They are not toys!
Today Hector arrives and
it’s Bonfire Night.
Let’s party!
What sort of music do you like?
Music?
Yeah, music, you know,
soul, funk, dance.
Watch me, like this.
Interesting.
I dance – like this. [Oh!].
I’ll get it, I’ll get it.
Hello.
Oh, yeah, that’s great,
sure, come up.
It’s the landlady!
The tarantula!
Quick, hide, Hector.
I’m off,
I owe two week’s rent!
Aaah!!
Next time in EXTRA –
the flat mates go shopping for Hector.
Hector goes shopping for the girls.
But what happens when Hector
goes shopping for himself?
EXTRA – don’t miss it!