The One Where It All Began
English Subtitles by
GELULA & CO., INC.
There's nothing to tell.
It's just some guy I work with.
You're going out with a guy.
There's gotta be something
wrong with him.
All right, Joey, be nice.
So does he have a hump
and a hair piece?
Wait. Does he eat chalk?
I don't want her to go
through what I did with Carl.
Okay, everybody relax.
Relax. This is not even a date.
It's just two people going out to
dinner and not having sex.
Sounds like a date to me.
I'm in high school,
in the middle of the cafeteria. . .
. . .and I realize I'm totally naked.
I've had that dream.
Then I look down and I realize
there is a phone. . .
. . .there.
-Instead of--
-That's right!
That one, I've never had.
All of a sudden,
the phone starts to ring.
I don't know what to do.
Everybody's looking at me.
They weren't looking at you before?
Finally, I figure
I'd better answer it.
And it turns out it's my mother.
Which is very, very weird
because she never calls me.
This guy says, ''Hello,''
I wanna kill myself.
You okay, sweetie?
I feel like someone grabbed my small
intestine, pulled it out of my mouth. . .
-. . .and tied it around my neck.
-Cookie?
Carol moved out today.
-Let me get you some coffee.
-Thanks.
No, don't!
Stop cleansing my aura.
Just leave my aura alone, okay?
Fine. Be murky.
I'll be fine.
I hope she'll be very happy.
No, you don't.
To hell with her. She left me!
And you never knew she was a lesbian.
Why does everyone
keep fixating on that?
She didn't know.
How should I know?
Sometimes I wish I was a lesbian.
Did I say that out loud?
I told Mom and Dad last night.
They seemed to take it well.
Really? So that hysterical call I got
from a woman sobbing at 3 a.m. . .
. . . ''I'll never have grandchildren! ''
Was, what? A wrong number?
Sorry.
Look, you're feeling
a lot of pain right now.
You're angry. You're hurting.
Can I tell you what
the answer is?
Strip joints!
Come on, you're single.
Have some hormones.
See, but I don't want
to be single, okay?
I just want to be married again.
And I just want a million dollars!
Rachel?
Oh, God, Monica!
Hi! Thank God!
I went to your building and
this guy with a hammer said. . .
. . .that you might be here and you are.
-Can I get you some coffee?
-Decaf.
Everybody, this is Rachel,
another Lincoln High survivor.
This is everybody.
Chandler and Phoebe. . .
. . .and Joey. And remember
my brother, Ross?
Sure!
You want to tell us now, or are we
waiting for four wet bridesmaids?
Oh, God! Well, it started about
a half-hour before the wedding.
I was in this room with
all the presents. . .
. . .and I was looking
at this gravy boat.
This really gorgeous
Limoges gravy boat.
When all of a sudden I realize--
Sweet 'N Low?
I realized. . .
. . .I was more turned on by
this gravy boat than by Barry.
And then I really freaked out,
when it hit me:
How much Barry looks like
Mr. Potato Head.
I always knew he looked
familiar, but. . . .
I had to get out of there,
and I started wondering. . .
. . . ''Why am I doing this?''
and ''Who am I doing this for?''
I didn't know where to go, and I know
you and I have drifted apart. . .
. . .but you're the only person
I know in the city.
Who wasn't asked to the wedding.
I was kind of hoping that
wouldn't be an issue.
I guess he bought her
the pipe organ. . .
. . .and she's really not
happy about it.
''Tuna or egg salad?''
''Decide! ''
''I'll have whatever
Christine is having. ''
Daddy, I just--
I can't marry him.
I'm sorry.
I just don't love him.
Well, it matters to me!
''If I let go of my hair,
my head will fall off. ''
She should not be
wearing those pants.
I say push her down the stairs!
Push her down the stairs!
Come on, Daddy, listen!
All my life, everyone's
always told me, ''You're a shoe! ''
''You're a shoe! You're a shoe!
You're a shoe! ''
I stopped and said,
''What if I don't wanna be a shoe?
What if I want to be a purse?
Or a hat?''
I don't want you to buy me a hat,
I--
It's a metaphor, Daddy!
You can see where he'd have trouble.
Look, Daddy, it's my life.
Well, maybe I'll just stay
here with Monica.
I guess we've established
she's staying with Monica.
Well, maybe that's my decision.
Well, maybe I don't need your money.
Wait! Wait! I said maybe!
Just breathe.
Breathe, that's it.
Just try to think
of nice, calm things.
Raindrops on roses
And whiskers on kittens
Doorbells and sleigh bells
And something with mittens
La la la something
And noodles with string
-These are a--
-I'm all better now.
I helped.
This is probably for
the best, you know?
Independence.
Taking control of your life.
The whole ''hat'' thing.
If you need anything,
you can always come to Joey.
Me and Chandler live across the hall.
And he's away a lot.
Joey, stop hitting on her!
It's her wedding day.
What? Like there's
a rule or something?
I got it.
Please don't do that again.
It's a horrible sound.
It's Paul.
Oh, God. Is it 6:30?
Buzz him in.
-Who's Paul?
-Paul, the wine guy?
Maybe.
Your ''not a real date,''
is with Paul, the wine guy?
He finally asked you out?
It's a ''Dear Diary'' moment.
Rach, I can cancel.
Oh, God. Please, no.
Go, I'll be fine.
Ross are you okay?
Do you want me to stay?
That'd be good.
-Really?
-Go on! It's Paul, the wine guy!
Does he sell it, drink it,
or he just complains a lot?
Hi, come in! Paul, this is. . .
. . .everybody.
Everybody, this is Paul.
-The wine guy.
-I didn't catch your name. Paul?
I'll be right back.
I've just got to go a--
A-wandering?
Change. Sit down.
Two seconds.
I just pulled out four eyelashes.
That can't be good.
Hey, Paul. Here's a little tip.
She likes it when you
rub her neck in the same spot. . .
. . .over and over again, till
it starts to get a little red.
Shut up, Joey!
Rachel, what are you
up to tonight?
I was supposed to be headed
for Aruba on my honeymoon. . .
. . .so, nothing.
Right. You're not even
getting your honeymoon.
Although, Aruba. This time of year?
Talk about your. . .
. . .big lizards.
If you don't feel
like being alone tonight. . .
. . .Joey and Chandler are
helping me with my furniture.
And we're very excited about it.
Thanks. But I'm just gonna
hang out here.
-It's been a long day.
-Okay. Sure.
Pheebs, wanna help?
I wish I could, but I don't want to.
Love is sweet as summer showers
Love is a wondrous work of art
But your love, oh, your love
Your love
Is like a giant pigeon
Crapping on my heart
Thank you!
I'm supposed to attach a bracket-y
thing to the side things. . .
. . .using a bunch of these
little worm guys.
I have no bracket-y thing.
I see no worm guys whatsoever. . .
. . .and I cannot feel my legs.
We got a bookcase here.
It's a beautiful thing.
What's this?
I would have to say that is
an L-shaped bracket.
-Which goes where?
-I have no idea.
-Done with the bookcase.
-All finished.
This was Carol's favorite beer.
She always drank it out of the can.
I should have known.
If you start with that,
we're out of here.
Please don't spoil all this fun.
Let me ask you a question.
She got the furniture,
the stereo, the good TV.
What did you get?
You guys.
-You got screwed.
-Oh, my God.
-I know. I'm such an idiot.
I should've caught on when she went to
the dentist four and five times a week.
I mean, how clean can teeth get?
My brother's going through that.
He's a mess.
How did you get through it?
He might try accidentally breaking
something valuable of hers.
-Say her--
-Leg?
That's one way of going through it.
Me, I went for the watch.
You actually broke her watch?
The worst thing I ever did was. . .
. . .I shredded my old boyfriend's
favorite bath towel.
-Steer clear of you!
-That's right.
Barry, I'm sorry.
I am so sorry.
You probably think it's about making
love with your socks on, but it isn't.
It's about me.
And I just--
Machine cut me off again.
Anyway. . . .
I know that some girl is going to be
lucky to become Mr. Barry Finkel.
But it isn't me.
It's not me.
Not that I have any idea who ''me'' is
right now, but give me a chance to--
I'm divorced!
I'm only 26 and I'm divorced.
Shut up.
That only took me an hour.
Between us, we haven't had a
relationship last longer than a Mento.
You, however, have had the love
of a woman for four years.
Four years of closeness and sharing.
After which,
she ripped your heart out. . .
. . .and that is why we don't do it.
I don't think that was my point.
You know what's scary? What if there
is only one woman for everybody?
I mean, what if you get one
woman, and that's it?
Unfortunately, in my case,
there was only one woman for her.
What are you talking about?
One woman.
That's like saying there's only
one flavor of ice cream for you.
Let me tell you something.
There's lots of flavors out there.
Rocky road, and cookie dough,
and bing cherry vanilla.
You can get them with jimmies,
or nuts, or whipped cream.
This is the best thing that
ever happened to you!
You got married. You were
like, what? Eight?
Welcome back to the world.
Grab a spoon!
I honestly don't know
if I'm hungry or horny.
Then stay out of my freezer.
Ever since she
walked out on me, I. . . .
What? What?
You wanna spell it out with noodles?
It's more of a fifth date
kind of revelation.
So there's going to be a fifth date?
Isn't there?
Yeah, yeah. I think there is.
What were you going to say?
Ever since she left me. . .
. . .I haven't been able to perform. . .
. . .sexually.
Oh, God! Oh, God!
I'm so sorry.
Being spit on is probably
not what you need right now.
How long?
Two years.
I'm glad you smashed her watch.
So you still think you might
want that fifth date?
Yeah, I do.
We are gathered here
to join together...
...Joanie Louise Cunningham...
...and Charles Chachi,
Chachi, Chachi...
...in the bonds of holy matrimony.
-Marriage is the most sacred--
-See!
But Joanie loved Chachi.
That's the difference.
''Grab a spoon. ''
Do you know long it's been
since I grabbed a spoon?
Do the words, ''Billy, don't be a
hero,'' mean anything to you?
Great story. But I gotta go.
I got a date with Andrea.
Angela. Andrea. Oh, man.
Andrea's the screamer.
Angela has cats.
Right, thanks. It's Julie.
I'm out of here.
You know, here's the thing. Even if
I could get it together enough. . .
. . .to ask a woman out. . .
. . .who am I going to ask?
Isn't this amazing?
I have never made coffee
before in my life.
-That is amazing.
-Congratulations.
I figure if I can make coffee,
there isn't anything I can't do.
I think it's, ''If I can invade Poland,
there isn't anything I can't do. ''
If you feel like you gotta make
a Western omelet or something. . . .
Although, actually
I'm really not that hungry.
Oh, good.
Lenny and Squiggy are here.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
-Morning, Paul.
-Hello, Paul.
-Hi. Paul, is it?
Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
-Stop!
Last night was like. . .
. . .all my birthdays, graduations, plus
the barn-raising scene in Witness.
We'll talk later.
Thank you.
That wasn't a real date.
What the hell do you do
on a real date?
Shut up and put my table back.
I've got to get to work.
If I don't input those numbers,
it doesn't make much of a difference.
So, like, you guys all have jobs?
Yeah, we all have jobs.
That's how we buy stuff.
Yeah, I'm an actor.
Have I seen you in anything?
I doubt it.
Mostly regional work.
Unless you happen to catch the
Wee One's production of Pinocchio...
. . .at the Little Theater in the Park.
It was a job, all right?
''Look, Geppeto. I'm a real live boy. ''
I will not take this abuse.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Once I was a wooden boy
A little wooden boy
You should both know that
he's a dead man.
Oh, Chandler!
How are you doing today?
You sleep okay?
Did you talk to Barry?
I can't stop smiling.
I see that. You look like you
slept with a hanger in your mouth.
I know. He's just so--
Remember you and Tony De Marco?
Well, it's like that.
With feelings.
-Are you in trouble!
-Big time!
Want a wedding dress?
Hardly used.
We're getting a little
ahead of ourselves here.
I'm going to get up, go to work,
and not think about him all day.
Or else I'm just going
to get up and go to work.
-Wish me luck!
-What for?
I'm gonna go get one
of those job things.
-Hey, Monica.
-Hey, Franny. Welcome back.
How was Florida?
You had sex, didn't you?
How do you do that?
I hate you. I'm pushing my
aunt through Parrot Jungle. . .
. . .and you're having sex.
So, who?
You know Paul?
Paul, the wine guy?
Yeah, I know Paul.
You mean, you know Paul
like I know Paul?
Are you kidding?
I take credit for Paul.
Before me, there was no snap in his
turtle for two years.
Of course it was a line.
Why? Why would anybody
do something like that?
We're looking for an answer
more sophisticated than. . .
. . . ''To get you into bed. ''
I hate men. I hate men!
Don't hate. Don't put that out
in the universe.
Is it me?
Is it like I have some sort of
beacon that only dogs. . .
. . .and men with emotional
problems can hear?
Come here.
Give me your feet.
I just thought he was
nice, you know?
I can't believe you
didn't know it was a line.
Guess what?
-You got a job?
-Are you kidding?
I'm trained for nothing.
I was laughed out of 12 interviews.
You're surprisingly upbeat.
You would be too if you found
Joan and David boots on sale. . .
. . .50% percent off.
How well you know me.
They're my, ''I don't need
a job or my parents.
I've got great boots,'' boots.
-How did you pay for them?
-Credit card.
And who pays for that?
My father.
Come on, is this necessary?
I can stop charging any time I want.
You can't live off your parents.
I know that. That's why
I was getting married.
Give her a break. It's hard being
on your own for the first time.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
When I first came to
this city, I was 1 4.
My mom had killed herself
and my stepdad was in prison.
And I got here,
and I didn't know anybody.
I ended up living with this albino
guy who was cleaning windshields.
And then he killed himself.
Then I found aromatherapy. Believe
me, I know exactly how you feel.
The word you're looking for is:
''Anyway. . . . ''
You ready?
No, I'm not ready.
How can I be ready?
''You ready to jump out of
the plane without a chute?''
I can't do this.
-I know you can.
-I don't think so.
You made coffee.
You can do anything.
Cut, cut, cut.
You know what?
We can just leave it at that.
Like a symbolic gesture.
That was a library card.
If you listen very closely, you can
hear a thousand retailers scream.
Welcome to the real world!
It sucks.
You're gonna love it.
That's it.
You gonna crash on the couch?
-No, I gotta go home sometime.
-Are you gonna be okay?
Look what I just
found on the floor.
What?
That's Paul's watch.
You can just put it back
where you found it.
Oh, boy! All right.
-Good night, everybody.
-Good night.
-I'm sorry.
-No!
-No, have it, really.
-Split it?
You probably didn't know this,
but back in high school I had. . .
. . .a major crush on you.
I knew.
You did?
I figured you thought I was
Monica's geeky older brother.
I did.
Listen, do you think--
And try not to let my vulnerability
become any kind of a factor here.
Do you think it would be okay if
I asked you out sometime, maybe?
Maybe.
Okay, maybe I will.
-Good night.
See you.
Wait, wait.
What's with you?
I just grabbed a spoon.
I can't believe what
I'm hearing.
I can 't believe
What I'm hearing
-What? I said you had--
Would you stop?
Was I doing it again?
I said that you had a nice butt.
It's just not a great butt.
You wouldn't know a great
butt if it bit you.
There's an image.
Would anybody like more coffee?
Did you make it?
-I'm just serving it.
-I'll have a cup of coffee.
Kids, new dream.
I'm in Las Vegas.
Miss, more coffee?
Excuse me? Could you give this
to that guy over there?
Go ahead.
Thank you.
Sorry. Okay, Las Vegas.
So I'm in Las Vegas.
I'm Liza Minnelli.
www.tvsubtitles.net
No, no, we're done!
The One With the Dozen Lasagnas
English Subtitles by
GELULA & CO., INC.
Aunt Silv, stop yelling!
If you'd told me
vegetarian lasagna. . .
. . .I would've made
vegetarian lasagna.
The meat's only every third layer.
Maybe you could scrape.
Ross, did you really read
all these baby books?
You could plunk me down in
any woman's uterus, no compass. . .
. . .and I could find my way
out like that!
This is cool.
It says in some parts of the world
people eat the placenta.
And we're done with the yogurt.
Sorry.
Aunt Silv, I did this as a favor.
I am not a caterer.
What do you want me to do
with a dozen lasagnas?
Nice talk, Aunt Silv.
You kiss Uncle Freddie
with that mouth?
Ross, listen.
Do you know that right now
your baby is only this big?
This is your baby.
''Hi, Daddy. ''
Hello.
''How come you don't live with Mommy?''
''How come Mommy lives
with that other lady?''
''What's a lesbian?''
Honey, you can say it.
It's Poconos. Poconos.
It's like ''poke a nose. ''
Poke a nose.
So did I hear ''Poconos''?
My sister's giving us her place
for the weekend.
First weekend away together.
-Yeah, it's a big step.
-I know.
It's just a weekend.
Big deal.
Wasn't this supposed to be
just a fling?
Shouldn't it be. . .
. . .flung by now?
We are way past the ''fling'' thing.
I'm feeling things I've only
read about in Danielle Steel books.
When I'm with him,
I'm just totally, totally. . . .
Nauseous.
I'm physically nauseous.
What am I supposed to do?
Call Immigration?
I could call Immigration.
I love babies with
their little baby shoes. . .
. . .and their little baby toes
and their little hands. . . .
You're gonna have to stop that. . .
. . .forever.
Need a new table.
You think?
-Come on in.
-Hello.
I brought the books. . .
. . .and Monica sends her love
along with this lasagna.
Great!
Is it vegetarian?
Because Susan doesn't eat meat.
I'm pretty sure that it is.
So I got the results
of the amnio today.
Tell me.
Is everything. . .?
Totally and completely healthy.
That's great! That is great!
When did you and Susan
meet Huey Lewis?
That's our friend Tanya.
Of course, it's your friend Tanya.
Don't you wanna know
about the sex?
The sex?
I'm having enough trouble with
the image of you and Susan together.
But when you throw in Tanya. . . .
The sex of the baby, Ross.
You know it?
Do you want to know?
I don't want to know.
Absolutely not.
I think you shouldn't know until
you look down there. . .
. . .and see,
''Oh, there it is. . . ''
. . .or isn't.
-Hello, Ross.
-Susan.
So?
So did you hear?
Yes, we did.
Everything's A-OK.
Oh, that's so cool!
It really is.
Do we know?
We certainly do.
It's going to be a--
Hello?
A guy who doesn't wanna know
is standing here.
Well, is it what
we thought it would be?
What. . .?
What did we think it'd be?
I don't want to know.
Don't want to know.
I should probably just go.
-Well, thanks for the books.
-No problem.
Susan.
Who should we call first?
Your folks or Deb and Rhona?
Never mind.
I don 't wanna know.
So just because it was my table,
I have to buy a new one?
That's the rule.
What rule?
There's no rule.
If anything, you owe me a table.
How did you get that?
This piece of furniture
was fine. . .
. . .until your breakfast adventure
with Angela Delveccio.
You knew about that?
The impressions you made in the butter
left little to the imagination.
How about if we split it?
What do you mean,
like, buy it together?
Do you think we're ready for that?
Why not?
It's a big commitment.
What if one of us wants to move out?
-Are you moving out?
-I'm not moving out.
You'd tell me if you were?
-It's just, with my last roommate--
-I know all about Kip.
We bought a hibachi together,
then he ran off and got married. . .
. . .and things got ugly.
Let me ask you something.
Was Kip a better roommate than me?
Don't do that.
You've got a couple changes
in your schedule.
Your 4:00 herbal massage
has been pushed back to 4:30.
And Ms. Summerfield
canceled her 5:30 shiatsu.
Thanks.
Here comes your 3:00.
I don't mean to sound
unprofessional, but-- Yum!
Paolo! Hi!
What are you doing here?
Rachella tell me you. . .
. . .massage?
Well, Rachella's right.
I don't know what you said,
so let's start.
I am. . .
. . .being naked?
That's your decision.
Some people prefer to take off--
Being naked!
I can't believe you don't want to know.
I couldn't not know.
If the doctor knows,
and Carol knows, and Susan knows--
And Monica knows.
How could you?
I don't even know.
Carol called to thank me
for the lasagna.
I asked. She told me.
So what's it going to be?
Great! Now he knows
and I don't know.
I'm sorry. I'm excited
about being an aunt.
Or an uncle.
Fine!
What's the matter?
Nothing! I'm sorry.
I'm just, I'm out of sorts.
Can we get some
cappuccino over here?
Oh, right! That's me!
That table place closes at 7. Come on.
Fine.
What is it?
You know Paolo?
I'm familiar with his work.
He made a move on me.
-The store'll be open tomorrow.
-More coffee.
What happened?
He came in for a massage. . .
...and everything was fine until....
My God!
Are you sure?
Oh, yeah. I'm sure.
And all of a sudden, his hands
weren't the problem anymore.
Was it. . .?
Boy Scouts could've
camped under there.
''Ooh,'' what?
--ma Thurman.
-The actress!
-Uma Thurman!
Thanks, Rach.
-What'll you do?
-You have to tell her.
You have to! It's your
moral obligation as a friend. . .
. . .as a woman.
It's a feminist issue.
Guys? Guys?
You have to tell her.
Feminist issue?
That's where I went.
She is gonna hate me!
Will you pick one?
Just pick one.
Here, how about that one?
That's patio furniture.
So what?
Like people will come in and think,
''Uh-oh, I'm outside again. ''
Fine.
What about the birds?
I don't know.
Birds just don't say. . .
. . . ''Hello, sit here. Eat something. ''
You pick one.
How about the ladybugs?
So forget about the birds, but
big red insects suggest fine dining?
Fine! Do you want the birds?
Get the birds!
Not like that, I won't.
Kip would've liked the birds.
Hi, Pheebs.
Are you moving out?
No, these aren't all
of my suitcases.
This one's Paolo's.
Rachel, can we talk for a sec?
Sure.
Just for a sec, because Paolo's
on his way over.
We haven't known each other
for that long a time.
There are three things
you should know about me.
One, my friends are the most
important thing in my life.
Two, I never lie.
And three, I make the best
oatmeal raisin cookies in the world.
Thanks, Pheebs.
My God!
Why have I never tasted these before?
I don't make them a lot, because
it's not fair to the other cookies.
You're right. These are
the best oatmeal raisin cookies.
Which proves that I never lie.
I guess you don't.
Paolo made a pass at me.
So what do you think?
It's the most beautiful table
I've ever seen.
I know.
So will you balance the plates
on these little heads?
Who cares?
We'll eat at the sink.
Come on!
Heads up, Ross.
Score!
You suck!
Are you okay?
I need some milk.
I've got milk.
Here you go.
Better?
I feel so stupid!
I think about the other day
with you guys.
And I was all,
''Oh, Paolo! He's so great!
He makes me feel so--''
God!
I'm so embarrassed!
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm the one he hit on.
Phoebe, I pushed him on you.
If I had never met him,
this would never--
-I'm so sorry.
-No, I'm sorry.
Wait!
-What are we sorry about?
-I don't know.
Right. He's the pig.
-Such a pig!
-Oh, God, he's such a pig!
He's like a big disgusting pig. . . .
-Pig man!
-Yes, good!
But he was my pig man!
How did I not see this?
Oh, I know!
Because. . .
. . .he's gorgeous.
And he's charming.
And the way he looks at you--
The end.
God!
Should I not have told you?
Trust me, it's much better
that I know.
But I just liked it better before.
It was better.
I think she took it pretty well.
Paolo's over there right now, so. . . .
We should go
and see if she's okay.
Just one second.
Score!
Game! Us!
Come on.
It looks like
we kicked your butts.
She kicked our butts.
You could be on the Olympic
''Standing There'' team.
Come on. Two on one.
Why are you still here?
She just broke up with him.
It's time for you to swoop in.
What, now?
Now is when you swoop.
When Paolo walks out of there,
you gotta be the first guy she sees.
She's got to know
you're everything he's not.
You're like the anti-Paolo.
My Catholic friend is right.
She's distraught.
You're there for her.
You pick up the pieces, and then
you usher in. . .
. . . ''The Age of Ross. ''
Hold it! Ascolta!
-How's it going?
-Don't stare.
She finished throwing
his clothes off the balcony.
Now there's just
gesturing and arm-waving.
That is either, ''How could you?''
or ''Enormous breasts! ''
Here he comes.
I am. . .
. . .to say goodbye.
Okay, bye-bye.
I hate you
for what you did to Rachel.
But I still have five of these. . .
. . .so heat it at 375
untiI the cheese bubbles.
I just wanna tell you. . .
. . .and I think I'd speak
for everyone when I say. . . .
Just look at her.
Guys, I think only one of us
should go out there. . .
-. . .so she's not overwhelmed.
-Right.
And I really think it should be me.
You all right?
I've been better.
Come here.
Listen. . .
. . .you deserve
so much better than him.
I mean, you. . .
. . .you should be with a guy who knows
what he has when he has you.
What?
I'm so sick of guys!
I don't want to look
at another guy.
I don't want to think
about another guy.
I don't even want
to be near another guy.
Ross, you're so great.
-Are you all right?
-Are you okay?
Medium.
Any cookies left?
See, Rach. . .
. . .I don't think swearing off guys
altogether is the answer.
What you need is to develop a more
sophisticated screening process.
I just need to be
by myself for a while.
I just gotta
figure out what I want.
See, because not all guys out there
are gonna be a Paolo.
No, I know. I know.
And I'm sure your little boy's
not gonna grow up to be one.
What?
I'm having a boy?
No. In fact,
you're not having a boy.
I'm having a boy.
Am I having a boy?
You're having a boy!
I'm having a boy!
-What?
-What is it?
I'm having a boy!
We already knew that!
I'm having a son.
And that would be a shutdown!
Shutout!
Where you guys going?
Come on, one more game!
It's 2:30 in the morning.
Get out!
You guys are always hanging out
in my apartment.
Come on, I'll only use
my left hand.
Come on, wussies!
All right! Okay!
I gotta go!
I'm going.
And I'm gone.
One more game?
www.tvsubtitles.net
Here's little Ben nodding off.
Look at Aunt Monica's Little boy.
-Look, he's got Ross' hair cut.
-Let me see.
Oh, God!
Is he just the sweetest thing?
You must just want
to kiss him all over.
That would be nice.
Pardon?
Nothing. Just a Little
extra air in my mouth.
Chan, can you help me out here?
I promise I'II pay you back.
Yeah, right.
Including the waffles last week. . .
. . .you now owe me. . .
. . . 17 jillion dollars.
Really, I'II pay you back this time.
Where's the money coming from?
I'm helping out at the NYU
Med School with some research.
What kind of research?
Just, you know, science.
Science.
Yeah, I think I've heard of that.
It's a fertility study.
Please tell me you're only
donating your time.
Come on, you guys.
It's not that big a deal.
I just go down there
every other day. . .
. . .and make my contribution
to the project.
But at the end of two weeks,
I get $ 700!
You're gonna be making money
hand over fist.
The One Where Rachel Finds Out
English Subtitles by
GELULA & CO., INC.
Okay, we got the coleslaw.
We got the buns.
We've got the ground-up flesh
of formally cute cows and turkeys.
Men are here!
We make fire.
Cook meat.
Then put out fire by peeing,
no get invited back!
Cute, cute!
Joey, Melanie called.
She's gonna be late.
So how are things going?
Is she becoming your special someone?
I don't know.
She's pretty great.
What does she think of
your Little science project?
You think I'd tell a girl I like
that I'm also seeing a cup?
The man's got a point.
The tough thing is, she really wants
to have sex with me.
Crazy bitch!
I got a week left in the program,
and according to the rules. . .
. . .to get the money, I can't conduct
any personal experiments. . .
. . .if you know what I mean.
Joey, we always know what you mean.
How long did you think
this barbecue was gonna Last?
I'm going to China.
Jeez, you say one thing and. . . .
You're going to China?
It's for the museum.
Someone found a bone.
They don't want us
to have the bone.
So I'm going to try to persuade them--
It's a whole big bone thing.
Anyway, I'm gonna be gone for a week.
So if you wanna reach me, you can't.
So here's my itinerary.
-Here's a picture of me.
-Oh, let me see.
Could you show it to Ben now and then
so he doesn't forget me?
Hi, Ben.
I'm your father.
I am The Head!
This barbecue's gonna be fun.
Is Rachel here? I wanted to wish her
a happy birthday before I Left.
She's out having drinks with Carl.
Hey, who's Carl?
You know, that guy she met
at the coffeehouse.
-See, there's this guy she met at--
-The coffeehouse? Right.
So you do know who he is.
I'm gonna go say goodbye
to the guys.
You know what?
Tell them that bone story.
-I have to go to China.
-The country?
No, this big pile of dishes
in my mom's breakfront.
Do you guys know who Carl is?
Let's see.
Alvin, Simon, Theodore. . . .
Rachels having
drinks with him tonight.
How can she, when she's never
shown interest in you?
Forget about her.
He's right, man. Please move on.
Go to China. Eat Chinese food.
Of course, there,
they just call it food.
I guess. I don't know.
AII right, just give her this
for me, okay?
We're just looking out for you.
We want you to be happy.
And I may only have a couple beers
in me, but I love you, man.
I'm still on my first.
I just think you're nice.
That's when me and my friends
started this fruit-basket business.
We call ourselves
''The Three Basketeers. ''
Like ''The Three Musketeers,''
only with fruit.
-How do you Like your burgers?
-No. Presents first, food later!
Hold on there, tiger.
How are you holding up?
Well, not so good.
She thinks we're gonna
complete the transaction tonight. . .
. . .if you know what I--
And you do!
So have you ever thought about
being there for her?
What do you mean?
You know, just be there for her.
Not following you.
Think about it.
I'm guessing this is from. . . .
Well, thank you, Melanie.
This one right here is from me.
It's light.
It rattles.
It's. . .
. . .Travel Scrabble!
Thank you.
This one's from Joey.
It feels Like a book.
I think it's a book.
And it's a book!
It's Dr. Seuss!
That book got me through
some tough times.
There is a Little child
inside this man.
The doctors say if they remove it,
he'll die!
-Who's this from?
-That's Ross' .
Oh, my God!
He remembered!
Remembered what?
It was months ago.
We were walking by this antique store,
and I saw this pin.
I told him it was just Like one
my grandmother had when I was Little.
I can't believe he remembered!
Well, sure, but can you
play it on a plane?
It's so pretty!
This must've cost him a fortune.
I can't believe he did this.
Remember when he
fell in Love with Carol. . .
. . .and bought her that ridiculously
expensive crystal duck?
What did you say?
Crystal duck.
The ''Love'' part?
Oh, my God!
That's good.
Just keep rubbing your head.
That'll turn back time.
This is unbelievable.
I mean, this is unbelievable!
I know.
This is really, really huge!
No, it's not. It's small,
it's tiny, it's petite, it's wee.
I don't think any of our lives
will ever be the same ever again!
Is there a mute button
on this woman?
I think this is so great!
I mean, you and Ross!
Did you have any idea?
No, none!
My first night in the city,
he mentioned asking me out. . .
. . .but nothing ever happened,
so I just. . . .
What else did he say?
Does he want to go out with me?
Given that he's desperately
in Love with you. . .
. . .he wouldnt mind getting
a cup of coffee or something.
Ross?
AII this time?
-I've gotta talk to him.
-He's in China!
The country.
Wait, his flight doesn't leave
for 45 minutes.
-What about the time difference?
-From here to the airport?
-You're never gonna make it!
-I've got to try.
What'll you say to him?
I don't know.
Then maybe you shouldnt go.
Right, because if you're gonna
break his heart, that can wait.
But if it's good news,
tell him now.
Maybe I'II know when I see him.
Here, look.
AII right, does this help?
AII I know is, I cannot wait a week.
This is just too big.
I've just got to talk to him.
I've got--
I'II see you Later.
I Love you!
Deal with me first!
AII right.
Excuse me, pardon me.
Your boarding pass?
I don't have one.
I need to talk to my friend.
Sorry, you're not allowed on
the jetway without a boarding pass.
He's right there,
in the blue jacket! Can I just--?
I'm sorry.
Federal regulations!
AII right, then could you please
just give him a message for me?
This is very important.
AII right.
What's the message?
I don't know.
Excuse me! Sir!
Excuse me! Sir?
I have a message for you.
Rachel said she loved the present.
She'll see you when you get back.
What?
Toby, I don't know
what she's talking about.
There's no Rachel!
Don't give me that deep freeze!
Oh, Joey, Joey, Joey!
I think I blacked out there
for a minute.
It was nothing.
Well, now we gotta
find something fun for you!
You know what?
Forget about me.
Let's give you another turn.
Me, again?
Sure. Why not?
Boy! Somebody's gonna get
a big fruit basket tomorrow!
I gotta tell you, you are nothing Like
I thought you would be.
How do you mean?
I just had you pegged as one of those
guys who are always, ''Me, me, me! ''
But you. . .
. . .you're a giver.
You're, Like, the most generous
man I ever met.
I mean, you're practically a woman.
So Rach, do you want to save
this wrapping paper?
It's only a Little torn.
Are you gonna go for it with Ross,
or should I throw it out?
I don't know.
I thought about it
all of the way there. . .
. . .and I thought about it
all the way back and. . . .
You know, it's Ross!
You know what I mean?
It's Ross.
-Sure!
-Sure.
I don't know. This is just
my initial gut feeling. . .
. . .but I'm thinking. . .
. . .it'd be really great.
Oh, my God, me too!
We'd be Like friends-in-law!
The best part is you already
know all about him.
It's Like starting on the 1 5th date.
But it would be Like
starting on the 1 5th date.
Another good point.
At the 1 5th date, you're already
in a ''relationship-py'' place.
You're committed.
What happens if it doesn't work out?
Why isn't it working out?
Sometimes it doesn't.
Is he not cute enough for you?
Does he not make enough money?
No, I'm just--
Maybe there's someone else.
Is there?
Is there someone else?
No, there is no one else.
Then why the hell
are you dumping my brother?
Hey, big--
Spender!
She's still asleep.
-So how'd it go?
-It was amazing!
You know how you think
you're great in bed?
The fact you'd even ask
shows how Little you know me.
Well, Last night
I couldnt do the thing. . .
. . .that usually makes me great.
So I had to do
all this other stuff.
And the response I got!
Man, oh, man!
It was Like
a ticker-tape parade!
I know. My room's very close
to the parade route.
It was amazing,
and not just for her.
For me too!
It's Like, all of a sudden
I'm blind. . .
. . .but all my other senses
are heightened.
You know? It's Like,
I was able to appreciate it. . .
. . .on another level.
I didn't know you had
another Level.
I know. Neither did I!
Hey, great skirts!
Birthday present?
-From who?
-From you!
I exchanged the blouse
you got me.
Well, it's the thought.
Doesn't Ross' flight get in
in a couple hours?
At gate 27B?
I've been thinking about it.
I've decided this Ross thing
is not a good idea.
Why?
Because I feel Like I wouldnt
just be going out with him.
I would be going out with
all of you.
There'd be all this pressure and--
No pressure, no pressure!
Nothing has even happened yet
and you're already so--
I'm not ''so. ''
I was a teensy bit weird at first. . .
. . .but I'II be good.
I promise.
Who is it?
It's me, Carl.
Come on up.
Behind my brother's back?
Is the kind of crazy thing
you won't be hearing from me.
Seven hundred bucks!
AII right, you did it!
Do we have any fruit?
Man! A hell of a two weeks.
You know what, though?
I really feel I learned something.
So you'll stick with this
''it's all for her'' thing?
What, are you crazy?
When a blind man gets his sight back,
does he walk around Like this?
I'm just saying, if I see one more
picture of Ed Begley Jr. . .
. . .in that stupid electric car. . .
. . .I'II shoot myself!
Don't get me wrong. I'm not against
environmental issues, per se. . .
. . .it's just that guy!
I can't believe you'd rather
go out with him than me.
Excuse me, please.
I'm trying to have a date here.
Fine, just stop thinking about me.
Can't do it, can you?
So I'm thinking about you.
So what?
I don't get it. What do you see
in this guy anyway?
Well, he seems to be
a very nice guy.
I mean, come on, buddy!
Get a real car!
Rachel, come on.
Give us a chance.
It's too hard.
Because it'll get weird
for everyone else?
Who cares?
This is about us.
I've been in Love with you
since the ninth grade.
-You're, Like, my best friend.
-I know.
If we broke up, and I lost you--
Why do you think
we'll break up?
Have you been involved with someone
where you haven't broken up?
No.
But it only has to happen once.
You and I know
we are perfect for each other.
Right?
So the only question is:
Are you attracted to me?
I don't know.
I mean, I've never looked at you
that way before.
Well start Looking!
Exactly!
And you just know
I'm gonna be the guy. . .
. . .caught behind this hammerhead
in traffic!
Right!
You're right!
You know what?
I forgot, I need to pick up
a friend at the airport.
I am so sorry!
If you want to stay
and finish your drinks, please do.
I'm sorry, I gotta go.
I'm sorry!
But. . . .
Excuse me! Pardon me!
I'm sorry.
Toby. . .
. . .for God's sake,
will you Let it go?
There's no Rachel!
I got that!
-Thanks, sweetie.
-No problem.
I cannot wait
for you to meet my friends!
Really? You don't think
they'll judge and ridicule me?
No, they will.
I just. . . .
-Can't wait!
Come on, they're gonna Love you.
www.tvsubtitles.net