_
♪ Hey, welcome back, my friends ♪
♪ Here's where our season ends ♪
♪ It's getting heavy
now on "Galavant" ♪
Enough!
Tensions are high, and maybe take five?
Sorry. I was just catching people up.
All right, gang.
I realize now that I've been going about
getting us out of here the wrong way.
I was thinking of big, strong hero moves,
but, um...
Well, I think that was just ego stuff.
So I've come up with a plan
that involves gaining
King Richard's confidence
using my wits.
We believe in you, Galavant. We trust you.
- Right, everyone?
- Mm...
No, he's got this.
Galavant's the complete package,
and I for one am finally just
throwing my arms in the air
and giving in to it.
Are they gonna kiss?
Yeah, they are.
Thank you so much.
Hi.
So, if you keep ignoring
the Russian bathhouse-like steam
surrounding you and Isabella,
you could find yourself in
the permanent friend zone.
So are you gonna, as they say...
"Kiss de girl," huh?
I don't know what's wrong with me, Sid.
This thing with her is just so big.
I feel like a kiss with Isabella
could just go on forever.
What has happened to you?
2:00. Time for lunch.
Enjoy yourselves.
You can have the fat one.
Wait a minute.
Gareth...
What?
I demand an audience with the king.
Oh, do you?
And what makes you think
he'll grant you that?
'Cause I've got some very
mean gossip about Madalena.
And you think the king's
gonna drop everything
just to hear some
scuttlebutt about some girl?
She's got feet like a 90-year-old troll.
It's delicious!
No, it's disgusting.
She's got bunions, gnarled knuckles, warts.
- No.
- Oh, yeah.
That's why she wears her socks in bed.
I haven't laughed so hard in minutes.
Anyway, the point is, we've both
been scorned by the same woman.
I just thought you'd like to know that.
Good night...
Unless you want to get a drink.
That's an interesting proposition.
Little guy time between frenemies
burnt by the same flame,
bros before hos, all that.
No, I don't think so.
The king needs to get his sleep.
Gareth, why do you always
have to poop on the party?
Maybe because you've got
to fight me to the death
in the morning,
or maybe that your brother has decided
that I'm gonna be his champion,
and for the first time ever,
you've decided to fight
one of your own battles,
and your whole kingdom's at stake.
Does that ring any bells?
Aw, you worried about me, Gar-bear?
Don't call me that.
Well, I'm so sorry if I upset you
the night before you'll probably kill me!
This sucks.
Gareth, do you remember the lullaby
Pearl used to sing to us when we were boys?
Pearl was our nanny.
Old woman, sweet face, big, gigantic boobs.
Come on, man, you must remember.
♪ Lay by my side and we'll sail away ♪
♪ Off to the shores of another day ♪
Good night.
Well, fine!
I didn't want to sing the
stupid song with you anyway!
Let's have that drink.
Shall we?
Synced and corrected by Berkersever
www.addic7ed.com
You must have felt badly.
Madalena absolutely destroyed me.
Drink up, drink up.
I couldn't get out of bed.
I didn't play my lute for weeks.
What, you think you've got it bad?
Madalena and I never even...
Well, let's just say
she never let me walk through her garden.
I don't follow.
I never pollinated her flower.
What?
Are we talking about the same Madalena?
Yes!
But you were married.
You didn't insist?
I'm not an animal.
I mean, sure, I'll kidnap a woman
and force her to marry me,
but after that, I'm all
about a woman's rights.
I'm a modern, 13th-century man.
Good for you. Cheers to that.
Thank you very much.
You know, the truth be told,
I've always sort of felt that that business
should never happen until two people
really love each other, you know?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I never loved anyone
until I loved Madalena,
and so that's why I'm...
I've never actually
walked in anyone's garden.
But you're the king.
That's right.
I am the king, so watch your mouth, boy.
I'm sorry I barked at you.
See? This is why I don't have guy friends.
Hey, it's all right, it's all right.
- You're under a lot of pressure.
- I know.
Brother's trying to steal your kingdom.
He's trying to steal your lady,
put you against your best friend.
Times are tough. Drink up.
- Here, let's... let's play a game.
- Hmm?
Let's just say there's this standing king.
And his evil, treacherous brother
comes into town,
and we wanted to sort of
"take care" of him.
I don't know, like, say, tonight.
Do you think anyone would care?
I don't follow.
Kill your brother.
What?!
Have you gone absolutely mad?
What do you expect me to do,
just sneak into Kingsley's bedchamber
and slice his throat while he sleeps?
What, in this outfit?!
Yes.
Everyone, I'm going to kill my brother!
Drinks are on me!
Right. Fill her up.
There we go.
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ oh... ♪
♪ We're off on a secret mission ♪
♪ We've got us a secret plan ♪
♪ We're going to go and slay your bro ♪
♪ As quietly as we can ♪
♪ We'll sneak up and
then surprise him ♪
♪ Before he has time to think ♪
♪ We're off and away ♪
♪ But first, another drink ♪
♪ Da-Da, Da-Da, Da, Da ♪
♪ We're off on a secret mission ♪
♪ A totally secret scheme ♪
♪ We'll slyly do in your next of kin ♪
♪ And quietly make him scream ♪
♪ We've got to be swift and stealthy ♪
♪ So none will raise a stink ♪
♪ We're off on our way,
but first, another drink ♪
♪ Da-Da, Da-Da, Da, Da ♪
♪ A secret, secret, hush, hush, hush ♪
♪ Secret, secret ♪
♪ Oh, we're off on a secret mission ♪
♪ It's some kind of secret plot ♪
♪ We're gonna go ♪
♪ yeah ♪
♪ And then... ♪
♪ exactly ♪
♪ Who are we? ♪
♪ I forgot ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, we're
gonna go kill the... ♪
♪ Someone ♪
♪ my brother! ♪
♪ The rat ♪
♪ the fink! ♪
Shh! Lower your voice!
Hey, w-what are all these dudes doing
in front of Madalena's room for?
Yeah, what is it? A party?
T-the queen's interviewing new consorts.
Next!
Oh, God. She's the worst.
Hey, you know what?
The queen is really proud of her feet.
Mm. Yeah, yeah.
Ask her to take her socks off.
Ask to kiss her feet.
That's an order from your king.
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ Secret, secret ♪
♪ 30th verse, same as the first ♪
Whoa. There's some serious
acoustics down here.
Hey, everybody!
Whoa. It looks like
someone couldn't do anything
if I went like this!
Stop it! I'm ticklish!
Hi, pretty Izzy.
Oh, you're so pretty.
But not just face, your brain.
It's like your beautiful brain
exploded all over your face.
Are you drunk?
Mommy.
Hey, I'm so excited about
Isabella getting older.
Way to keep it high and tight.
Oh, look, it's the little
stickman in the red.
- Hello.
- He remembered you!
I should have just kissed you.
I should have kissed you ages ago.
Yeah, well, um, maybe we
should talk about this tomorrow.
Okay, bye-bye.
Yes, and we will, and we're gonna kiss,
and it's gonna be one of
those forever sort of kisses.
Tell her, Sid. Didn't I say that earlier?
When I sat down over
there, I said it, didn't I?
Burned into my brain, sir.
You see?
Boop!
Okay, I've got to go kill a king.
I beg of you, sire, stop it!
Bye, everybody!
Thank you, thank you!
It was fun! You try it!
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ We're off on a secret mission ♪
♪ To finally kill my sib ♪
♪ And now that we're in his bedroom ♪
Hey, before we do this thing,
I just want to say thanks for tonight.
I really needed to get out.
Just focus!
You want to kill him in the head,
or do you want to kill him in the neck?
Right. Here we go.
Hey! Oh, and promise me
you're not gonna say anything
to anyone about that thing I said.
What thing? About me being a virgin.
I think we've heard enough.
- Oh, no.
- Oh!
My dear, little, dinky brother,
untouched by war and women.
I mean, what I meant was virgin slayer.
You're [Bleep].
Throw lover boy in a dungeon.
So mean.
Oh, and you won't be needing this.
My crown!
He stole my crown.
Keep your chin up. Don't
let them see you cry.
Never let them see you cry.
Gareth, I assume you like women.
If you fight for me, I
will give you land, a title,
and as many women as you desire.
What's your type?
Either really fat or really skinny,
nothing in between.
I'll give you fat and skinny.
I'll get back to you.
Awesome.
It was so rude!
Who does that to my favorite crown?
Did you know that? I
got it for my birthday!
- Galavant...
- Izzy, you're so pretty.
Oh, well, at least he stopped talking.
Yeah, it's great. Yeah. About time.
I failed in my mission, Gareth,
and now it's our last night
before we have to duel to the death.
Come on, let's sing Pearl's song together,
for old times' sake.
Shut up.
I've told you your whole
life to grow a pair,
and you just won't listen, and
now you're gonna die for it.
Even though I'm the one
who's gonna kill you,
it's not my fault!
It's not my fault!
I warned you!
I know you did, my friend.
♪ Lay by my side and we'll sail away ♪
♪ Off to the shores of another day ♪
♪ All set to go once I hear you say ♪
♪ "Good night, my friend,
until the morning" ♪
♪ Up we will float
as we close our eyes ♪
♪ Stars all around us, like fireflies ♪
♪ Just me and you,
drifting through the skies ♪
♪ Good night, my friend ♪
♪ Not a thought ♪
♪ Ah-ah ♪
♪ Not a care ♪
♪ Resting safe and sound ♪
♪ With each other there ♪
♪ And so we'll rock
on our nighttime ride ♪
♪ Cozy and warm on the rolling tide ♪
♪ Till we arrive on the morning side ♪
♪ At journey's end ♪
♪ Good night ♪
♪ Sleep tight ♪
♪ We're gonna be all right ♪
♪ Good night, my friend ♪
Good morning, sunshine.
Ow.
Hi.
How are you?
Oh, God. Ow.
Rough night?
I don't remember what happened.
You said her pretty brain exploded
and went all over her face.
And you tried to kiss her.
You were a bit of a mess, sir.
A big, hot mess.
Well, that's the least of our problems.
I think I might have
ruined our only chance,
and now I don't know what to do.
Good thing I do. Wake up, sire.
We've come to get you out of here.
Oh, God.
Well, I knew you cared.
Take him outside.
This place is horrible.
All right, everyone, take
only the bare essentials.
We can always pick up
odds and ends on the road.
None of you are coming, except you.
What? You're coming with me.
I'm not going anywhere, not
without everyone in here.
You don't have a choice, son.
Listen, I remember what I said last night,
and I meant every word.
I think you're the most wonderful...
I think I'm falling in love.
Nice kiss. I hope he remembers it.
Come on, you.
Galavant, no!
Please, Gareth!
Princess, as long as Galavant's alive,
we stand a chance of being rescued.
What's this?
Where am I?
These pirates will take you and the king
back to his kingdom, where he'll be safe.
What? No.
I'm not leaving her.
I'm going back.
I've left word with my men.
You step one foot in that castle
and everyone you love gets the ax.
No more games, Galavant.
Listen, Gareth, I'm moved,
but I've made my bed,
and for once, I should lie in it.
- You get in that boat.
- No, Gareth.
I know you're doing
this because you love me.
I don't love you. I don't even like you.
No one here likes you, so go.
Well, now you're just
being mean to me so I'll go.
You're self-centered,
self-absorbed,
and you wear too much velvet.
Now you're just going into
a lot of specific details,
so I'll believe you.
You have a skinny left
calf and a crooked...
Okay, okay, fine. I'll go.
But you're not fooling anyone.
Go on. And you.
Not one hair.
I give you my word.
And know this... I will return for them.
Justice will be done.
I'm excited for you,
but let me give you a
couple of instructions.
He can't sleep at night
if he ain't got a second pillow to hug.
Dairy makes him gassy.
And if he gets cross,
give him some salty snacks.
It's good for his electrolytes.
But if one hair on his head gets harmed,
I will hunt you down, I will gut you,
and I will use your skin as a lap blanket.
Do you understand?
We have a deal.
All right, shove off, me hearties.
Arrr!
♪ Good night, my friend ♪
What in God's name is going on here?!
Galavant and King Richard have gone.
We don't know where they are.
Find them or I'll eat your
firstborn for breakfast.
He's behind this. I know it.
Where have you been?
I'm sorry, milady, I must have slept in.
Oh, really?
Well, why don't you help yourself wake up
by going down to the dungeon
and killing everyone who's left?
Okay. It will be my pleasure.
Okay, here's the plan.
One of you is gonna knock
me out and take my keys.
What? You're not going to kill us?
I keep my promises,
and I promised your little lover boy
that I'd take care of you.
So who's first?
Come on.
Next.
Die!
Just take the keys and go.
Not you. You're coming with me.
Why?
I think I'll keep you for insurance.
Just go! I'll be fine.
Just get everyone to safety.
I'll come back for you.
Please do! So scared!
Gareth, did you kill everyone
who needed to be killed?
No, milady.
What kind of kingdom are you running here?
A henchman that doesn't kill,
a queen who does nothing about it.
This place has gone soft...
Turns out he wasn't my type.
You just got a promotion.
Sit.
You're gonna have to either
lose or gain a lot of weight.
We had nowhere else to go.
You really hurt my feelings, Izzy.
I don't think I want to be
your future husband anymore.
I'm sorry.
- But...
- Just kidding!
Come on in!
Let's get to know each
other, my future wife.
So happy you came.
I built a room just for you,
my perfect, pretty princess.
You see, it's not so bad.
It's for you...
To live in forever.
Everyone say bye-bye to Izzy.
Oh, boy.
♪ Our season ends right there ♪
♪ With questions everywhere ♪
♪ Like will the princess
waste her whole life waiting? ♪
♪ Will Gareth and the Queen ♪
♪ Rule the entire scene? ♪
♪ Will all this singing
kill our Nielsen ratings? ♪
♪ Sid, the peasants, the entire crew ♪
♪ Will they be back for season two? ♪
♪ Who knows? ♪
♪ But if there are more shows ♪
♪ Then off our hero goes ♪
♪ And so the legend grows ♪
♪ The legend known as Galavant ♪
What, what?
Eh, it's you.
This will be fun.
Make the best of it, right?
It's like a buddy trip.
What are those... fables? [Muttering]
Buddy... buddy books, buddy fables?
This'll be a good time.
www.tvsubtitles.net
Behold, my fellow travelers.
Today, we cross the winding straits
to the rocky river
to the shores of Valencia.
No, I wouldn't take the rocky river route.
There are rumors of thieves and bandits.
I don't care about bandits.
I'm Galavant, and Galavant will
be deterred by no foe in his...
Who ate all the raisins
out of the trail mix?
I hate cashews, and Brazil nuts are gross.
You know what?
Heroes get the raisins.
And they choose the path.
That's just the way it goes.
Look, can we just hold it
together for a few more days?
We've been doing so well, right?
- Right.
♪ We eat together ♪
♪ We drink together ♪
♪ We work in perfect sync together ♪
♪ We smile ♪
- ♪ Frown ♪
- ♪ Blink ♪
♪ Together completely ♪
♪ We walk together, in time together ♪
- ♪ Can't help ♪
- ♪ Yelp ♪
- ♪ Kelp ♪
♪ But rhyme together ♪
♪ Our voices chime together so neatly ♪
♪ And togetherness is what we do ♪
♪ Together, me and him and you ♪
- ♪ Like rock ♪
- ♪ And scissors ♪
♪ And paper ♪
♪ And stuck together ♪
♪ All day together ♪
♪ We're in each other's way together ♪
♪ Our quirks are on display together ♪
♪ Or nearly ♪
♪ But togetherness
will see us through ♪
♪ Unless I kill the other two ♪
♪ Or we kill her together ♪
♪ But there's some things we don't share ♪
♪ Like the way I've kind of
sort of totally played him ♪
♪ Oh, God, I've betrayed him ♪
♪ And there's some things we don't share ♪
♪ Like I'm kind of sort of
always thinking about her ♪
♪ Or like how you both ignore me
all of the... ♪
♪ Each day together's
a chore together ♪
- ♪ A belching ♪
- ♪ Nagging ♪
- ♪ Bore ♪
♪ Together ♪
♪ then listening to her
snore together ♪
It's like she's a bear.
♪ But together, though,
is what we'll be ♪
♪ For what feels like eternity ♪
- ♪ Together ♪
- ♪ Me ♪
- ♪ And me ♪
♪ As one ♪
♪ As one! ♪
♪ As... ♪
♪ As o-o-o-one! ♪
- That is so typical.
- What's typical?
I thought you said I was gonna
have the big finish this time.
It was supposed to be my turn afterwards.
- It's never your turn.
- Well, no, that's...
Bandits.
- If only someone had warned us.
- Yeah, well, you snore.
Galavant - 01x04
Comedy Gold
sync and correction by solfieri
www.addic7ed.com
I've got something else
you can do with your hands.
I cannot believe My Queen is
cheating on me with that joker.
He's a jester, sir.
I know he's a jester, Gareth.
I was insulting him
by calling him a joker,
like when you call someone a clown.
- But people like clowns.
- Damn it, man! Would you just let me vent?!
I think I know why Madalena
likes him more than me.
He's funny.
How do I compete with that?
Well, funny's easy. I mean, I'm funny.
Really?
- Yeah. Knock, knock.
- Who's there?
He's a  you  thing up
you in the  chair
with the  and knees
is taking it
out that son
Good Lord, Gareth.
Do you kiss my ring with that mouth?
My mum taught me that one.
Oof.
Now, if that fool is tickling
my wife's funny bone,
it leaves me no choice.
I know what I have to do.
Hello, jester.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
I know precisely what you have
been doing with my wife.
Aah!
It's a bendy sword.
Isn't that fantastic?
Oh!
Not even a giggle.
See, this is precisely
why I need your help.
Please teach me to be funny.
I'm begging you.
- Gah!
- Ohh!
- Oh!
- Aah!
Even when you know it
bends, you still think... whoa!
Please tell me you hid the jewel.
Of course I hid the jewel...
In a place where no one will ever find it.
Uh, excuse me. Where are you taking us?
The pirate king will decide your fate.
"I don't care what road we choose.
I'm Galavant.
- I get to eat the raisins."
- "I'm Isabella.
I chew with my mouth open like
a cow working on a fresh cud."
I have a deviated septum. I told you that.
I can't breathe through my nose.
If I chew with my mouth closed,
I'd get no air.
Do you want me to die?
Well...
Wait. What are pirates doing
miles from the ocean?
I'm... so sorry. Am I missing something?
Where's your boat?
I'll be asking the questions around here.
Arr!
Actually, go ahead.
I didn't have a question ready.
Um... don't you need a boat to be pirates?
You're on land.
- Land ho!
- Carl, stop it.
All you need to be a pirate
is a dark heart
and a wicked disregard
for other people's lives.
And swords.
Of course swords.
That goes without saying.
Everyone knows pirates need swords.
- What about a hook hand?
- Parrots? Peg legs.
- Land ho!
- I said stop it!
Maybe it'll be easier to explain
in a pirate shanty.
♪ Ho ♪
♪ We're cruel and vicious pirate men ♪
♪ As hard and tough as brass ♪
♪ By far the fearsomest buccaneers ♪
♪ To ever walk on grass ♪
- ♪ We pillage here ♪
- ♪ And plunder there ♪
♪ We rage from dusk till dawn ♪
♪ we hoist the anchor
and swab the deck ♪
♪ Then gather for drinks on the lawn ♪
♪ We're the lords of the sea ♪
♪ Except we aren't at sea ♪
♪ Just not of the actual sea ♪
Arr...
♪ Now, how we ended up here,
'tis a dire and dreadful tale ♪
♪ The kind to leave the meanest
rogue a-puking o'er the rail ♪
♪ So fateful, so accursed ♪
♪ Such a stroke of evil luck ♪
♪ our ship washed up
on that thar hill ♪
♪ And hey, I guess it stuck ♪
♪ so now we hold the river
here by brutal, violent force ♪
♪ We've also taken up gardening ♪
- ♪ Sustainably ♪
- ♪ Of course ♪
♪ we make you pay to cross this way ♪
♪ And squeeze you till it hurts ♪
♪ And on the side, we sell a line ♪
♪ Of homemade organic desserts ♪
♪ We're the lords of the sea ♪
♪ Though, technically, next to the sea ♪
♪ Or sort of "of the se-e-a"! ♪
So, now we live here,
and we rob any passersby.
- Which brings us back to you.
- Please, sir.
We're merely poor travelers
with nothing worth taking.
Hey, captain. Look what I found.
Oh, for the love of g... in your purse?
That's where you thought
no one would look for it?
I put it with my girls' supplies.
Guys never look there.
They must have sisters.
Poor travelers, huh?
Well, what do we have here?
It's a jewel.
I know it's a jewe... you know what?
You're having a time-out. Go to your tent.
Don't you give me that look.
Right. Comedy lessons. Let's begin.
I'm sorry. What is that noise?
It's my bells, sire. I'm terrified.
Don't be.
I already told you
I've decided not to kill you.
I mean, not that I don't want to.
In fact, it would be mondo satisfying
to cut your face off
and sew it back on inside out.
Nah, I'll stick with my first plan.
Teach me to be funny so I can woo my wife.
Whatever you say, My King.
♪ Comedy is easy
once you know the basics ♪
♪ Starting with the concept of surprise ♪
Right.
♪ Take what folks
think, give it a wink ♪
♪ You try it on now for size ♪
- Me?
- Yeah.
He was surprised.
Uh...
- ♪ Comedy gold ♪
- Really?
♪ I'm telling you, it's comedy gold ♪
Yes.
♪ You're killing it ♪
♪ If that doesn't slay 'em ♪
♪ I'll murder you cold ♪
♪ Swear to God, it's comedy gold ♪
Well, our work here is done,
so I'll just be going.
Oh, we're just getting started.
- Ah, right.
- Lesson two!
♪ Lesson number two is also fundamental ♪
♪ Something that we call
"the rule of three" ♪
♪ Set up the joke, give it a stroke ♪
♪ Third time, bam ♪
Yes! Now me!
Three serfs walk into a bar.
The first serf orders a hot grog.
The second serf orders a hot grog.
And the third serf orders a hot grog.
But he has no money and neither do
the other two because they're serfs.
Huh?
♪ Comedy gold ♪
- Yes! Nailed it!
- ♪ I promise you, it's comedy gold ♪
♪ Hilarious ♪
- ♪ The crowd will be rolling ♪
- ♪ Or heads will be rolled ♪
♪ Oh, not with all this comedy gold ♪
More, more!
♪ Props can be a riot,
ethnic humor, can't deny it ♪
♪ Or a pratfall,
if it's properly applied ♪
♪ Depending on the viewer,
take it black or work it bluer ♪
♪ Or try an observational aside ♪
Have you ever noticed how lepers
have pieces falling off of them?
I mean, what's that all about?
♪ Gonna be killer ♪
♪ Gonna be ace ♪
♪ Folks dying of laughter
all over the place ♪
♪ And if I get desperate ♪
♪ A pie in the face? ♪
I dare you.
♪ Telling you, it's comedy gold ♪
Oh! You are a wonderful teacher.
Perhaps now I shall finally be able to
satisfy my wife the same way you have.
My God, we've got a strange relationship.
♪ Telling you, it's comedy gold ♪
Pirates, that's pomade.
It's for relaxing my curls, not eating.
Right, men.
Let's stow this booty in the chest.
Carl, give me the key.
Oh, come on, guys. Not again.
These idiots really stink
at being pirates.
No kidding.
Unbelievable.
It's kind of nice being
on the same page, isn't it?
It is nice to have a break
from the relentless stream
of criticism, yeah.
Maybe if you did things right,
I wouldn't have to say it.
- Mouth breather.
- Egomaniac.
And it's over.
You. Walk with me.
Oh, right. Of course.
Lads, could you give me a hand?
Arr.
You know, we met before, at Lilith Faire,
the island of Lesbos.
I looked a little different...
Fewer wrinkles.
More like...
Yes, of course.
Well, you're Peter Pillager,
the pirate king.
Well, your men used to be
the scourge of the seas.
What happened there?
Oh.
You know how it is when you
spend too much time with people.
Little things start to get to you...
- Oh...
- And before you know it,
it's all about who's taken whose booty.
"It's my booty." "No, it's my booty."
booty, booty, booty.
- You stopped working together.
- Big-time.
We can't even agree on how to
get our ship off that damn hill.
The truth is...
I could do with a man like you.
So I have a proposition.
Either, "A," I kill all of you
and keep that jewel
and the girls' supplies.
- Why do you want the girls' supplies?
- Or "B," you join me and I let your squire
and that annoying little
mouth breather go.
Well, in all fairness to her,
only 'cause she's not here
to defend herself,
the mouth breathing
is a medical condition,
- so she can't really help it.
- Seems like a pretty simple fix to me.
Put food in mouth, close mouth, chew.
What kind of moron can't do that?
Again, not to get into semantics here,
but if she closes her mouth
while she eats,
she's literally not breathing
out of anywhere.
You get used to it.
Honestly, lately, I can't fall asleep
until she starts snoring.
Dude, you're making me uncomfortable.
Who are you choosing,
me or the mouth breather?
Call her a "mouth breather" one more time.
Mouth breather.
How did you do that?
I keep trying to tell everyone...
Oh.
I'm not just the guy
that eats the raisins.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Chef coming through. Thank you.
This way, my lady.
Here's your table, My Queen.
What fresh idiocy does king
Richard have in store for me now?
Um, I'm...
That was rhetorical. Shoo.
Chef out.
Welcome to the show!
I introduce to you, without further ado,
the king of comedy!
Hello! Thank you very, very, very much.
Now, I understand you've all come here
under threat of death,
and I appreciate it.
In fact... I ordered it.
Everybody laugh!
What on God's flat earth is going on?
Well, they say the way to a woman's heart
- is through her funny bone, so...
- Oh, God. Let's not do this.
Why did the king go to the dentist?
To get his teeth crowned.
Uh, you've heard that one.
Mm! "You might be a peasant" jokes.
If you have more children than teeth,
you might be a peasant.
Is this thing on?
Ugh. He's dying out there.
Give him the pie.
Now?!
That's the big finale.
Damn it, man, look at the poor bastard.
Give him the pie.
If your toilet is a tree,
then you might be...
She laughed! It worked! She laughed!
Quick, give me more pies so I can
keep hitting Gareth in the face.
Or someone else. I-I can pie someone else.
You're a fool.
When my men see me captive,
they will swarm on you like hornets.
No. Bees.
No, hornets was better.
Well, you can let them try,
but I'll be damned if I'm letting my team
end up like yours.
So I'm gonna rescue them,
rouse us to work together,
defeat your... hold on.
Oh, for the love of Mike, what happened?
Sid was right.
It was time to stop bickering
and work together.
So we did, and we overthrew the camp.
You missed an amazing battle,
better than anything at castle black.
Well, FYI, I was also gonna come back,
and I was gonna suggest that
we start working together, too,
- wasn't I? Tell them.
- Oh, please, stop.
This whole time, I've been
saying that I was gonna...
- This is all a little humiliating.
- You know what? Doesn't matter.
I know we've been
driving each other crazy,
but I think we've got something
really good going on here.
I mean, look at us...
We're gorgeous, very diverse.
I think if we pull it together, we could
do something great, legendary even.
What do you say?
We are diverse.
Super diverse.
I remember when we had something special.
Arr.
I miss us.
Now, look, either we can take
your pirate supplies...
The swords, the hooks...
- Parrots.
- Booty.
- Peg legs.
- Girls' supplies.
Yes, yes, all of it,
or we can work together
to get your ship off that hill
and you can take us to Valencia.
What do you say?
Did I just cut your hand?
Yes. Very badly.
Sorry.
Where are you going?
It's time for 4:00 fool-around.
Is it?
M-my sundial must be slow
because of the... c-clouds.
If you're worried I'm upset
about you helping my husband
with that ridiculous show, then don't be.
Who cares? He's an idiot.
Yes, well, that's the thing.
I don't think I can do this anymore.
I guess I just feel a little... guilty.
Well, that's very noble of you
to care about someone's feelings.
Guards!
If you're developing a conscience,
then you're no good to me.
Take him to the dungeon,
the really scary one.
With the mice.
Wait, no! Please!
At least let me change my clothes!
These are gang colors!
Oh, hello.
I was just coming to see Steve.
Who's Steve?
Steve McKinzie. The jester.
You don't know his name?
Well, no matter.
Say, what do you call
a tiny mosquito in a tin suit?
- Oh, God.
- Nope.
A gnat in shining armor.
- I've got so many of these.
- Please stop talking.
No, I love talking with you.
Right, you maggots!
Let's get this boat off the hill.
What?
It's just nice to hear you
call us "maggots" again.
You've always been maggots in here.
Arr!
Prepare the lines!
♪ we heave together, we ho together ♪
♪ All working toe to toe together ♪
♪ Ahoy, look out below together! ♪
Run away! Run away!
♪ Now off together,
we'll cruise together ♪
♪ With pirate stuff we'll use together ♪
♪ Guys, we should get tattoos together ♪
Arr!
♪ And, together, look what we can do ♪
♪ Together we're one scurvy crew ♪
- ♪ Together, we're not bad ♪
- ♪ It's true ♪
My God, just get a room, you two.
♪ Togetherness will see us
through to the end ♪
Land ho!
"Land ho," indeed, Carl.
Gal...
Can I call you "Gal"?
Uh, well, I don't love it.
I have to talk to you.
I feel a little guilty about something.
Actually, so do I.
I stashed a bag of trail mix
before we left.
Raisins intact.
Really?
Knock yourself out.
And feel free to eat with your mouth open.
It's not as gross as I make it out to be.
I mean, it's gross,
but it's not gross-gross.
Listen, Galavant,
I think the reason
I've been so difficult recently
is that I was villainizing you
so I felt better about myself.
I'm probably signing my parents' death
warrant by telling you this, but...
I lied.
I'm leading you into a trap.
Galavant?
We're almost there.
Did you hear anything I just said?
Sorry.
I don't always listen when you talk.
I will get better at that.
What were you saying,
something about
your parents or something?
I'm looking forward to seeing them.
Right. Yeah, parents are the best.
Godspeed, pirates!
To Valencia!
Arr!
I'm coming, my love.
sync and correction by solfieri
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net
Galavant - 01x01 - Pilot
♪ Way back in days of old ♪
♪ There was a legend told ♪
♪ About a hero known as Galavant ♪
♪ Square jaw and perfect hair ♪
♪ Cojones out to there ♪
♪ There was no hero quite like Galavant ♪
♪ Tough, plus every other manly value ♪
♪ Mess with him, he'll disembowel you ♪
♪ Yay, he ruled in every way ♪
♪ A fairy-tale cliché ♪
♪ And people called him Galavant ♪
There he is!
♪ The man we're speaking
of, he had a lady love ♪
♪ And Madalena, she was one fair maiden ♪
♪ Long legs and perfect skin ♪
♪ A body built for sin ♪
♪ With cleavage you could
hold a whole parade in ♪
♪ Ah, true love was never this ecstatic ♪
♪ Nor as wildly acrobatic ♪
♪ Yes, he loved her to excess ♪
♪ Thrice daily, more or less ♪
♪ And she'd be screaming ♪
♪ Galavant! ♪
- * One tiny problem *
- Look.
♪ Soon would arise ♪
♪ Richard, a nearby king
of wealth and stature ♪
♪ He watched Madalena, lust in his eyes ♪
♪ And he asked her for her hand ♪
♪ Well, more like a demand ♪
♪Well, more like had
his henchmen snatch her ♪
No! Galavant, help!
♪ Which brings us to today ♪
♪ The royal wedding day ♪
♪ No one can stop it now but Galavant ♪
♪ Poor Madalena waits
behind King Richard's gates ♪
♪ For the arrival of her Galavant ♪
♪ Now, at last begins our true adventure ♪
♪ Epic, wild, a real butt-clencher! ♪
♪ So, huzzah and tally ho! ♪
♪ Sit back and here we go ♪
♪ Attend the tale of ♪
♪ Galava-a-a-a-nt! ♪
Is everything all right... My Princess?
Yes, My King.
I should think so.
In a few moments, we shall marry,
and you will instantly become the richest,
most powerful woman in the land.
Yes, My King. Very exciting.
And then... tonight...
You will join me in my bed.
Yes, My King.
We're going to do it!
Yes.
We're not going to just
sit in bed and open gifts
and talk about how much
fun the wedding was, okay?
We're... doing... it.
Yep.
My lady.
I mean, of course, we're
going to open some presents,
- but then we're going to do it.
- Got it.
Ohh!
Ugh!
Ohh! Aah!
Aah!
♪ By all the stars above,
I'll save my one true love ♪
Hey, look! Oh, wow! It's him!
♪ it's Gala... ♪
♪ I shall not be denied
until she's by my side ♪
I suggest you fall.
Thanks!
And so, on this glorious day,
we celebrate the union
of our greatest king!
So sorry to interrupt.
My lady.
All right, all right. Hold on.
Now, Gareth and I could surely
fight all night to an even draw,
if that's what you want.
Hell, you can even send
all your men to help him,
if you so desire.
But I'll fend them all off.
'Cause here's the thing.
I love her, Richard.
She's the first thing I
think of in the morning
and the last thing I think of in the eve.
And you can offer her great fame,
and you can offer her great fortune,
but...
Only I can offer her
great love.
And that is what she chooses.
Actually...
Hmm?
I don't know. I've been thinking a lot
about it ever since he kidnapped me, and...
I'm gonna go with the fame and fortune.
- Yes!
- Seems like an easier life, you know?
Oh, I'm really sorry, Gal.
I hope we can be friends.
Mm.
- Hold that thought, darling.
- Mm.
Good night, sweet prince.
Oh.
Damn it, Gareth.
Would you just do that for me, please?
Night-night.
Good morning... sir.
I see we're getting an
early start this morning.
Oh, what do you want, Sid?
Sir... when you hired me to be your squire,
it was the most exciting
thing to ever happen to me.
Best squireship in the land.
My parents completely plotzed.
But ever since Madalena...
- Don't say her name.
- Right.
There's someone here to see you.
She brings with her an opportunity.
I would beg you to meet with her.
- Sid, I'm not seeing anyone.
- And here she is... may I present
the Princess Isabella
Maria Lucia "Elisabeeta"...
- "Betta."
- ... Betta of Valencia.
Well, that's a mouthful.
Uh-huh.
Sir Galavant,
I have traveled long and
far to seek your favor.
Four months ago, my peaceful
kingdom of Valencia...
I'm sorry. What is that smell?
That would be me.
Four months ago,
my peaceful kingdom of Valencia
fell under attack from a rival land.
My people were taken captive.
My entire family either
killed or imprisoned.
Oh, that's terrible. That's just terrible.
Still, you've got a nice way about you.
I'm sure you'll land on your feet.
Nice meeting you. Door's on the wall.
Before being captured, my
father hid me in the cellar
and handed me the
priceless Jewel of Valencia.
I hid in that cellar for months
as my family was slaughtered above me.
I now offer you this priceless jewel,
all that my country has left to offer.
I throw myself at your mercy, Sir Galavant!
Please...
Save my people.
Sorry. I got distracted.
What did you say after I said, "nice
meeting you. Door's on the wall"?
You're no hero. Who are you?
Oh, I'm nobody, princess.
♪ Where is the gallant knight ♪
♪ Who stood for truth and right? ♪
♪ The Valiant dragon-slayer Galavant? ♪
♪ Where is his steely gaze? ♪
♪ The abs the poets praise? ♪
♪ Whatever happened to that Galavant? ♪
♪ The man you're searching for ♪
♪ Lost all he loved, and more ♪
♪ His hope, his pride,
all sense of Galavant ♪
♪ Add to that losing streak,
a couple kegs a week ♪
- * Plus 20 pounds, ta-da! *
- No!
- Yep.
- But you're...
♪ Still, you have to! ♪
- No, I don't.
- But...
- See ya!
- Wait!
♪ How will I... ♪
♪ No idea ♪
- Please!
- No.
- * I'm begging on my knees *
- Bye-bye!
- * I'll pay whatever fee *
- You're still here?
♪ We're lost without you, Gala... ♪
That man is an animal!
W... wait, wait, wait, wait!
Princess Isabella Maria
Lucia "Elisabeet... " Bet...
Princess?
Banana.
Banana who?
Orange.
Orange who?
"Orange" you glad I
didn't say "banana" again?
Whoa!
Another wonderful routine, Jester.
I'm not seeing it, baby.
Perhaps his humor flies
over your head, then.
Honestly, Gareth, I don't
know what she sees in him.
No idea, My King.
Well, I will go and compliment the Jester.
And while I do, husband,
perhaps you can make some progress
convincing the king and queen of Valencia
- to tell you where their jewel is hidden.
- I've tried everything.
Mm-hmm.
Galavant would not stand for this.
- What did you just say?
- I said,
"Galavant would not have stood for this"!
See, that's what I thought you said.
I just wanted clarification. Thank you.
Find me the jewel, would you, dear?
Of course, darling.
Jester, um...
Join me in my chamber, would you?
I'd love to learn a little more
about how you, uh... craft a joke.
Ooh!
She really gets a kick
out of that damn Jester.
I don't know. Maybe it
is all going over my head.
Oh, it's definitely
going over your head, sir.
A midday snack, My King?
Come up here.
What happened to the other chef?
Looked just like you,
but... older, more wrinkly.
My father?
Right. What happened to him?
- You had him killed, sir.
- Hmm?
Your mutton was too rare.
Well, that doesn't sound like me.
You killed his father before him.
Your family has killed
the last four generations
of chefs in my family.
It's not a great job, My King.
I'm such a bully.
I'm under a terrible amount of
pressure. You have to understand that.
Oh, it's fine, My King.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, Gareth, I try so hard to please her.
I invade a kingdom for a jewel,
I respect her vow of chastity,
and yet every day I have to hear it
over and over again.
♪ Galavant ♪
♪ Blah, blah, blah, blah, Galavant ♪
♪ I want her, need her,
crave her, yes, it's true ♪
♪ But she is not the only
thing I desperately want to do ♪
♪ I want to shoot him with a crossbow ♪
♪ I want to stab him in the eye ♪
♪ I want to liberate
his head from his neck ♪
♪ And then punt the bloody wreck sky high ♪
Oh!
♪ I want to hurl him out a window ♪
♪ And shove explosives
where the sun don't shine ♪
♪ Want to skewer him with swords ♪
♪ Then slowly twist them ♪
♪ All around his reproductive system ♪
♪ Won't that be divine? ♪
♪ Then she'll be mine ♪
Everybody sing!
♪ Ahh ♪
♪ And then you'll do it every evening ♪
♪ Sweet God, at last! ♪
♪ In every room on every floor ♪
♪ Till I can't do it anymore ♪
♪ And with no Galavant
distracting your bride ♪
♪ We could start a genocidal war ♪
- * Yay, we're gonna go to... *
- Wait, what?!
♪ I'll get back to all my hobbies ♪
♪ Like raising taxes
and tormenting the poor ♪
♪ Crush those poor! ♪
♪ No more "Galavant is
just complete perfection! ♪
♪ "Gal would never lose his... ♪
♪ ... temper" ♪
♪ Won't that be divine? ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
♪ And she'll be mine ♪
♪ Ia la la la ♪
♪ Just mine, all mine ♪
♪ Mine, all mine, all mine! ♪
Well, that was ripping!
This is all very exciting, My King,
but Galavant still lives.
And he is still the greatest
warrior in five kingdoms.
Fine. If I can't win her love, I'll buy it.
Bring me the king and queen of Valencia.
I'll find her that stupid jewel.
"'Orange' you glad I
didn't say 'banana' again?"
Not funny at all, sir.
Tommy.
Tommy. Tommy!
There appears to be a rather
large hole in my bucket,
and I would very much like you to fix it.
Sorry, Gal. I'm gonna have to cut you off.
Tommy, come on. It's me.
It's Gal.
Hey, Gal. Come on. You're
embarrassing yourself.
I'm embarrassing yourself.
Can I buy you a drink?
No!
Good. You can buy me one.
Now, where were we?
Two months ago, you were
imprisoned in a cellar.
Then what happened?
Ah, here we are.
Regular spots, please. Thank you very much.
I believe you know where to stand.
Now, let me ask you one question.
I've tried to be kind to you.
Have I not?
You pillaged our peaceful
kingdom, killed half our army.
But I haven't killed you.
I mean, think about it.
I've killed a massive
amount of people this week,
but I haven't killed... kil...
Gareth, I have a horribly scratchy throat.
A bit of tea, please.
Tea for the king!
I'm not really a yeller.
I've been fighting a
bug since the invasion.
I swear, it's the plague.
It's not the plague.
- Feel it, though... does that feel lumpy?
- No.
- You didn't even feel it.
- We beg you to show mercy to our people,
- good King Richard.
- We've done this.
Look, here's the thing.
My wife really wants that jewel of yours.
Now, I know, at times, she
can come off as a bit, um...
What's the word?
- Evil.
- Cruel.
No, that's not it. It's more...
- Sadistic.
- Vicious.
You know, I think you really
just have to get to know her.
She can be a
- Would you stop it, Gareth?!
- All right.
How's about this?
You tell me where the jewelry is,
we'll pack up shop.
We'll stop the pillaging and the killing,
yada, yada, and everyone's happy.
The Jewel of Valencia is priceless.
I know. I know.
It is a symbol of Valencia.
It has belonged not to us,
but to our people for thousands of years.
Totally understand. Totally empathize.
- Can I have it?
- Never!
This is so not how I wanted to do this!
It is about to get very messy in here.
Ooh, my tea! Thank you very much.
Mm.
Is there lemon in there?
Yes... My King?
Some unsqueezed lemons.
Well, it's delightful. Just delightful.
Kill the king, make her watch.
No!
Mmm.
Sid, fetch me a drink.
When he tells me to fetch,
those are my favorite moments.
Thanks again for the drink.
Drinks.
Right. Thanks again.
My father used to tell stories of you,
- of your skill in battle...
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Your heroism, of your goodness.
What happened to you?
I mean... eh.
Oh, come on. I've come a long way.
Surely I deserve some kind of backstory.
All right.
My parents were people of
massive, massive appetites.
They loved everything... they
loved food. They loved drink.
But most of all, they loved each other.
Ironically, they also hated each other.
And they fought violently every day.
Didn't have time for much else, in fact.
So... at the age of 8, I swore off love.
Devoted myself to doing
something better with my life
than wasting it on love.
So I read, I trained, I learned languages.
All the time other young men
chasing spent chasing girls,
I spent that time bettering myself.
But I come from a long family of lovers.
You can't fight genetics.
So when it inevitably happened...
- When I fell...
- You fell hard.
I fell hard.
And her?
She fell softer...
As it turns out.
Look, I'd love to help. Really, I would.
But I'm...
I'm sort of out of the whole
"damsel in distress" business
at the moment, so...
I listened from below as he
ordered my parents to their death.
And after coming all this way,
your advice is for me
to just turn a blind eye
and watch king Richard destroy my kingdom
and everyone I've ever loved?
What?
Did you just say...
"King Richard"?
Oh, come here!
- Isabella.
- Father!
Ah!
Maybe this is what we're looking for.
Ooh, sweet!
Any luck on the Jewel, Richard?
Well, actually, my dear...
I know. I know. You're working on it.
Well, why don't you stop working on it,
start acting like Galavant,
and do something already?
Will do, My Queen.
I swear, if I have to hear the
name Galavant one more time.
If only there was some way that I could...
Ah.
She's a pretty young
thing, isn't she, Gareth?
- A bit plump for my liking.
- Plump?
The girl is 100 pounds soaking wet.
I know, but I like skinny.
Like, really unhealthy skinny.
You love your parents, don't you, my dear?
Leave my parents be.
Leave them be, or so help
me, I will kill you myself.
And spunky.
Ha! More like "chunky"!
Just stop it, Gareth!
I am trying to do something here!
Fine. If we can't beat
Galavant on his turf,
we'll bring him to our own.
If you want your parents to live,
you will travel to find Galavant.
You tell him that I, king
Richard, have invaded your kingdom.
Offer to pay him with the jewel.
When that doesn't work, I
want you to tell him this...
I feel like you should
be writing this down.
- I will remember it.
- It's a bit long.
I'd really just be more
comfortable if you wrote it down.
- I will remember it.
- Like a steel trap.
- Always had a wonderful memory, this one.
- Fine.
You tell him that king Richard is a...
Is a cruel and vicious man.
Four months I hid in that cellar.
He and his queen slept right above me.
And you tell him that every night,
you would listen while he
screamed at his queen...
Screamed at his queen, and
each night I would be left
with only the sobs of that poor woman.
Every night, she would cry
out, "I made the wrong choice.
I'm so sorry, Gals. I'm so sorry."
She must have left some maidens back home.
Never knew what she meant.
"I'm so sorry, Gals."
I love you, Gal.
"I'm so sorry, Gal."
She was saying, "I'm so sorry, Gal."
We leave tomorrow at sunrise.
Pack lightly. There's a long journey ahead.
♪ And so begins our plot ♪
♪ Of which there's quite a lot ♪
♪ With Isabella stringing Galavant ♪
♪ And with the evil king
prepared to do his thing ♪
♪ And with the queen still
pretty sure he can't ♪
♪ And, with Gal about
to start his journey ♪
♪ One both twisty and immensely turny ♪
♪ Oh, it's lots of plot, we know! ♪
♪ But anyway, hi ho! ♪
♪ We're off and here we go! ♪
♪ Come back for our next show ♪
♪ To see what's next for Galava-a-a-a-nt! ♪
Oh, for God's sake, Jester!
Stop with the singing and get
back to what you're good at.
- Knock, knock.
- Not that.
- Whoo-hoo-hoo!
- Oh, Jester!
sync and correction by solfieri
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net