Wait.
Grunkle Stan!
Kids! I can't believe it!
I thought I lost you two.
- Ahh!
- Mr. Pines, it's really you!
I've been hugging strangers
to practice for this moment.
We missed you, you old codger.
I've missed you knuckleheads too.
It's good to have you back.
So... what's everyone doing here?
Yeah, there's, like,
monsters and gnomes.
And is Pacifica wearing a potato sack?
Hey! Even in a sack
I still look better than you.
It's... It's a long story.
Hey, is anyone gonna feed me?
Larry King's disembodied
wax head wants num-nums.
We're trying to ration
our food, remember?
- Mmm... mmm...
- Uhh, it's happening again!
Hey, everyone!
Eye bat!
Evasive maneuvers!
- Shh! Keep it down!
- Get the lights!
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~
2x20 - Weirdmageddon, Part III
Welcome to what's left
of normal around here...
home base.
Ow!
We have...
# Several injuries #
- Ooh! - Ow!
- My liver, girl!
Rumble McSkirmish?
Do not be afraid.
Weirdmaggedon has taught me
there are some battles I cannot win.
I am now Humble McSkirmish.
Grunkle Stan, how'd this all happen?
So I was hammering signs out back
when the sky started
vomiting nightmares.
I listen to a lot of AM radio,
so I knew what this meant...
the end of the world.
What I didn't expect
was what happened next.
Turns out whatever you and my brother
did to the Shack with
your unicorn voodoo
made the crazy place
invincible to weirdness.
Of course... the unicorn spell!
That's why this is the only
place Bill's magic can't touch.
That's when Possum
Breath over here shows up
leading a bunch of injured
stragglers through the forest.
They needed a place to stay,
and since the Mayor got captured,
I elected myself de facto chief.
The plan's to stay in here and
eat brown meat until we run out.
- Then I vote we eat the gnomes.
- Hey, I'm short, not deaf!
Shh! Shh!
Stress will make you chewy.
Grunkle Stan, we can't all
just hide inside the Shack.
There's a town in need of saving!
Me and Ford tried to do it,
but he got captured by Bill.
Serves that jerk right!
My brother's had some stupid plans,
but going up against an all-powerful
space demon was his worst one yet.
Trust me, we have everything
we need right here.
It's not the Ritz, but at least the
monsters inside know how to massage.
- You know Shiatsu?
- Yes, I've taken some classes.
So, you're really just
gonna let Bill win?
Look, kiddo.
We got a good deal here.
Besides, I'm sure wherever
the rest of the townsfolk are,
they're fine.
This is Shandra Jimenez
reporting live from the
inside of Bill's castle.
Here for the first time are images of
what's happened to
the captured townsfolk.
Viewers are advised to look away
if they don't want to see their friends
turned into a twisted
throne of human agony.
- Mom and Dad?
- My family!
Deputy Durland!
Is there no one who will
save the people of this town?
I'm Shandra Jimenez,
and I'm being turned into
stone by a flying eyeball.
Oh, no. My parents are bad,
but even they don't
deserve to be turned to stone.
Curse you, Bill! Why must
you take everything we love?!
Guys, don't you see?
Our friends need us,
but we only save them if we fight back!
Mabel is right.
Bill wants us to run and hide.
He wants us to think he's invincible.
But Ford told me before he was captured
that he knows Bill's secret weakness.
- Weakness?
- Now, if we band together,
if we combine all of
our strength, our smarts,
- our... whatever Toby has...
- Aureus rashes!
...then we just might
be able to rescue Ford,
learn Bill's weakness,
and save Gravity Falls!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Have you all forgotten
who's in charge here?
Besides, we're only safe inside!
It's not like we can take
the Mystery Shack to Bill.
Wha... Whoa!
Holy hootenanny!
Flapjack and fiddlebanjos!
Sorry. Sorry.
Got a little excited.
What I meant to say is,
I think I figured out a way
to fight Bill and rescue Ford.
But we're all gonna
have to work together!
Now...
if you just...
Don't worry, Ford.
We're coming for you!
Let me go!
You insane three-sided...
Wha... What is this place?
♪ We'll meet again ♪
♪ Don't know where, don't know when ♪
♪ Oh, I know we'll meet
again some sunny day ♪
Wh... Where am I?
You're in the penthouse suite, kid!
The tip of the pyramid! Have a drink.
Make yourself comfortable.
You know that couch is
made from living human skin?
Quit the games, Cipher!
If I'm still alive, you
must want something from me.
Ah, sharp as ever, Fordsy.
As you may have noticed...
I've recently had a
multi-dimensional makeover!
I control space and matter,
and now that that dumb
baby's out of the way,
time itself!
- But I wasn't always this way.
- Oof!
You think those chains are tight?
Imagine living in the
second dimension...
flat minds in a flat
world with flat dreams.
I liberated my dimension, Stanford,
and I'm here to liberate yours.
There's just one hitch.
As it turns out,
my weirdness can't escape the
magical confines of this town!
There's something keeping me in.
Incredible! Gravity Falls' Natural Law
of Weirdness Magnetism.
I studied this years ago!
- And did you find a way to undo it?
- Of course!
There's a simple equation that
could collapse the barrier.
But I'd never tell you!
Listen, Ford, if you just
tell me that equation,
finally your dimension will be free!
Anything will be possible!
I'll remake a fun world...
a better world!
A party that never ends
with a host that never dies!
No more restrictions!
No more laws!
You'd be one of us.
All-powerful!
Greater than anything you've imagined!
And all I need is your help.
You're insane if you
think I'll help you.
Ha ha ha!
I'm insane either way, brainiac!
But have it your way.
I'll just fish around
and get that equation
directly out of your mind!
Not so fast!
You know the rules, Bill.
You may be able to haunt
my dreams, but you can't
enter my mind unless I shake
your hand and let you in.
You're making this so
much harder than it needs to be.
Everyone has a weakness, tough guy!
I'll make you talk!
It's only a matter of time.
All right. I've made some thingamadiculous
robomajigs in my day,
but this is the first one
that won't be used for evil!
Whoa! These blueprints
are incredible, McGucket.
This is your most
amazing invention yet.
Question: Does it have any gun-swords?
I watch a lot of anime and, uh,
trust me, you're gonna
want some gun-swords.
What's an "anime"?
- We have much to discuss.
- Discuss, nothing!
These scribbles are a bunch
of cockamamie balderdash!
Excuse my French.
_
And where would you even find a bunch
of idiots crazy enough to build it?
Grunkle Stan, you're
lookin' at those idiots.
Idiots!
_
Whoa... What...
What are you...
Hey... Hey, now.
Hey! Don't touch that.
Hey...
Uhh! Uhh!
_
Thanks for these
apocalypse sweaters, Mabel.
The end of the world has
never been so comfortable.
Mm-hmm!
Uhh! Fine, I'll wear it.
But I'm not gonna like it.
Admit it. This is the best
day of the end of the world.
I think we actually have
a chance to beat Bill
- and win back our future.
- Yeah. Getting to actually live to see our
13th birthday party is the only
birthday present I want right now.
Hey, if we're lucky enough
to get there, I guarantee
this whole town is gonna
throw you the best birthday
- party you've ever seen.
- Thanks, Soos.
Hey, has anyone seen Grunkle Stan?
This whole plan is bonkers.
But of course, no one asked
the Chief what he thinks.
- After all I've done for everyone!
- Schmebulock.
Yeah, exactly... it's a
total load of schmebulock.
Is something wrong, Grunkle Stan?
You're acting grunklier than usual.
It's this darn plan to save my brother.
If you didn't notice, I already
saved him once from that portal,
and he never thanked me!
He causes the end of the world,
and somehow it's still always
"Stan's the screw-up, Ford's the hero."
Well, maybe people think he's a hero
because he didn't want to
hide in the Mystery Shack!
Well, maybe if he hid in the Mystery
Shack he wouldn't have been captured!
Guys! Guys! Trust me,
tomorrow's gonna be great!
- I believe in us.
- Help! Leader Mabel!
I keep accidentally
flexing through my sweater!
It happened again!
Those weird cow-monsters
are delightful! Coming!
All right, fellas!
Let's hope this turns out
better than my other inventions!
Everybody ready?
Dipper, now!
Huh?! Whoa!
Forgive me, boy. Your
hyper-flammable merchandise
is the only thing keeping me goin'.
What in blazes?!
No! No! Nooo!
Ready to talk now?
I won't.
I won't let you into my mind!
What do you think, pals?
Another 500 volts?
Hey, do you hear that?
What?!
I just fixed that door!
It's the Shacktron, dude!
They made the house into a robot.
Fascinating!
So the mortals are trying
to fight back, huh? Adorable!
Henchmaniacs, you know
what to do! Take them out!
This was a bad idea.
Uh, hey, dudes. Is this thing on?
Tes...
Heh. Uh, I just wanted you monster dudes
to hand over Ford, or we'll
have to, like, fight and junk?
Hey, you're a little cutie.
I have butchered millions
on countless moons!
Whoa. I liked you
better before you talked.
Real... real bring-down, this guy.
Attack!
All right, dudes!
Everyone! Like we planned!
Three, two, one. Go!
Ha ha ha! Good pig.
Get 'em, Gobblewonker!
Hyah! Hyah!
Oh, no, you don't!
Everyone! Incoming!
Does this thing have an escape hatch?
Everybody! Maximum power!
And... now!
Guys, seriously?
You had, like, one job to do here.
Bravo, Dipper and Mabel!
Well, would ya look at that?
Those kids really care about you.
And you care about them.
Don't you?
What are you... Oh. Oh, no.
Perhaps torturing
those kids will make you talk!
No. No! Not the kids! You ca...
Lets get this over with.
What the... No!
No! No! No! No!
Attack!
My eye!
Do you have any idea
how long it takes to regenerate that?
We've got him distracted!
Now's our chance!
Rescue team, move out!
OK, everyone!
We get in, rescue Ford,
get out, save the world.
Piece of cake.
Just so we're clear,
if I die, I'm suing all of you.
Hey, on second thought,
maybe we could come up with a plan
that doesn't involve us
plummeting to our certain death.
- Now!
- Ahh!
- Oh, man, oh, man...
- Whoo-hoo!
Oh, man.
It looks even worse up close.
I found Great-uncle Ford!
He's golden!
But not in the good way!
Great. Grab him
and let's get out of here.
- But how are we going to unfreeze them?
- I know!
Gideon! What happened to you?
Bill captured me.
He's been forcing me
to do cute dances in this
cage for all eternity.
I'm so tired of being cute!
How do we undo this?
Mayor Tyler.
He's the load-bearing human.
Pull him out, and the
whole thing goes down.
Ah. My mouth tastes like nightmares!
I think I'm dark and
tortured for reals now.
This experience will
forever scar Tad Strange.
No more sailor suits!
- Wendy!
- Guys!
- Mom! Dad!
- Durland!
My Blubs!
Don't you ever scare
me like that again!
Kids! Ah, you did it!
I knew I could count on you two.
Fiddldeford! I... I haven't
seen you since we parted ways.
You must hate me.
I've tried forgettin'.
Maybe I should try forgiving.
- Come here, old friend.
- Hey, good to see you too, bro.
Now let's get out of here, huh?
Listen, Uncle Ford, we
don't have a lot of time.
Remember how you told me
right before you were frozen
that you knew Bill's weakness?
- Yeah, a secret way to defeat him?
- I... I do!
Now, does anyone have a pen?
Pencil? Anything?
Ah.
Perfect!
Uh, we've got Bill outside,
but I don't know how long
we can keep him occupied.
Yes, yes. Good, good.
Drawing a circle on the floor.
Well, he's lost his mind.
My mind is fine. And there is
a way to beat him... with this!
The world's most confusing
game of hopscotch?
No, a prophecy.
Although it would be
a pretty fun game of hopscotch.
Many years ago,
I found ten symbols in a cave.
Some I recognized then.
Some I only recognize now.
The native people of Gravity Falls
prophesized that these symbols
could create a force strong
enough to vanquish Bill.
With Bill defeated,
his weirdness would be
reversed and the town could be saved.
This whole time I thought
it was just superstition.
But seeing you all here now
I finally understand that it's destiny!
Dipper, the pine tree.
Mabel, the shooting star.
The question mark.
This one's unsolvable.
That one's easy.
You've been rockin' that dumb
hoodie since the seventh grade.
Whoa. Destiny hoodie!
The tent of telepathy sign!
That must be Gideon.
Whoo!
An excuse to stand next to Mabel!
- Don't turn this into a big deal.
- Oh, I won't.
I will.
What the...
Hey, Achilles!
Nice work with the heel!
Fore!
Hold hands, everyone! This is
a mystical human energy circuit.
Ice? Who's Ice?
They symbol's needn't
all be literal, Dipper.
It just has to be someone
cool in the face of danger.
Wendy! Wendy!
Shut up, you guys.
Much like the spectacles
need to be someone scholarly.
- Heh heh!
- This is freaky.
Now hold hands, everyone.
Ew! I'm not touching that.
Do it, sweetie. Do the
one thing no one in our
family has ever done...
touch the hillbilly.
Great-uncle Ford, I think it's working!
Yes, this is it!
The rest of you get out!
It's too dangerous!
We just need one more person...
Stanley! Stanley, get over here!
You're the only one left.
You realize this is
a bunch of hogwash, right?
You really think some caveman graffiti
is gonna stop that monster?
Dang it, old man, now's not the time!
- Come on!
- What are you doing? You're gonna ruin this!
I've never held hands this
long, and I very uncomfortable!
Whoa. Hey, I'm not
the enemy here, people.
Don't forget who literally
created the end of the world.
I'm sorry, Stanley. I know.
Just help me fix it! Please!
Fine. Just do one thing.
Say "thank you."
- What?
- I spent thirty years
trying to bring you
back into this dimension,
and you still haven't thanked me!
You want me to shake your hand?
Say "thank you"!
- Fine. Thank you.
- Now, see?
Between me and him, I'm
not always the bad twin.
Between "him and me."
Grammar, Stanley.
I'll "Grammar, Stanley"  you,
you stuck-up son-of-a...
Don't jeopardize this, you idiot!
- Everything's on the line!
- Stop it!
Join hands!
Oh, no, it's Bill!
Right? Isn't that what
you're all thinking?
Hey, Gideon, why aren't you dancing?
Chop chop, huh?
Ha ha ha ho!
This is just too perfect!
Didn't you brainiacs know
the zodiac doesn't work
if you don't all hold hands?
And what's better,
you've brought every
threat to my power together
in one easy-to-destroy circle!
Oh, no!
- My hair!
- My hair also!
You guys want to see what
happens to your friends
when you can't get along?
- Hey! You give them back!
- You've gone too far, cipher!
Yeah! We're not scared of you!
Oh, but you should be.
Oh, no!
Ya know, this castle could
really use some decoration!
Looks like it's too late
for your friends, Stanford!
Kids!
But you can still save your family!
Last chance: Tell me how
to take Weirdmageddon global
and I'll spare the kids!
- No! Don't do it!
- Yeah! Bill makes bad deals!
Don't you toy with me, shooting star!
I see everything!
Ow! Not again!
Why?! Every time!
Nice shot, pumpkin!
I just regenerated that eye!
I know that hurts, because I've
accidentally done it to myself...
multiple times!
Save yourselves!
Run! We'll take care of Bill!
What?! That's a suicide mission!
- Trust us. We've beat him before...
- and we'll beat him again!
Hey, Bill!
Come and get us, you pointy jerk!
What? No! It's too dangerous!
Not so fast! You two wait here!
I've got some children
I need to make into corpses!
See ya real soon!
Bill, no!
- Oh! What do we do? What do we do?
- Kids!
When I get my hands on you kids,
I'm gonna disassemble your molecules!
You've tricked me for the last time!
Ohh! I can't believe this!
The kids are gonna die,
and it's all my fault...
because I couldn't
shake your stupid hand!
Ahh, Dad was right about me.
I am a screw-up.
Ah, don't blame yourself. I'm
the one who made a deal with
Bill in the first place. I
fell for all his easy flattery.
You would have seen him
for the scam artist he is.
How did things get so
messed up between us?
We used to be like Dipper and Mabel.
The world's about to end
and they still work together.
- How do they do it?
- Easy. They're kids.
They don't know any better.
Whoa, where you goin'?
I'm gonna play the
only card we have left.
Let Bill into my mind.
He'll be able to take over the
galaxy, and maybe even worse,
but at least he might
let the kids free.
What?! Are you kiddin' me?!
Are you honestly telling me
there's nothing else we can do?!
Bill's only weak in the mind space.
If I didn't have this
darn plate in my head,
we could just erase
him with the memory gun
when he steps inside my mind.
What if he goes into my mind?
My brain isn't good for anything.
There's nothing in your mind
he wants. It has to be me.
We need to take his deal.
It's the only way he'll agree
to save you and the kids.
Do you really think he's
gonna make good on that deal?
What other choice do we have?
I'm starting to think
there's no way out of here.
Like Grunkle Stan always says,
when one door closes,
choose a nearby wall and
bash it in with brute force!
Ha! Now let's round up the townsfolk,
and together we can defeat...
Oh, no!
- You'll never take us alive, monsters!
- That's fine with us!
- Oh, no!
- Peek-a-boo!
All right, Ford, time's up!
I've got the kids!
I think I'm gonna kill one of
'em now, just for the heck of it!
Eeenie-meenie...
minee...
Wait!
I surrender!
Good choice.
Don't do it, Ford!
It'll destroy the universe!
It's the only way!
Even when you're about to die, you
Pines twins just can't get along!
My only condition is that you
let my brother and the kids go.
Fine.
No, Grunkle Ford!
Don't trust him!
It's a.... deal!
Oh, I'm here. I'm finally here!
Look at this place...
a perfect, calm, orderly void.
Gotta hand it to you, Ford,
you really know how to clear your...
What?!
Ha ha! Do a pretty good
impression of my brother, don't I?
Switch clothes and no
one can tell us apart.
Welcome to my mind.
Surprised you didn't recognize it.
What?! The deal's off!
What the... No, no, no, no!
Oh, yeah.
You're goin' down, Bill.
You're gettin' erased.
Memory gun. Pretty clever, huh?
Y-You idiot! Don't you realize
you're destroying your own mind too?
Eh. It's not like I was using
this space for much anyway.
Let me out of here! Let me...
Oh... Why isn't this working?!
Hey, look at me. Turn around and
look at me, you one-eyed demon!
You're a real wiseguy, but
you made one fatal mistake.
You messed with my family.
You're making a mistake!
I'll give you anything...
money, fame, riches,
infinite power, your own galaxy!
Please! No!
What's happening to me?!
Staaanleeey!
Heh. Guess I was good
for something after all.
Hey! Hey!
- Oh...
- Ohh!
Whoa. Huh.
Oh, my gosh!
Grunkle Stan, you did it!
Oh, uh, hey there... kiddo.
What's your name?
- Grunkle Stan?
- Heh. Who ya talkin' to?
C-Come on. It's me.
It's me, Grunkle Stan!
Grunkle Stan, it's me!
We had to erase his mind to
defeat Bill. It's all gone.
Stan has no idea, but he did it.
He saved the world.
He saved me.
You're our hero, Stanley.
Hey, this is a real
nice place ya got here.
It's your place, Grunkle Stan.
Don't you remember?
Even a little?
Nope, but this chair hugs
my butt like it remembers.
Ah.
Hey, why the long faces?
You guys look like
it's someone's funeral.
Who's that big guy crying
in the corner?
We saved the world,
but what's the point?
Grunkle Stan's not himself anymore.
There's gotta be something
we can do to jog his memory!
There isn't.
I'm sorry. Stan's gone.
I know my Grunkle
is in there somewhere!
There's gotta be something around
here that can help bring him back!
This'll work! This has to work!
Here's the first day we came
to Gravity Falls, Grunkle Stan.
And here's a macaroni
interpretation of my emotions.
That time we went fishing.
That Summerween we spent together.
Don't you remember anything?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what this is
or who you are or...
Gah! Quit it, Waddles!
I'm trying to remember my life story!
What did you say?
I said get Waddles off of me!
It's working! Keep reading!
Skip to my page!
He needs to remember our
boss-employee relationship.
Hey! Just cause I have amnesia,
don't go tryin' to give
yourself a raise, Soos.
- It's happening! Keep going!
- OK. OK!
"Day Two. Grunkle Stan smells
weird but we're starting to bond.
He told us a lot about being
a businessman in the '80s
and seemed happy when
we pretended to listen.
He also gave me a grappling hook
which everyone is impressed by.
And in more important news,
I've met some neighborhood hotties!"
_
Good Morning, Gravity Falls!
It's another beautiful day,
but every day is beautiful
now that the...
unpleasantness is over.
Git outta here, ya ornery critters!
Ah, good as new.
Oh! Looks like you've got a friend!
Robbie, would you be a dear and
get us the sawed off shotgun?
Ugh. Fine, whatever.
- Brains and so forth!
- Nope! None of that, thank you.
None of us really understand
what just happened,
and none of us want to.
That's why I'm passing
the "Never Mind All That" Act.
If anyone goes asking
around about the "events"
of the last few days, what do we say?
Never Mind All That!
And if you break the rules,
we're gonna zap ya!
Zap! Zap!
We're mad with power!
And love.
In other news,
the Northwest family has gone broke.
After pledging his allegiance to Bill
and then placing all his
savings in weirdness bonds,
Preston Northwest had
to sell his mansion
to preserve his family fortune.
You're only going to have one pony now!
But fortunes have also turned for
local maniac Fiddleford McGucket
who, after regaining his sanity,
has made millions overnight
submitting his patents
to the US government.
I'm gonna buy me a bigger shed!
Hey, that one's for sale!
In other good news,
town hero Stanley Pines
has fully recovered his memory
and will be throwing a party
to celebrate his niece and
nephew's thirteenth birthday
and final day in town.
But other than that, I can safely say
our beloved Gravity
Falls is back to normal.
- And now, Bodacious T, with sports.
- It's called Death Ball!
♪ ...to you ♪
I can't believe you all got together
just to throw a party for us!
After all the Pines family
has done for the town,
it's the least we could do!
You've helped everyone here.
Thanks to y'all savin' us, I
learned to open my heart to kindness.
No more evil-doin'.
From now on, I'm gonna try to
be Li'l Gideon, regular ol' kid.
Oh... Ha ha! Whoo!
I am bustin' a move
on this skatin' board.
More like busting your pants, loser!
Hee hee hee!
- Dude, make a wish, dawg!
- Ya know, on my first day here,
if you had asked me what
I wanted, I would have said
adventure, mystery, true friends.
But looking here at all of you,
I realize that every wish came true...
- I have everything I wanted.
- If I had only one wish,
it would be to shrink all
of you with a shrink ray
and bring you home with us in my pocket.
But since that's impossible...
Is that impossible?
Since that's probably impossible,
my only wish is for everyone
to sign my scrapbook.
I'll never forget you guys.
Wait.
Now I'll never forget you guys!
I now officially declare you:
technically teenagers.
Welcome to Angst and Acne Forever.
One of us! One of us!
- Whoo-hee!
- Whoopee!
- So how do you feel?
- Samey, but differenty.
Hey, you two.
When are you gonna open
your presents already?
- I broke a nail wrapping them.
- Ha ha! Pacifica.
Stanley, I need to talk to you.
I didn't want to say anything
with everyone listening,
but we've got a problem.
Weirdmageddon has been
contained, but I'm detecting
some strange new anomalies
near the Arctic Ocean.
I want to go investigate it,
but I think I might be
too old to go it alone.
Are you sayin' you
need someone to help you
sail around the world on
the adventure of a lifetime?
I don't just want someone
to come with me, Stanley.
I want it to be you.
Will you give me a second chance?
You think we'll find treasure?
And babes?
Heh!
I'd say there's a high probability!
But what should we do
with the Mystery Shack?
I think the town's
had enough mystery for one lifetime.
Are you thinkin' what I'm thinkin'?
Everyone, I have an
announcement to make.
Me and my... Heh!...
nerdy bro over here
have some catchin' up to do,
we're gonna be away for a while.
That's why I'm shutting down
the Mystery Shack for good!
You shut down your mouth for good!
I'm sorry, Mr. Pineses,
it's just that this shack is
the most magical place on Earth.
Sure, the attractions are all fake,
but dreams aren't fake.
Like this mermaid:
It's not just a dead fish butt
sewn to a monkey carcass,
it's a marvelous creature
that makes us believe
that anything is possible.
You shut down this shack,
and you shut down our dreams!
At least... my dreams.
Aw.
I'm sorry, Soos, it's just
there's no one around to run it.
At least there wouldn't be
if I hadn't just found
the perfect replacement.
Ladies and gentlemen, the Mystery Shack
is under new management!
You... You mean it, Mister Mystery?
You're Mister Mystery now, Soos.
Try not to burn the place down.
I'll move in immediately.
Do you really have to go?
There is still so much
we haven't done together.
Summer's over, Candy.
It's time for us to grow up.
But not too much.
I hate my dumb heart
for making me feel things!
- Cut. It. Out. Heart!
- Hey, can you punch my heart too?
No, mine!
Punch my feelings away!
Candy and Grenda,
thank you for being my people.
You'll always be my best friends.
Grunkle Stan, thanks for
wearing my Goodbye sweater.
Ah, it's cold out. I had to.
What? But it's, like,
eighty-something degrees out today.
Can it, Soos!
- Hey. You mean a lot to me, man.
- You too.
Something to remember me by.
Oh, and this.
Read it the next time
you miss Gravity Falls.
Last bus leaving Gravity Falls.
All aboard.
Guess we said goodbye to
everyone except... Waddles.
I... don't know how to
explain this, but...
Mom and Dad won't let me bring
a pig home to California, so...
you have to stay here!
Come on, come on!
I have to go.
I'm... I'm sorry, Waddles!
Ah! You know what?
Forget it!
I lived with this pig all summer,
now your parents are gonna have to!
Hey, bus guy!
This pig is coming with the kids!
Now, hold on a second. Bringing
animals aboard a moving vehicle
is strictly prohibited by...
Wah... W-Welcome aboard.
You can sit in the front row, pig.
Kids, you knuckleheads
were nothin' but a nuisance
and I'm glad to be rid of ya.
We'll miss you too, Grunkle Stan.
- Ready to head into the unknown?
- Nope.
Let's do it.
- Bye! Bye, everybody!
- I'll miss you guys too!
Bye, dudes! Bye!
If you've ever taken a road
trip through the Pacific Northwest,
you've probably seen a bumper sticker
for a place called Gravity Falls.
Well, I've moved in.
It's not on any maps,
and most people have never heard of it.
Some people think it's a myth.
But if you're curious, don't wait.
Take a trip.
Find it.
_
It's out there somewhere
in the woods... waiting.
_
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~
2x11 - "Not What He Seems"
Come on, come on. Should be
just enough to finish the job.
Phew! Can't be too careful
with this stuff.
"Warning."
Blah blah blah...
"Extreme usage could result
in minor gravity anomalies."
Can it, Poindexter.
I've come this far.
I'm not giving up now.
Yes, this is it!
It's gonna be a bumpy ride,
but it'll all be worth it.
Just eighteen more hours.
Finally, everything changes...
today.
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~
It's here!
It's here! It's here!
Okay, so I was
just opening random doors,
because I'm a creep, when
I found something amazing!
If it was worth waking up at
7:00 am for, that will be amazing.
- Feast your eyes!
- Whoa!
Bro. Bro.
We're both thinkin' it.
Crazy rooftop fireworks party!
Not so fast, kids.
There is no way on Earth
you're setting off those
dangerous, illegal fireworks...
without me.
Here you go, sweetie!
Set something on fire
for your Grunkle Stan!
I am the god of destruction!
- Whoa!
- Yay! Whoo!
Hold on a minute.
Do you have a permit for those?
Uh...
Uh, do you have a permit
for being totally lame?
Hey-o!
Well, I can't argue with that.
Carry on.
But seriously, though, we should
probably clean this mess up.
- With water balloons?
- I don't see why not.
Seriously?
- Ow.
- Whoo!
Ah, this is what Saturdays are for.
Doing dumb things forever!
Dumb things forever!
Whoa, there!
To Grunkle Stan!
Not just a great uncle...
The greatest uncle!
All right, all right. I tell ya,
it's unnatural for siblings
to get along as well as you do.
Don't worry, we've
still got plenty of summer left
to drive each other crazy.
Heh... yeah...
plenty of summer left.
Kids, there's something I, uh...
something I should tell you.
It's, um...
W-well, it's complicated.
I...
I'm gonna go refresh my soda.
Enjoy it while you can, Stan.
They'll find out sooner or later.
Today's the day.
What is that, a ladybug?
What the... Oh, no!
Target's secure!
Take the house!
What the... ?
Kids are secure.
Roof team, go!
Clear!
Pig secure... we have secured a pig.
Hey, hands off, you stooge!
I don't understand!
What did I do that warrants
this much arresting?
The government guys?
I thought you got eaten by zombies.
- We survived... barely.
- I used Trigger as a human shield.
- He cried like a baby.
- Wha... Hey!
Not in front of the special ops guys.
This is security footage of
a government waste facility.
At 0400 hours last night, someone
robbed 300 gallons of dangerous waste.
What? You think that's me?
Don't play dumb with us, Pines!
But I actually am dumb!
Last night I was restocking
- the gift shop... I swear!
- Wait, Grunkle Stan!
You've got the wrong guy!
Our Grunkle Stan might shoplift
the occasional tangerine, but
he's not some evil supervillain.
Listen, kid. We've been
watching your family all summer,
and we've seen some disturbing things,
but nothing as dangerous as
what your uncle is hiding.
Somewhere hidden in this
shack is a doomsday device!
Trigger, you take the children.
I'll talk to the old man.
Sorry to break it to you, kids,
but you don't know your uncle at all.
- Icee pop, clear!
- Hey!
Kids! You gotta believe me!
For once I'm actually innocent!
Kids!
♪ Headin' into work,
doot doo doo doo doo ♪
Ground team, move move move!
- Break down the door!
- Or... maybe not.
Stanford Pines, you stand accused
of theft of government waste,
conspiracy, and possession
of illegal weapons.
How do you plead to these charges?
Uh... "guiltoccent."
I mean, "innoguilty."
Um...
Can I have my phone call?
Okay, give me whatever you
got that comes with a free toy.
Soos!
Mr. Pines? Is this some
sort of possession situation?
Soos, pick up!
Mr. Pines, what happened?
I heard you got arrested or something?
I had to go get some panic food.
Listen, I need something from you.
You know that vending
machine in the gift shop?
I need you to guard it with your life.
No matter what happens,
no matter who talks to you,
don't let them touch that machine!
Time for a repair guy...
to become a repair man.
Sir, your Junior Yum-Yum
Baby-Time Kiddo Meal?
Just put one in my mouth.
Let's do this.
We've got Mr. Pines in custody.
Our men are searching
the shack for that device.
You take care of those kids.
What are you gonna do to us?
- We'll be taking you to child services.
- Boo!
In the meantime, enjoy
some mindless reality TV...
designed to pacify you and
make you stop asking questions.
I'm about to make the incision.
Ker-prank!
You're watching Ker-Prank'd
with Justin Ker-Prank.
Dipper, this is crazy.
There's no way Stan was
stealing hazardous waste.
- We gotta clear his name!
- Hmm...
Wait a minute, the security tapes!
Didn't Stan say he was restocking
the gift shop last night?
If we could get the Mystery
Shack's surveillance tapes,
we could prove he's innocent!
We just need to think
of a way out of here.
Think, Mabel. Think.
No!
Oh oh oh...
Mayday, mayday!
Agent down!
- Darn branch!
- Yes!
Backup! Requesting backup!
Come on, Dipper. We're gonna
go clear our uncle's name.
Oh, you poor kids. You really
think your uncle's innocent?
I've seen it all before.
False names, double lives.
One minute, they're
playing with water balloons.
The next, they're
building doomsday devices.
Your uncle scammed the whole world.
You gonna let him scam you, too?
You... You don't know
what you're talking about.
You're gonna regret this!
Only five more hours till it happens.
I gotta be there!
Come on, Stan,
you gotta think of a way out of this.
Think! Think!
Huh?
They're getting stronger!
Of course, that's it!
H-hey! Whoa!
Is it just me, or did the
entire world just hiccup?
I'm sure it's just
a baby-sized earthquake.
Aww, baby-sized!
It's happening!
The end times!
When that machine activates,
I gotta get outta town!
Git in there, raccoon wife, git!
Eh?
All right, here's the plan.
I'll take out those
two guard guys, you karate-chop
the other dude in the neck,
and then we'll back-flip
through the front door!
Mabel, aren't you forgetting
the simpler solution?
Oh, right.
- So is it a rock, or is it a face?
- I think... it's a metaphor.
All right. If I was Stan,
where would I hide
those surveillance tapes?
Wait! The Antelabbit!
Don't you mean "jackalope"?
Pfft! That can't be right.
Yes!
It's this week!
This is it!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Someone yelled "Wormy Dance."
We had to!
Fast-forward.
Ha! There it is!
Stan restocking, like he said.
And the date shows it was last night!
It's proof! He's innocent!
- Uh-oh.
- Uh, maybe he's just
going to the bathroom outdoors,
the way nature intended.
Oh, no. Stan, you didn't!
Don't panic. That could
be anyone in that suit.
Hot Belgian waffles!
Wait, I'm alone. I can
swear for real! Son-of-a...
That's him, all right.
Okay, okay. So maybe Grunkle
Stan stole some toxic waste.
That doesn't mean he's leading
a nefarious double life.
Mabel, I'm not so sure about that.
What? What is all this?
Stetson Pinefield?
Hal Forrester?
Andrew "8-Ball" Alcatraz?
These are fake IDs, Mabel!
You wouldn't need these
unless you were trying to
hide your real identity.
But why would Stan do that?
What?
"Stan Pines Dead"?
"Foul play
suspected in Pines' death."
"Fiery car crash, brakes cut... "
By who?
"Unnamed grifter at large"?
Why would they call him "unnamed"?
- Unless Stan...
- ... isn't...
Stan?!
Stan Pines is dead?
Then who have we been living with?
It doesn't make any sense!
There has to be some explanation.
Maybe we're getting Ker-Pranked!
Justin Ker-Prank is gonna
jump up from behind one of
these plants, any minute now!
Any minute, Justin.
Can't believe it! This whole summer
I've been looking for answers,
and the biggest mystery
was right under our nose.
There's gotta be some kind of
explanation in here, somewhere.
What the... ?
"Secret Code to Hideout"?
Let me see that!
A1, B, C3...
- I've never seen a code like this.
- Wait, I have!
Dipper, it's the vending machine!
All right, Pines.
Play time is over.
Chopper's ready to
dust off to Washington.
I'll enjoy putting you away.
What? Um, can't we stick
around for maybe one minute,
uh, one minute, thirty seconds?
We're not falling for your games, Pines.
You've been running your whole life.
Your time is finally up.
Bathroom break?
Just gimme 15 seconds.
Sorry, but you've got a flight to catch.
Oh, yeah? So do you!
Huh?
Whoa, whoa, hey!
Hey!
Dang it, get back here!
Men, get him!
No!
You won't get away with this!
Gonna get ya! Gonna get ya!
Ow!
Whoa!
- You know where the Mystery Shack is?
- Uh, yeah.
Okay, here's a hundred bucks.
Drive as far away from
the Shack as possible,
and don't stop when the
cops start chasing you!
He's getting away!
Obviously, follow that cab!
Stanford escaped! He's at large!
We need to sweep the town!
Move, move, move!
All right, Soos, remember the plan.
Protect the machine, earn Stan's trust,
legally get adopted by Stan,
change name to Stan Junior.
- Soos!
- Oh, kids, where have you been?
W-what are you doing here?
Stan gave me a mission
to protect this machine.
Ha!
And I thought I loved snacks!
Soos, listen.
Something huge is going on here.
If Stan is hiding some dangerous secret,
we need to find out what it is!
- I need you to step aside.
- Yeah, just let us through
so we can prove this is all
just a big misunderstanding.
Guys, I know this seems crazy,
but I promised Stan I would
guard this with my life.
I'm sorry, Soos.
Attack glitter!
It's pretty, but it hurts!
- Please, Soos!
- C'mon, Soos!
Aw, c'mon, I don't wanna fight you guys!
This hurts me more than it hurts you!
Seriously, it hurts me
way more than it hurts you.
Ohh...
It's like something from a video game.
- Or a dream.
- Or a nightmare.
I gotta be there when it happens!
Guys, are we dreaming?
Somebody wake me up.
This... can't be real.
I don't understand. Why
would Mr. Pines have all this?
It's just like that bunker in the woods.
But what is it doing
underneath the Mystery Shack?
Okay, okay, so he's got
a huge, gigantic lab.
That doesn't mean anything bad.
Everyone's got secrets!
It's still Stan, and he loves us.
- And we love him, right?
- Can't be... it's impossible.
The other two journals?!
All this time, all this time,
Stan had them?!
I can't believe it!
Was anything he said to us real?!
- Why would he have those journals?!
- Maybe he's the author.
Or maybe he stole them from the author!
Maybe the reason he has
all of those fake IDs
is because he is a master criminal,
and this machine is his master plan!
Whoa!
"I was wrong the whole time."
"The machine was meant to create
knowledge, but it is too powerful!"
"I was deceived, and now it is too late!"
- "The device, if fully operational,"
- "could tear our universe apart!"
"It must not fall into the wrong hands.
"If the clock ever reaches zero,
our universe is doomed."
It's the final countdown!
Just like they always sung about!
The agents were right!
We have to shut it down!
There! Quick!
Turn these! Together!
That's it!
The shutdown switch!
This all stops now!
Don't touch that button!
Dipper, just back away.
Please don't press that shutdown
button. You gotta trust me.
And I should trust you, why?
After you stole radioactive waste,
after you lied to us all summer!
- I don't even know who you are!
- Look, I know this all seems nuts,
but I need that machine to stay on.
If you just let me explain...
Oh! Oh, no!
Brace yourselves!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
T-minus 35 seconds.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Whoa!
Dipper!
Mabel! Hurry!
Shut it down!
No!
Mabel, Mabel, wait!
Stop!
Soos, what are you doing?
I gave you an order!
Sorry, Mr. Pines,
if that is your real name,
but I have a new mission now,
protecting these kids!
Soos, you idiot, let me go!
- Let me go! C'mon!
- Mabel, press the red button!
- Shut it down!
- No, you can't! You gotta trust me!
Grunkle Stan, I don't even
know if you're my Grunkle!
I wanna believe you, but...
Then listen to me.
Remember this morning,
when I said I wanted to
tell you guys something?
T-minus 20 seconds.
I wanted to say that you're gonna
hear some bad things about me,
and some of 'em are true, but trust
me, everything I've worked for,
everything I care about,
it's all for this family.
Mabel, what if he's lying?
This thing could destroy the universe!
Listen to your head!
Look into my eyes, Mabel!
You really think I'm a bad guy?
He's lying!
Shut it down, now!
- Mabel, please!
- Ten, nine...
Grunkle Stan...
Six, five...
I trust you.
Mabel, are you crazy?!
We're all gonna...
One.
Nooo!
W-What? Who is that?
The author of the journals...
... my brother.
- Is this the part where one of us faints?
- Oh, I am so on it, dude.
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~
Thirty long years
and it's all led up to this.
My greatest achievement!
Probably
should have worn pants.
Agh!
Feisty, I like it.
If I finally pull this off, it
will all have been worth it.
I just need to keep
playing it cool.
If anyone ever finds out
about this...
Yeah, right.
I've come this far.
Who could possibly
catch me now?
See there, there it is again.
We haven't seen
readings like this for 30 years.
Is it coming from deep space?
An enemy weapons site?
Just as I suspected.
Gentlemen, we're going
to Gravity Falls.
Oh, right.
Show time.
Welcome to the grand
re-opening of the Mystery Shack!
Mystery Shack!
We're here to celebrate the defeat
of that skunk little Gideon.
Boo!
Please, please, boo harder.
But I didn't catch
that pork chop all alone.
These two scams deserve
some of the glory.
Oh!
Okay, okay.
Most of the glory.
Smile for the camera.
Your camera's
a cinder block, Toby.
I just want to be
a part of things.
Smile for a real camera.
Everyone say
"something stupid."
Something stupid!
And don't forget to come to the
after party tonight at 8:00.
We're doing
a karaoke bonanza, people.
Lights! Music! Enchantment!
Phoo!
And an amazing karaoke
performance by our family band,
Love Patrol Alpha.
Oh, I don't know about that.
I would never
agree to that ever.
Too late, I wrote your names
on the list.
It's happening.
Buy your ticket, people.
You know you don't have anything
else going on in your lives.
I'm talking to you, pizza guy.
Don't lame out on me.
Ha!
The town loves us.
We finally got that Gideon
smell out of the carpet.
Everything
is finally going my way.
Hey, Grunkle Stan,
now that we have a moment,
I've been meaning to ask you
for my journal back.
What? Journal?
Oh, you mean this old thing?
It was so boring
I couldn't even finish it.
You didn't see nothing.
Wait, you're just gonna
give it to me?
Just like that?
What else do you want?
A kiss on the cheek?
I-- I got to go.
Whoa!
I wouldn't mind
a kiss on the cheek.
Not gonna happen.
Mabel, we've got to talk.
Almost losing my journal
made me realize
that I'm halfway
through the summer
and still no closer
to figuring out
the big mysteries
of Gravity Falls.
Gideon almost
destroyed the town
to get his hands
on this journal.
But why?
Who wrote it?
Where are
all the other journals?
What was Bill talking about when he
said everything was going to change?
There's something huge
going on right under our noses.
And it's time we stop goofing
around and get to the bottom of it.
Bro, you've looked at that
thing, like, a bazillion times.
There's nothing
left to discover.
Half the pages are blank,
remember?
I just feel like I'm one puzzle piece
away from figuring out everything.
Don't worry, Dipper.
Lord Mystery Ham
is on the case.
"I play by me own rules!
What? What?"
I don't know
why I tell you things.
Do you hear that?
Hey, Mr. Pines,
what's that code word
I'm supposed to yell
when I see a government vehicle?
Wait, what?
Government vehicle?
The Mystery Shack is now closed.
Everybody out!
I will not hesitate to use
the hose on the elderly.
Uncle Stan, what's happening?
Yeah, you never
shut down the gift shop.
Welcome to the Mystery Shack,
gentlemen.
What can I get you?
Key chains?
Snow globes?
These rare
photos of American Presidents?
My name is Agent Powers.
This is Agent Trigger.
We're here to investigate reports of
mysterious activity in this town.
Activity.
Mysterious activity
in the Mystery Shack?
You got to be joking.
I assure you I am not.
I was born with a rare disorder
that makes me
physically incapable
of experiencing humor.
I don't understand that sound
you're making with your mouth.
Now if you'll excuse us, we're
conducting an investigation.
Investigation.
Wait, wait.
Did you guys say you're investigating
the mysteries of this town?
That information is classified.
But, yes.
Look, between you and me,
I believe there is a conspiracy
of paranormal origin
all connected to this town.
We're just one small lead away
from blowing
the lid off this
entire mystery.
Are you kidding me?
I'm investigating
the exact same thing.
I found this journal in the woods
which has almost all the answers.
If we work together,
we could crack the case.
If you have evidence of these
claims, we should talk.
We can talk right now.
Please, please, come in.
I have so much to show you.
I'm sorry, agents.
Kid has an overactive imagination
and, like, a sweating problem.
Zing!
Paranormal town stuff,
it's just part of gift shop lore.
Sells more tickets, you know.
Pop-poro-po-po.
Swag.
We have other spots
to investigate.
We'll be on our way.
I'm confiscating
this for evidence.
Smart move.
Wait!
No, wait!
We have so much to talk about.
Hold it, kiddo.
Trust me, the last thing you want
around here in a party is cops.
I'm confiscating that card.
And how's about
you go be a normal kid?
Flirt with a girl,
or steal a pie off a windowsill.
But, Grunkle Stan,
you don't understand.
And don't go talking
to those agents.
That could have
been my big break.
Bro, maybe Grunkle Stan
is right.
We're throwing
a party tonight.
Can't you go one night
without searching
for aliens or raising
the dead or whatever?
I'm not gonna raise the dead.
I just need a chance to show
those agents my book.
Trust me, Dipper.
The only book you'll need
tonight is right here.
Boo!
I say "kara," you say "oke."
Kara...
I could do this all day.
Agh!
Well, the confetti
cannon works.
And the karaoke machine
has all the best songs.
"We built this township
on rock and roll."
"Danger lane
to highway town."
"Taking over midnight"
by AmperSandra.
Listen, kid, you do not want
to hear this voice singing.
Trust me.
Grunkle Stan, karaoke
isn't about sounding good.
It's about
sounding terrible, together.
Check it out! These black lights
make my teeth look scary.
It's like a crime scene
in my mouth.
Come on, you'll love it.
It's not fair.
Finally I meet someone
who can help me
solve the mysteries of this town
and Stan confiscates their card.
Dude, I probably
shouldn't be telling you this,
but I'm pretty sure Stan hides
like everything in his room.
If I go into Stan's room,
I could get in so much trouble.
Yeah, you're probably right.
That's what
makes it fun, dummy.
Man, I can't wait to smash
these Stanatas.
Smash!
Grenda has entered the party!
Stan's brains look delicious.
Girls!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my gosh, Mabel!
Is that a boom box sweater?
See for yourself.
Poke!
Yeah, yeah!
Work it! Ah!
Aw!
I thought this was
gonna be a rave.
Thompson, take off your shirt
and make it a rave.
I'll do anything
for your approval.
Oh, come on.
I promise I won't
send it to anyone.
Who's got one good eye
and one good pie?
These kegs are full of meat.
Tambry sends me
the craziest text.
The whole town is showing up and
no sign of those pesky agents.
Wendy, Dipper, how are those
posters coming along?
Hmm.
I'll keep an eye out for Stan.
You go rustle through
his weird old man biz.
All right, Grunkle Stan,
where did you hide that card?
Nothing.
Ew!
Pretending I never saw that.
Wait a minute.
Yes!
I got it!
Agent Powers.
Hi, this is Dipper.
The kid from the Mystery Shack, the
one with the, um, sweating problem.
I have that journal
I wanted to show you.
And you're certain this journal
will help our case?
I'm 100% positive.
Very well.
We're on our way.
Sorry, Dipper.
I got distracted.
Kid, why did you call
those agents?
I've told you once,
I've told you 100 times,
there's nothing supernatural
going on in Gravity Falls.
Yes, there is.
After everything that's happened,
you have to know that by now.
All I know
is that your dumb obsession
is gonna get us all in trouble
one of these days.
Now go enjoy
the rest of the party,
'cause when it's over,
you're grounded.
Hmm.
Hey, boys, looking good!
Gorney, you clean up nice.
Mr. Poolcheck,
move those crazy legs.
You-- You weird pool man.
What's the problem, officers?
Did you catch my face
going 90 smiles per hour?
We've got complaints about
the loudest party in town.
Three words.
We want in.
Welcome to your dreams.
Guys, I'm so glad to see you.
Working together, we can crack all
the big questions of Gravity Falls.
Trust me, this book is the lead
you've been looking for.
I'm thinking
full-scale investigation.
Forensics, researchers.
Do you guys have a helicopter?
I'm sorry, "helicopters".
Kid, I'd love to believe you,
but this just looks like
more junk
from your uncle's gift shop.
I mean, "leprecorn"?
I can't be the only one
that thinks that it's not funny.
I can confirm.
Not funny.
No, it's real, I swear.
You should
"send it to the lab".
Am I saying that right?
Your uncle was right about
that overactive imagination.
We've got paperwork to do, kid.
- Boring paperwork.
- Wait!
This book is real.
Gnomes, cursed objects, spells!
Listen!
Uh...
Corpus Levitas!
Uh, Diablo Dominus!
Um, Mondo Vicium!
Huh?
Ha, a zombie!
A real actual zombie, see.
Spooky journal, 100% real.
Now can we work together?
- Mother of all that is holy.
- What do we do?
It's just one zombie.
Trust me, I see stuff like this
all the time.
Good thing
it was just that one.
Oh, my gosh.
You guys can help, right?
Kid, we've been chasing
the paranormal for years,
but we've never seen
anything like this before.
Get down!
Oh, my gosh.
What have I done?
♪ What up, fools?
It's Blubs and Durls ♪
♪ Making all that money
and getting them girls ♪
Oh!
What do you say, guys?
Is this party legendary?
When I say Mabel,
you say Pines.
Mabel!
We're all gonna die!
Why does that never work?
Whoa, whoa.
I think it's an earthquake.
Hey, everybody, we got
to get out of here!
We're all doomed.
Quick!
Into my getaway pouch!
Mabel,
escape while you still can!
Wait! No!
Don't leave!
You haven't even done
our family karaoke song yet.
Dipper, what's the one thing
I asked you not to do tonight?
Raise the dead.
- And what did you do?
- Raise the dead.
Get back, dudes.
This is about to get intense.
Sorry, one second.
You've got to admit
this is pretty cool.
Zombies!
Don't panic. Maybe they're just
a really ugly flash mob.
Dudes, stay calm.
I've been training for
this moment my whole life.
With all the horror movies
I've seen,
I know literally everything there is
to know about how to avoid zombies.
Second thought,
gonna flip the script.
Can I eat your brains?
Yay or nay?
Seeing some yay faces
over here.
Quick, the golf cart.
Oh, come on.
That's a bummer.
Good news for me though.
Soos!
Sorry, dude, I just really
want those brains.
Stay back!
Give it up, dudes.
Your fighting only makes us
look more rad.
What do we do?
Where's Grunkle Stan?
How's he supposed to help?
He doesn't even believe
in the supernatural.
Those agents
could ruin everything.
Darn kid!
He has no idea
what he's messing with.
He's stubborn.
That's his problem.
Sort of like me, I suppose.
I got too much on my mind to
worry about those kids right now.
All right, let's see.
Take that, sucker!
This thing's a surprisingly
good weapon.
We need to board up
all the windows.
Okay,
maybe that will hold them.
- Oh!
- Hi, dudes.
By the way, I taught the zombies
how to get to the fuse box.
Among these dudes
I'm like a genius.
Get those brains, dog.
Dipper, isn't there something in the
journal about defeating zombies?
No! There's nothing in here
about weaknesses.
This can't be happening.
I wanted answers so bad
I put everyone in danger.
Now we're toast.
It's all my fault
and no one can save us.
No!
Mabel, I'm sorry!
Dipper!
You two, attic, now!
Grunkle-- Grunkle Stan?
I said now!
All right, you undead jerks,
you ready to die twice?
The only wrinkly monster
who harasses my family is me.
Take that!
And that!
Beat it, no-eyes.
Anyone else want a piece?
Oh! Ow!
Everything hurts.
Grunkle Stan, that was amazing!
Are you all right?
Well, at least, you can't deny
magic exists anymore, right?
Kid, I've always known.
Wait.
What are you talking about?
I'm not an idiot, Dipper.
Of course, this town is weird
and the one thing
I know about that weirdness
is that it's dangerous.
I've been lying about it to try
to keep you away from it,
to try to protect you from it.
It looks like I didn't lie
well enough.
What do we do?
Normally,
the journal would help us,
but there's nothing in there
about defeating zombies.
It's hopeless.
Wait, wait, wait, the text!
It's glowing
in the black light.
What?
All this time I thought
I knew all the journal secrets.
But they're written
in some kind of invisible ink.
Invisible ink?
This is it.
"Zombies have a weakness!
Previously thought
to be invincible,
their skulls can be shattered by
a perfect three part harmony."
Three part harmony?
How can we create that?
I have a naturally
high pitched scream.
I can make noises with my body.
Sometimes intentionally.
Boys, boys.
I think you're both missing
the obvious solution.
Hello. Hello.
Does this seem loud?
Oh, Gossiping Housewives is on.
Eh, I already sat down.
Zombies and gentlemen,
I'm Mable,
they're Dipper and Stan
and together,
we are Love Patrol Alpha!
I never agreed to that name.
Hit it!
Uh, Mabel, our lives
may not be worth this.
♪ Friday night ♪
♪ We're gonna
party till dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry, Daddy ♪
♪ I've got
my favorite dress on ♪
Mabel, this is stupid.
♪ We roll into the party ♪
♪ The boys are
looking our way ♪
♪ We just keep dancing ♪
♪ We don't care
what they say ♪
♪ And all the boys
are ganging up in my face ♪
Guys, we have to sing together
or it won't work.
♪ Boys are a bore ♪
♪ Let's show 'em the door ♪
♪ We're taking over
the dance floor ♪
♪ Oo-oo ♪
♪ Girls do what we like ♪
♪ We're taking over
tonight, oo-oo ♪
♪ Girls do what we like,
oo-oo ♪
♪ We're taking over tonight ♪
♪ We're queens
of the disco! ♪
♪ Oo-oo ♪
♪ Girls do what we like ♪
♪ We're taking over tonight ♪
♪ Taking over tonight ♪
Duck!
Thank you!
We'll be here all night!
Deal with it, zombie idiots!
Pines! Pines!
I'm sorry about this, guys.
I totally ruined everything.
Dipper, are you kidding me?
I got to sing karaoke with my two
favorite people in the world.
No party could ever top that.
Kids, listen,
this town is crazy.
So you need to be careful.
I don't know what I'd do with
myself if you got hurt on my watch.
I'll let you hold
onto that spooky journal
as long as you promise me
you'll only use it
for self-defense
and not go looking for trouble.
Okay, as long as
you promise me
that you don't have any other
bombshell secrets about this town.
Promise.
Man, we have got a lot of
zombie damage to clean up.
Where's my handyman anyway?
Brains! Brains!
Holy Moses!
Wait!
There's a page in here about
curing zombification.
It's gonna
take a lot of formaldehyde.
Ooh, and cinnamon.
Come on, Soos,
let's fix you up.
Brains! Brains!
Soos, cut it out!
Sorry, dude.
I can't believe it.
All this time the author's secrets
were hiding in plain sight.
A whole new chapter
of mysteries to explore.
That was insane.
I've never seen
anything like it.
Who do we report to?
This is bigger than
we imagined.
We need to bring in
the big guns.
But they'll never believe us.
Then we'll make them
believe us.
This is the town
we've been searching for.
Ba-- Ba-- Bam.
Another zombie!
- Drop your weapon!
Oh, okay,
it's just--
- Who is that guy?
- A very ugly man.