It was May of 2006 in New York City
and life was good.
But everything was about to change.
So... what do you think?
Robin again?
Ted, the universe clearly does not want you and Robin to be together.
Don't piss off the universe. The universe will slap you.
But don't you think the universe has more important things to worry about than my dating life?
Unless your dating life is the glue holding the entire universe together... Whoa. Chills.
Anybody else get chills?
Look, I realize we've been down this road before,
but the fact is, whatever I do,
it all keeps coming back to Robin, so...
I gotta do this.
Ow! What the hell?
That wasn't me. That was the universe.
The funny thing was, at that very moment, the universe was working on something--
a storm.
And so tropical storm Willy is going to be with us at least until Monday.
It's gonna rain cats and dogs, folks.
So don't step in a poodle.
Sandy? Robin?
Thanks, Lou.
Boy, too bad. Our big Metro News One camping trip was going to be this weekend.
Yeah, but camping out in the rain? No fun. Muddy. Yuck.
Guess we'll have to take a rain check.
And we'll check in with you tomorrow, New York.
Have a great night.
And, we're clear.
Bummer. I was hoping to finally have sex with you this weekend, Scherbotsky.
Well, I'd give you the "I don't date coworkers" speech again,
but, God, you must have that sum'bitch memorized by now.
Shame, though. It was a pretty hot show tonight.
The rhythmic give and take of our improvised banter there at the end
really got my freak juice flowing.
Dude, he's right. How many times do you have to watch this crash
and burn before you say, "enough"?
One more. One more time.
One more big, beautiful, stupid romantic gesture.
And then, whatever she says, yes or no, that's it.
If it's yes, great.
If it's no, then I am done going after Robin forever.
So what's this big, beautiful romantic gesture?
I am going to make her...
a mix CD.
No, I'm kidding. I got a plan.
Lily, I'm going to need the spare key to Robin's apartment.
I see where this is going.
Ted, waiting naked in a girl's bed wearing whipped cream undies does not work...
usually.
The setting-- Martha's Vineyard, 1999.
The characters: Yours truly and a raven-haired au pair by the name...
Universe.
So, this plan you speak of?
Remember the first night Robin and I went out?
I stole a blue French horn for her and it almost worked.
Yeah. Dude, that was awesome,
but how are you ever going to top that?
She should be here any second.
Uh, we're pretty hungry. When do we get our pizza?
Enough with the-- we'll go get pizza later, all right?
Just...
Damn it.
Hello.
Hey, Lily, I'm locked out of my apartment. I need to come pick up my extra key.
Extra key?
Do I have an extra key to your apartment?
Yes, I gave it to you.
Oh, right. That key.
Yeah, I lost it.
Great, now I gotta go to the locksmith.
No, wait, uh...
Maybe you should just knock.
Knock?
Lily, my dogs aren't that well trained.
Hello, Lily, this is Janet Kagan at the Russell House Art Foundation here in San Francisco.
I'm pleased to inform you that we've accepted your application for our summer fellowship.
We look forward to hearing from you. Bye-bye.
Uh, Robin, I-I gotta go. Just knock, okay?
Summer fellowship?
Just knock.
Okay.
Hi.
Robin...
I've sort of said this already.
I mean I've half said it. I've tried to say it, and I've said it badly.
So this is me, just saying it.
With strings.
I'm crazy about you. I think we should be together.
What do you say?
- What do you say?
- Yes.
No.
I don't know.
Those are the three options.
- Ted, this is so...
- I know.
I mean, I come home, I was going to watch Jeopardy and there's a string quartet and...
I have to pee.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Uh, well, go ahead. We'll, uh, we'll wait.
Yeah, 'cause when we talked earlier, you said there'd be pizza.
No, I said I'd get you a pizza afterwards.
Look, could we talk about this later? I'm sort of professing my love here.
Sure.
We're not getting any pizza.
Okay. Let's talk.
Okay.
Oh, hey, you guys want to take five?
Thanks, guys. Just need a minute.
Sort of a big life decision. Love the blue instruments, though.
Kind of an inside joke.
Thanks.
- You're crazy.
- Right. Come on.
It's not that I haven't thought about this.
You know that I have, but let's look at this, okay?
We only just started being friends again.
I know. But-- come on.
And we want different things.
That's still there. That's not going away.
I mean, what if we do this and it doesn't work out
and I'd lose you as a friend?
I gotta think about this.
Okay, fine. Think about it on the plane.
Let's go to Paris for the weekend. I'm serious.
I'm kidding. I'm serious.
I can't go to Paris, I'm going camping.
I thought that thing was canceled.
Well, it's back on.
Since when?
Since like an hour ago.
..sending the storm back out into the Atlantic.
So it's blue skies this weekend.
Sandy? Robin?
Thanks, Lou, but that blue sky isn't without at least one cloud.
I'm sorry to announce that one week from today I will be leaving Metro News One.
It has been an honor to bring you the news each night,
and read the paper to you each morning.
I will always treasure it.
Good night, New York.
And we're clear.
You're leaving?
There. I quit my job.
We're not coworkers. Will you please have dinner with me?
I'm joking. I got offered a job at CNN.
Oh, congratulations.
Congratulations yourself.
What do you mean?
Well, Joel asked me who I thought should replace me as lead anchor.
I told him you.
They're announcing it next week. Act surprised.
Wow.
Thanks.
And, yes.
Yes, what?
Yes, let's go get dinner.
How about this weekend on the camping trip?
I roast a mean weenie.
Oh, you're kidding me.
No way. Don't go on this thing.
Ted, I have to go. It's a company camping trip.
Really? Because it also kinda sounds like a date.
With Sandy... and his weenie.
I mean is this not a date?
I don't-I don't know.
So, what? You actually like this guy now?
I don't know.
Are you gonna hook up with him?
- Yes, you do.
- No, Ted, I don't.
And you know what? That's okay.
I don't plan out every second of my life like you do.
- I don't plan out every...
- Oh, really? What is all of this?
I mean, why can't you just say, "Hey, Robin, let's go get some sushi?"
No, it has to be a-a string quartet and-and Paris and flowers and chocolates
and let's spend the rest of our lives together.
Don't you think we're a little bit past sushi at this point?
God, you are so terrified of anything real.
It's like you're floating out in space.
Touch the ground, Robin.
Live in the world, make a mistake. Make this mistake.
I need to think about this.
Fine.
No, I'm sorry, I...
I can't do this anymore.
I need an answer.
If you want me to say yes right now, I-I can't do that.
Well, if it's not yes, then it's a no.
Then I guess it's not meant to be.
Nice try, buddy.
Good hustle out there.
Look at the bright side. At least you got some closure.
She's made her choice and you can finally move on.
Screw that. This ain't over.
Ted, you sat here in this very booth and you said...
I don't care what I said.
This is gonna happen. She can't say it's not meant to be.
It is meant to be, and you know why?
'Cause I mean it to be.
- Unpause?
- Unpause.
Let's pause.
See, Marshall and Lily had a rule that at any point during a fight
they could pause and take a break.
Their fights often lasted for days.
- A painting fellowship?
- I was never going to take it.
- In California?
Ted, she is going on that camping trip.
Dude, barring some act of God, Robin's gonna be with Sandy this weekend.
Fine.
If an act of God is what it takes,
then an act of God it is.
What are you talking about?
I'm gonna make it rain.
I can't let Robin go camping with this guy.
So how do I keep that from happening?
Simple-- I make it rain!
Ted, do you want me to slap you again?
'Cause I kind of enjoyed it the first time.
Look, I-I might be crazy right now... No, you know what?
I am definitely crazy right now, but I have a plan.
That girl you used to go out with, Penelope,
wasn't she getting her PhD in Native American culture?
Yeah.
Are you still in touch with her?
Sure. I mean, even though we stopped having sex,
we still get together, like, once a month to chat and catch up,
and of course I'm not in touch with her!
Well, you're gonna need to get in touch with her.
She's gonna teach me how to do a rain dance.
- Did you just say a "rain dance"?
- Yes.
- A rain dance.
- A dance to make it rain.
- Yes.
- We're finding Penelope!
- No, we are not!
Yes, we are!
Ted, you're forcing me to be the voice of reason, and it's not a good look for me!
Why the hell should I help you?
Come on, I know it didn't work out between us, but we did... have a relationship.
We had sex twice in your car, and then you dumped me.
How is that a relationship?
Twice!
- Barney, there is no way...
- Shh!
Seriously, come on.
Penelope, I really need to make it rain this weekend.
Why?
There's this girl...
"There's this girl."
You know, the traditional rain dance is a sacred prayer to nature.
I don't think the Great Spirit looks too kindly on white dudes who co-opt it to get laid.
Penelope, this is the girl I love.
If it doesn't rain this weekend, she's gonna end up with the wrong guy.
Please.
This wrong guy, is he a huge jackass?
Absolutely.
- Kind of like Barney?
- Kind of.
- Hey.
- You hit on my mom!
We weren't exclusive!
I'm in.
And so the three of us headed up to the roof of my building.
Okay.
Crouch down and bend over a little bit.
Wow, it took five shots of tequila to get you in that position.
I will throw you off this roof.
There's so much of your mom in you.
And she's been throwing up ever since.
So how'd she manage to eat so much chocolate?
Remember that guy, Ted, that I was telling you about?
Well, I came home and I found him waiting in my apartment
with a string quartet and roses and chocolates...
Oh, that's so sweet.
Okay, yes, it's sweet in theory, but isn't it also kind of crazy?
I mean, a string quartet in my living room-- who does that?
Nobody does that.
Exactly.
No, honey-- nobody does that.
But I guess I'm just a hopeless romantic.
I'm gonna put my hand up your dog now.
So you're saying you would forbid me from going?
Forbid? Who said forbid?
I was just reminding you that there's this wedding coming up in a couple of months,
and I was kind of hoping you'd save the day.
Look for me-- I'll be the guy in the awesome suit.
Come on, Lily. It's what you've always wanted.
Yeah, but there's a lot of things I've always wanted, and I haven't done any of them.
I'm sorry. I just need to do this before settling down forever.
So now we've gone from "I was never gonna do it" to "I need to do this"?
Did I leave the room at some point? When did that happen?
Oh, maybe when you said you wouldn't let me do it.
I never said that!
You know, if you're having these kind of doubts now,
what's gonna change in three months?
Maybe we just shouldn't get married at all.
Maybe not.
- Pause.
- So, are you just, like, starving?
- Totally.
Red Lobster?
Oh, lobster, lobster, lobster, you are delicious!
Oh, God, I love butter sauce! There's nothing bad about it.
Say something bad about butter sauce, I dare you.
I wouldn't dare.
Marshall, no. We're on pause.
There's no crying in Pauseland!
Pauseland is a magical place, with--
with popcorn shrimp mountains and butter sauce rivers!
Damn it!
Happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy birthday,
happy, happy, happy, happy, appy, happy birthday,
happy, happy...
Ted, this is funny.
Still funny.
Still fu... And now it's sad.
Hey, Penelope, you sure I'm doing this right?
I think so.
Does it, uh, look anything like a real rain dance?
Hey, Penelope, have you, uh, have you ever actually seen a rain dance performed?
No.
No?
I've read extensively on the subject:
firsthand accounts, theoretical criticism, the anthropological...
Have you ever seen a rain dance?
I've seen a film strip.
Terrific. Uh, look, I should run.
I'm getting brain surgery from some guy who's seen a couple episodes of E.R.
I can't believe this.
We've been up here for the past hour making complete asses of ourselves.
What do you mean "we," white man?
How did we get here?
Couple of days ago, the biggest problem in my life was,
did Ted eat the last pudding snack pack in the fridge.
I think there's still one left.
Dibs.
- Unpause?
- Unpause.
Look... I know this sucks.
It's just something I'm going through.
I'm not asking you to understand it.
I'm not asking you to be happy about it.
I'm just asking you to support it.
I want to, Lily, okay?
I really do.
But I just can't.
Why not?
Because you're scaring the hell out of me, that's why not.
What if you decide to go be a painter
and then you realize I don't fit in to your life anymore,
and three months becomes forever?
Can you promise me that that's not gonna happen?
Marshall...
'Cause if you can't promise me that, we shoul just break up right now.
I'm not gonna wait around for three months just to have my heart ripped out.
Marshall, I love you.
Can you promise me that that's not gonna happen?
- Pause.
- No, Lily, we cannot pause this anymore.
Can you promise me that that's not gonna happen?!
- Pause!
- Why do you want me to pause?!
That's just a great use of the pause function, baby.
Thank you.
Hey, Ted.
Whatcha doing?
A rain dance.
Dude, that's not a rain dance, that's a fat kid with a bee in his pants.
Look, I highly doubt the Great Spirit is a stickler for choreography.
It's the thought that counts.
She's leaving in half an hour.
These are your awesome years. You're wasting them on this girl.
This isn't gonna work!
Yeah. I know that.
- Well, then why are you doing this?
- Because I love her.
I love her!
I told her that the first night we went out,
and here it is, eight months later, and nothing's changed.
So yes, I know this isn't gonna work.
But it has to work!
You hear me, universe?
This is Ted Mosby talking!
Give me some rain!
Come on!
Come on...!
Oh, come on!
Pushing the front back into the Tri-State area
and giving Manhattan one of its worst storms in over a decade.
How about that? He did it.
Robin! Hey, Robin!
Oh, thank God you're here!
My camping trip got rained out.
I know. I'm sorry.
- It's not your fault.
- Yeah, it is.
Come down here.
It's pouring. You come up.
No, you have to come down here.
- Why?
Because I made it rain, that's what I did today!
And that's enough. I-I've done my part. Now, get down here!
I'm not dressed, Ted. No. Come up.
I'm not coming up there, Robin, I'm not.
You have to come down here!
- I was gonna...
- I know.
And that's how Robin and I ended up together.
Turns out, all I had to do was make it rain.
As I rode home the next morning, the city looked the same,
the people looked the same. It all looked the same.
But it wasn't.
In just one night, everything had changed.
Transcript: Raceman
Subtitles: Willow's team
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net
When you're single, and your friends start to get married,
every wedding invitation presents a strange moment of self-evaluation:
"Will you be bringing a guest, or will you be attending alone?"
What it's really asking is,
"Where do you see yourself in three months?
Sitting next to your girlfriend, or hitting on a bridesmaid?"
I always checked that I was bringing a guest.
I was an optimist.
Who the hell am I gonna bring to this wedding?
Ted, have you ignored all my teachings?
For the most part, yeah.
No, you don't bring a date to a wedding.
That's like bringing a deer carcass on a hunting trip.
Oh, Ted. Oh, Ted. No-- no date.
Deer carcass? Really? That's the metaphor you're going with here?
Ted, it's a simile.
Well, it's too late now. If I don't bring a date,
a $200 piece of chicken/salmon will go uneaten.
I got to bring someone, but who?
Of course, I knew who I wanted to bring.
Robin-- the big unanswered question in my life.
Problem was, she was dating this really rich guy named Derek.
Derek.
Well, Derek and I just broke up.
Oh, no, that's terrible! Are you okay?
Yeah, do you need a drink or something?
Nah... We never really clicked.
I felt bad, though. He was pretty bummed.
Ah, don't beat yourself up.
He'll be fine. I mean, the guy's, like, a billionaire.
He can put his platinum card on a fishing line and reel in ten chicks hotter than you.
Thanks. I feel a lot better.
I think I'll get that drink now.
Okay, guys, I got to say something.
I think my feelings for Robin may be resurfacing.
Oh, please-- they were buried in a shallow grave.
Not again. Come on. Dude?
We all know how this movie ends.
Ted falls in love, love kicks Ted in the sprouts, roll credits.
No, you guys just have to look at the whole picture.
Fact:
Robin was into me when we first met.
Even though she didn't want a relationship, we had an amazing kiss on the roof.
Fact:
On New Year's Eve, we kissed again.
I need a date to this wedding.
Wish me luck.
What I don't get is why is Claudia marrying Stuart?
She's way hotter than him.
How way?
Way way.
This wedding does sound pretty amazing, though.
Fancy hotel ballroom,
everybody all dressed up...
Oh, here we go.
What?
We can't get anywhere with our wedding plans
because I want it to be fun and Marshall wants it to be lame.
Oh, yeah. Okay, that's a pretty fair assessment of our two arguments.
I thought so.
You know what? Excuse me if I don't want to get married
barefoot in the woods next to Lake No-One's-Going-To-Drive-That-Far.
Yes. I want a ballroom,
and I want a band, and I want shoes.
I've been dreaming about this day since I was, like...
A little girl?
What up!
Okay. I'm just saying that it's my wedding, too, and I should have a say in it.
Yes, but I'm the bride, so I win.
Well, I thought marriage was about two equal partners sharing a life together.
Right, but I'm the bride, so I win.
I mean, seriously-- Claudia and Stuart?
I mean, I've hooked up with the odd lass who was beneath my level of attractiveness,
but, you know, I was drunk.
There's no way Claudia has been drunk for three years.
You know, I've always found that the best way to get over a failed relationship
is to celebrate someone else's successful one.
Oh, it makes sense.
So, with that in mind, uh, our friends Claudia and Stuart
are having this crazy black-tie wedding on Saturday.
You want to be my plus one?
Ooh... "Plus one." You make it sound so romantic.
Fine.
You want to be my date?
Your date?
I'd love to.
How fancy are we talking about here?
Oh, you're going to want to bring your "A" game.
Oh, I'll bring it.
I'll bring it so hard, the bride's going to look like a big white bag of crap.
Lily? I need a dress.
You're going? That's awesome!
Oh, my God-- four days to find a dress?
I know, it's a suicide mission.
Well, if we leave now... we can still have a fighting chance. Let's do it!
Bye, babe.
Whoa! Did you see how fired up she was?
I don't know, there's something there.
And, come Saturday, a little music, a little dancing, a lot of champagne...
Who  knows?
Wow. Ted, you're going to have to find another gender for yourself,
'cause I'm revoking your "dude" membership.
Yeah... how was that manicure yesterday?
Invigorating, thanks.
Okay, I wasn't going to say it in front of the guys,
but  back then I really thought that's how it worked.
You put yourself and a girl you like in some romantic setting...
the stars line up...
and shazam.
I know now that life is never that simple.
Hey, Claudia!
Yes, I want Tahitian Vanilla! You wrote it down wrong?
No, no, no, no, listen to me--
if I go to my wedding and the cake is not Tahitian Vanilla,
I will come down there and burn your little shop to the ground!
Do you want to find out if I'm kidding?
Yeah, good-bye.
Hey!
How's it going?
My wedding is in two days, that's how it's going.
Oh, don't worry, it's going to be great. I'm so excited.
Well, you should be-- lots of single girls.
Oh, well, yeah, I'm... bringing a date, so I'll be off the market.
What?
I'm bringing a date.
You're not bringing a date.
Uh... yes, I am.
Uh, no, you're not.
I checked "plus one."
No, you didn't.
Claudia, I'm pretty sure I checked...
Ted, you did not check "plus one"!
You are not bringing a date to my wedding!
Wait, I've already invited someone.
You are not bringing a guest, Ted!
The guest list has been closed for months-- months!
But I checked "plus one"! I always check "plus one"!
You absolutely did not check "plus one"!
If you had checked "plus one," I would have called you to get the name of your guest,
so I could have the place cards printed up.
Did I call you to get the name of your guest?
Is there a place card with her name printed on it?
She doesn't need a place card. She knows her name.
What's she eating?! Huh?! You ordered the chicken. What did she order?
Do you see how your story is full of holes?
Come on, Claudia, we go way back.
Isn't there room for just one more person?
Don't make me hurt you, Ted.
I don't believe this! Claudia's crazy!
But, to be fair, she's also hot.
I totally checked "plus one." I'm sure I did.
- Yeah, right.
- I did!
Yeah, I don't think you did. You know why?
Because deep down, you didn't want to show up at this thing with a date.
See, for all your big talk about being ready for a relationship, deep down, you're single.
It's your default setting.
Ted, you know what's in the back of your brain?
Oh, great, here comes the little Barney speech.
Behind a curtain, in a dark little room secretly controlling your every move?
- A little Barney...
- A little Barney.
A little Barney.
And you know what he said?
"Ted... you will bring no dates to this wedding.
You... will hit on drunk bridesmaids with actual-size Barney."
Wow. Please stop.
I got to call Claudia. If I just explain to her...
Ted, no! Let it go.
She's about to get married, she's got enough to worry about.
Then what am I going to do?
The only thing you can do-- tell Robin she can't come.
Just a second!
- Hey!
- Hey. Listen...
Wait, two things. First of all... I have been laying groundwork all afternoon.
Totally subtle, totally cool, not pushing, not even nudging, just:
the theme of today is, "Ted rocks."
And she's picking up what I'm laying down.
- Lily, there's a problem...
- Wait, no.
Thing number two: the dress.
We got a dress.
Go.
Well?
Did I bring it, or... did I bring it?
I think I brought it.
Wow.
That's what I was going for.
I'm so excited about tomorrow. We're going to have so much fun.
Yeah, about that...
I'll pick you up at 5:00.
So? The dress?
I don't have a plus one for the wedding.
What?
I ran into Claudia, and she told me I didn't check "plus one" on the reply card.
- Why didn't you check "plus..."?
- I did check "plus one."
- But Robin is so excited.
- I know.
-  And the dress!
Okay, okay. Well, we'll sneak her in.
We can't sneak her in, we're not Ninjas.
- Oh, I wish we were Ninjas.
- I know.
You could always ask Stuart.
Can I do that?
Well,  sure.
You guys have been friends for a long time.
And it's 40% his wedding, too.
I don't know... it's going to be a tough sell.
Dude, no problem whatsoever.
Really?
Sure, the more, the merrier.
Wow! Wow, thanks for being so cool about this,
'cause you know, Claudia said...
Yeah, yeah, yeah. This morning at the rehearsal,
Claudia called our seven-year-old flower girl a whore.
So, don't take it personally, she's just a little stressed.
Yeah, she's not usually like that.
No.
Well, thanks, Stu!
It's going to be a great wedding.
Honey, this magazine says more and more couples are opting
to have non-traditional weddings out in the woods.
Well, if a magazine says so, we should go get married in the woods,
like a couple of squirrels.
Squirrels don't get married, Marshall.
Like you could possibly know that.
I did it. I did it-- I'm taking her to the wedding.
Nice!
What? How?
I talked to Stuart.
You went around the bride.
"Oh, this hornets' nest looks harmless.
Maybe I'll poke it with a stick.
Oh, look, some Gremlins. Let me go feed them after midnight!"
Did you know about this?
It may have been my idea.
What?
Stuart doesn't get a say?
Ah! So you admit it-- the groom should have an equal say.
Well, yeah, sure, on the stupid stuff, like who comes.
So I can invite whoever I want?
Sure, there's plenty of room in the woods.
It's Claudia.
So it begins.
Come on, it can't be that bad.
Here, Lily, you answer it.
What? Why?
Because this whole thing was your idea.
And... Claudia scares me.
But... but you're the... But I just want to...
Ted's phone.
Oh, hi, Claudia.
What?
Now I wasn't there, but from what I heard, it went something like this...
Oh, by the way, honey, Ted stopped by and I told him
he could bring his date to the wedding.
You what?
...always undermining me at every turn...
...try to show a little flexibility, but no!
It's all about you!
...and your mother...
You know what?
The wedding's off!
They broke up!
O w!
It's not because of me, is it?
And my dad already paid for this huge wedding!
Oh, he's going to kill me!
And then he's gonna kill Ted!
Then I'm gonna kill Ted.
It's Robin.
Answer it!
Uh, Lily's phone.
Ted, where's Lily? I need to tell her about these awesome shoes I just bought.
Uh, Lily's busy.
Oh, okay, well, I just wanted to say they're gorgeous and Ted's going to love them.
That's great, I'll tell Lily to tell me.
Uh, listen, I really want to keep talking, um, but now's not a good time,
so I'm really excited about tomorrow, okay, bye.
Okay, bye.
Crap, she bought some expensive shoes. She's really looking forward to this.
- Do you think she's into me?
- Ted, focus!
Okay, okay, sweetie, just calm down.
Do you want to go somewhere and talk?
I want to go somewhere and drink!
Okay, meet me at MacLaren's. I'll see you there.
Oh, I feel terrible.
Well, feel terrible later. Right now, we gotta fix this.
Lily, you go down to the bar and comfort Claudia.
Ted and I will go and try to talk some sense into Stuart.
Um, tell Claudia I'm sorry.
Did she seem pissed at me?
She said if there's no wedding tomorrow, you owe her father $400,000.
What say we get these crazy kids back together?
Hi, sad eyes.
What's got you down?
Stuart and I just broke up.
Oh, God, I'm so sorry. That's just, that's...
Two vodka cranberries, please.
You remembered I drink vodka cranberries.
Remember?
When it comes to you, how can I forget?
They all drink vodka cranberries.
So... is there anything else you need... sweetie?
You got $400,000?
No.
But I do have a hug.
Thank you.
Stuart, I-I don't know what to say. If I caused this in any way...
Ted, for all I know, you did me the biggest favor anyone's ever done me.
Oh, come on, man, you don't mean that.
No, I do-- this whole thing has made me realize I miss being single.
I miss staying out late, and making messes and not cleaning them up.
I miss owning porn.
Dude, who doesn't?
And you know, I'll see some super-hot model chick, and I'll think,
"Why am I with Claudia? I could be with her."
That's just crazy!
I mean... you're the luckiest... You and Claudia both...
The point is I want to get married. I want to settle down,
but right now, that's just not who I am.
I'm not a commitment guy; I'm a single guy.
Stuart, you don't have to be one or the other.
Everybody feels this way sometimes.
Relationships aren't easy; they're hard work.
It's about compromise, growing together, all that Dr. Phil crap.
How would you know? You're not even married.
Okay, ask this guy. Nine years he's been with Lily.
He's the pro-- this guy knows relationships.
Tell him, Marshall.
Stuart, don't get married.
- Dude...
- What?
Look, I'm sorry.
Being in a couple is hard. And committing, making sacrifices, it's hard.
But if it's the right person, then it's easy.
Looking at that girl and knowing she's all you really want out of life,
that should be the easiest thing in the world, and if it's not like that,
then she's not the one. I'm sorry.
You  know I don't have $400,000, right?
Maybe we got together too young.
Maybe that's what the problem was.
I mean, I'm 28 years old,
and I've really only ever been with one man.
That's just, that's...
Two more vodka cranberries, please!
Claudia... it's all gonna be okay.
Oh, thanks for listening, Barney.
It really means a lot to me.
Isn't it weird that we should... run into each other like this?
Two souls, of equal levels of attractiveness,
both fitting together like two pieces of a very attractive puzzle.
- Oh, hell, no!
- Ow! Ow! Ow!
Claudia is getting married tomorrow,
and so help me God, if I catch you even so much as breathing the same air as her,
I will take those peanuts you're trying to pass off as testicles,
and I will squeeze them so hard your eyes pop out,
and then I'll feed them to you like grapes!
Wait, my eyes or my testicles?
One of each.
All right! All right!
Claudia?
Stuart.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, too.
I love you.
I love you too, babe.
Marshall and Ted set me straight.
And when Marshall told me not to marry you, it made me realize I...
Marshall said what?!
It's more complicated than that!
He made me realize how much I love you.
These guys got us back together.
Okay, I'm cool, I'm cool.
So where did we land on the whole plus one thing?
No, no, no, no!
It took three more vodka cranberries to subdue Claudia,
but, eventually, she graciously agreed to let me bring Robin.
Still wow.
Wow yourself. Look who else brought it.
Oh, yeah. I thought about leaving it at home,
but I figured I don't want to get there and realize I need it
and have to go all the way back to get it. So, yeah, I brought it.
Oh, sorry.
Hello?
Oh, my God. Tonight?
You're kidding.
They want me to anchor the news tonight.
Really?
Like anchor anchor?
What happened to Sandy?
Okay.
Okay. Sure. What time do you need me to...
Right now?! Oh.
Do it.
Okay, I need like five minutes to change, and, um, I'll call you from the cab...
So admit it.
This wedding is both indoors and amazing.
I'll give you the crab puffs. The crab puffs are good.
The crab puffs were incredible.
We should totally have them at our wedding.
Definitely...
Hey. We just agreed on something.
Did we just start planning our wedding?
I think that we did.
We totally have to get that brown dipping sauce.
Ooh, I thought the red sauce was, like, awesome.
My God, were you born without taste buds?
What?
I love you.
Coming up, are there snakes living in your walls?
The answer may surprise you... after the break.
Man, you know something? Stuart's my new hero.
If that dude can bag a nine,
I got to be able to bag, like, a 16.
What's a 16?
Those two eights right over there.
Yeah.
Hi, Ted.
Claudia.
We just wanted to get a picture with the woman who almost ended our relationship.
Yeah, where is she?
Um... she couldn't make it.
What's so funny?
Oh, plan a wedding. You'll see.
Look at that.
That's how it's supposed to be. That right there.
Easy, simple.
It's just not like that with Robin.
It's not easy, and on some level, it has to just be easy.
Speaking of easy... bridesmaids, Ted. Bridesmaids.
By the way, I almost forgot.
We found this.
I didn't check "plus one."
You were right.
Of course, I was right.
I'm single.
Maybe that's just who I am.
And you know what? I like being single.
Being single's the best.
Yeah, stay out as late as you want.
Answer to no one.
The whole world full of endless possibilities.
Never having to go to a farmer's market.
Okay. Ah... doing some math here.
Table six has got three bridesmaids: an eight, an eight, and a seven.
I am willing to give you one of the eights, lowering myself to a 15,
which means you owe me...
So there we were, two single guys, doing our usual single-guy thing.
For whatever reason, I had let myself believe that this night would be a turning point,
that this was the night my life-- my real life-- would finally begin.
The funny thing is...
I wasn't totally wrong.
Because that night was just beginning.
Transcripts : Raceman
Subtitles: Willow's Team
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net
Kids, I'm gonna tell you an incredible story ;
the story of how I met your mother.
Are we being punished for something ?
No.
Yeah, is this gonna take a while ?
Yes. 25 years ago, before I was Dad,
I had this whole other life.
It was way back in 2005.
I was 27, just starting to make it as an architect
and living in New York  with Marshall,  my best friend from college.
My life was good.
And then Uncle Marshall went and screwed the whole thing up.
Will you marry me ?
Yes. Perfect !
And then you're engaged.
You pop the champagne.
You drink a toast.
You have sex on the kitchen floor.
Don't have sex on our kitchen floor.
Got it.
Thanks for helping me plan this out, Ted.
Dude, are you kidding ?
It's you and Lilly.
I've been there for all the big moments of you and Lilly :
night you met, your first date, other first things.
Yeah, sorry.
We thought you were asleep.
It's physics, Marshall.
If the bottom bunk moves, the top bunk moves, too.
My God.
You're getting engaged tonight.
Yeah. What are you doin' tonight ?
What was I doing ?
Here Uncle Marshall was taking the biggest step of his life.
And me ?
I'm calling up your Uncle Barney.
Hey, so you know how I've always had a thing for half-Asian girls ?
Well, now I've got a new favorite... Lebanese girls.
Lebanese girls are the new half-Asians.
Hey, you want to do somethin' tonight ?
Okay, meet me at the bar in 15 minutes. And suit up !
Where's your suit ?
Just once, when I say suit up, I wish you'd put on a suit.
I did that one time.
It was a blazer !
You know, ever since college it's been, Marshall and Lilly and me.
Now, it's gonna be Marshall and Lilly... and me.
They'll get married, start a family.
Before long, I'm that weird, middle-aged bachelor their kids call Uncle Ted.
I see what this is about.
Have you forgotten what I said to you the night we met ?
Ted, I'm gonna teach you how to live.
Barney. We met at the urinal.
Oh, right. Right.
Lesson one : lose the goatee.
It doesn't go with your suit.
- I'm not wearing a suit.
- Lesson two : get a suit.
Suits are cool.
Exhibit "A."
Lesson three : don't even think about getting married till you're 30.
30. Right. You're right.
I guess it's just, your best friend gets engaged,
you start thinking about that stuff.
I thought I was your best friend.
Ted, say I'm your best friend.
You're my best friend, Barney.
Good. Then, as your best friend,
I suggest we play a little game I like to call
- "Have you met Ted ?"
- Wait. No, no, no.
We're not playing "Have you met Ted ?"
Hi, have you met Ted ?
Hi, I'm Ted.
Yasmine.
That's a very pretty name.
Thanks. It's Lebanese.
I'm exhausted.
It was finger-painting day at school,
and a five year-old boy got to second base with me.
Wow ! You're cooking ?
Yes, I am.
Aw...
Are you sure that's a good idea ?
After last time, you looked really creepy without eyebrows.
I can handle this.
I think you'll find I'm full of surprises tonight.
So, there's more surprises ?
Like what ?
Marshall was in his second year of law school,
so he was pretty good  at thinking on his feet.
Boogedyboo !
And that's all of 'em.
I'm gonna go... cook.
I'm so happy for Marshall, I really am.
I just couldn't imagine settling down right now.
So, do you think you'll ever get married ?
Well, maybe eventually...
some fall day, possibly in Central Park.
Simple ceremony.
We'll write our own vows.
Band, no DJ.
People will dance !
I'm not gonna worry about it !
Damn it, why did Marshall have to get engaged ?
Yeah, nothing hotter than a guy planning out his own imaginary wedding, huh ?
- Actually, I think it's cute.
- Well, you're clearly drunk.
One more for the lady !
Oh, hey, look what I got.
Oh, honey ! Champagne.
Yeah.
No. You are too old to be scared to open a bottle of champagne.
- I'm not scared.
- Then open it.
Fine.
Please open it ?
You are unbelievable, Marshall.
There are two big questions a man has to ask in life.
One, you plan out for months.
The other just slips out when you're half drunk at some bar.
Will you marry me ?
You wanna go out sometime ?
Of course, you idiot !
I'm sorry, Carl's my boyfriend.
'Sup, Carl ?
I promised Ted we wouldn't do that.
Did you know there's a Pop Tart under your fridge ?
No, but dibs.
Where's that champagne ?
I wanna drink a toast with my fiance.
I don't know why I was so scared of this.
It's pretty easy, right ?
Why am I freaking out all of a sudden ?
This is crazy.
I'm not ready to settle down.
How does Carl land a Lebanese girl ?
The plan has always been don't even think about it until you're 30.
Exactly. The guy doesn't even own a suit.
Plus, Marshall's found the love of his life.
Even if I was ready, which I'm not...
but if I was, it's, like, "Okay, I'm ready. Where is she ?"
And there she was.
It was like something from an old movie,
where the sailor sees the girl across the crowded dance floor,
turns to his buddy and says, "See that girl ?
I'm gonna marry her someday."
Hey, Barney, see that girl ?
Oh, yeah. You just know she likes it dirty.
Go say hi.
I can't just go say hi.
I need a plan.
I'm gonna wait until she goes to the bathroom,
then I'll strategically place myself by the jukebox...
Hi, have you met Ted ?
Let me guess... Ted.
Sorry, Lilly.
I'm so sorry.
- Take us to the hospital.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Did you hit her ?
Hit me ? Please !
This guy can barely even spank me in bed for fun.
He's all like, "Oh, honey. Did that hurt ?"
And, I'm like, "Come on !
Let me have it, you pansy !"
- Wow, a complete stranger.
- No, no, no, no ! It's okay.
Go on.
So, these, uh, spankings...
you in pajamas or au naturel ?
So, what do you do ?
I'm a reporter for Metro News One.
Well, kind of a reporter.
I do those dumb little fluff pieces at the end of the news.
You know, like, um...
monkey who can play the ukulele.
I'm hoping to get some bigger stories soon.
Bigger, like, uh... gorilla with an upright bass ?
Sorry. You're really pretty.
Oh, your friends don't seem to happy.
Yeah, see, the one in the middle just got dumped by her boyfriend.
So, tonight, every guy is "the enemy."
You know if it'll make your friend feel better,
you could throw a drink in my face. I don't mind.
She would love that !
And it does look fun in the movies.
Hey, you wanna have dinner with me Saturday night ?
Oh, I can't.
I'm going to Orlando for a week on Friday.
Some guy's attempting to make the world's biggest pancake.
Guess who's covering it ?
That's gonna take a week ?
Yeah, he's gonna eat it, too.
It's another record.
Hey ! What's takin' so long ?
Uh, I know this is a long shot, but how 'bout tomorrow night ?
Yeah. What the hell ?
Jerk !
That was fun.
De... wait for it... nied !
Denied !
We're goin' out tomorrow night.
I thought we were playin' laser tag tomorrow night.
Yeah, I was never gonna go play laser tag.
The next night, I took her out to this little bistro in Brooklyn.
That is one badass blue French horn.
Yeah.
Sort of looks like a Smurf penis.
Son, a piece of advice :
when you go on a first date, you really don't wanna say "Smurf penis."
Girls don't ordinarily like that.
But this was no ordinary girl.
Lilly ?
How long have you been sitting there ?
Stupid eye patch.
Mom, Dad, I have found the future Mrs. Ted Mosby.
Marshall, how have I always described my perfect woman ?
Now, let's see... she likes dogs ?
I've got five dogs.
She drinks scotch ?
I love a scotch that's old enough to order its own scotch.
Can quote obscure lines from Ghostbusters ?
Ray ! When someone asks you if you're a god, you say "Yes !"
And I'm saving the best for last.
Do you want these ?
I hate olives.
She hates olives ! Awesome !
The olive theory.
The olive theory is based on my friends Marshall and Lilly.
He hates olives, she loves them.
In a weird way, that's what makes them such a great couple.
Perfect balance.
You know, I've had a jar of olives just sitting in my fridge forever.
I could take 'em off your hands.
They're all yours.
Oh, it is on !
It is on till the break of dawn.
But wait.
It's only the break of 10:30.
What happened ?
I gotta get one of those blue French horns for over my fireplace.
It's gotta be blue.
It's gotta be French.
- No green clarinet ?
- Nope.
Come on. No purple tuba ?
It's a Smurf penis or no dice.
There you are !
We got a jumper.
Some crazy guy on the Manhattan Bridge.
Come on. You're coverin' it !
Um... all right.
I'll be right there.
I'm sorry.
I had a really great time tonight.
Yeah.
So ?! Did you kiss her ?
No. The moment wasn't right.
Look, this woman could actually be my future wife.
I want our first kiss to be amazing.
Aw, Ted, that is so sweet.
So you chickened out like a little bitch.
What ? I did not chicken out.
You know what ?
I don't need to take first kiss advice from some pirate
who hasn't been single since the first week of college.
Anyone who's single would tell you the same thing,
even the dumbest single person alive.
And if you don't believe me, call him.
Hey, loser.
How's not playing laser tag ?
Because playing laser tag is awesome !
- Oh, I killed you, Conner !
- Don't make me get your mom !
Hey, listen.
I need your opinion on something.
Okay, meet me at the bar in 15 minutes.
And suit up !
So, these guys think I chickened out.
What do you think ?
I can't believe you're still not wearing a suit.
She didn't even give me the signal.
What, is she gonna, she gonna bat her eyes ayou in Morse code ?
"Ted... kiss me."
No ! You just kiss her !
Not if you don't get the signal.
Did Marshall give me the signal ?
No ! I didn't. I swear.
But, see, at least tonight,
I get to sleep knowing Marshall and me,
never gonna happen.
You should have kissed her.
Oh, I should have kissed her.
Well, maybe in a week when she gets back from Orlando.
A week ? That's like a year in hot girl time.
She'll forget all about you.
Mark my words... you will never see that one again.
There she is.
Ooh ! She's cute.
Hey, Carl, turn it up.
...persuaded him to reconsider.
At which point, the man came down off the ledge,
giving this bizarre story a happy ending.
- Reporting from Metro One News...
- Guy didn't jump.
I'm gonna go kiss her.
Right now.
Look, dude.
It's midnight.
As your future lawyer, I'm gonna advise you that's freakin' crazy.
I never do anything crazy.
I'm always waiting for the moment, planning the moment.
Well, she's leaving tomorrow.
This may be the only moment I'm gonna get.
I gotta do what that guy couldn't.
I gotta take the leap !
Okay, not a perfect metaphor,
'cause for me it's fall in love and get married,
and for him it's... death.
Actually, that is a perfect metaphor.
By the way, did I congratulate you two ?
I'm doing this.
Let's go.
- Word up.
- We're coming with you.
Barney ?
All right, but under one condition.
Look at you, you beautiful bastard. You suited up !
This is totally going in my blog !
Stop the car.
Uh, pull over right here.
I gotta do something.
Excuse me. Pardon me. Just a sec'.
Enjoy your coffee.
Go ! Go ! Go !
Everybody brings flowers.
Okay.
Moment of truth.
Wish me luck.
Ted's gonna get it on with a TV reporter.
"This just in." Okay.
Kiss her, Ted !
Kiss her good !
Kiss the crap outta that girl !
Marshall, remember this night.
When you're the best man at our wedding and you give a speech,
you're gonna tell this story.
Why does he get to be the best man ?
I'm your best friend !
As I walked up to that door, a million thoughts raced through my mind.
Unfortunately, one particular  thought did not.
I've got five dogs.
Not good. Not good.
- No !
- Get back in there !
You're wearing a suit !
Ted ?
Hi.
I was just, uh...
Come on up.
He's in.
So...
Ranjit, you must have done it with a Lebanese girl ?
Okay, that's my Barney limit.
I'm gonna see if that bodega has a bathroom.
Actually, I'm from Bangladesh.
The women hot there ?
Here's a picture of my wife.
A simple "no" would have sufficed.
She's lovely.
So, Ted, what brings you back to Brooklyn at 1:00 in the morning in a suit ?
I was just hoping to...
get those olives...
that you said I could have.
Would you like those olives with some gin and vermouth ?
Are you trying to get me drunk ?
For starters.
So, Marshall, this olive theory, based on you and Lilly ?
You hate olives.
Lilly loves 'em.
You can't stand 'em.
Yeah. Hate olives.
Two weeks ago, Spanish bar on 79th street, dish of olives, you had some... what up ?
You have to swear that this does not leave this cab.
- I swear.
On our first date, I ordered a Greek salad.
Lilly asked if she could have my olives.
- I said, "Sure. I hate olives."
- But, you like olives.
Well, I was 18, okay ?
I was a virgin.
Been waitin' my whole life for a pretty girl to want my olives.
Marshall, I'm gonna give you an early wedding present.
Don't get married.
I think I like your olive theory.
I think I like your new French horn.
I think I like your nose.
I think I'm in love with you.
What ?! What ?! What ?!
Come on, man, you said your stomach's been hurting, right ?
You know what that is.
Hunger.
You're hungry for experience.
Hungry for something new.
Hungry for olives.
But you're too scared to do anything about it.
Yeah, I'm scared, okay ?
But, when I think of spending the rest of my life with Lilly...
committing, forever, no other women...
doesn't scare me at all.
I'm marrying that girl.
Lilly.
Lilly, I like olives.
We'll make it work.
So, Orlando.
You gonna hit Disneyworld ?
You love me ?!
I-I-I can't believe I said that.
Why did I say that ?
Who says that ?
I should just go.
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
Promised you these.
Olives.
Thanks. I love you.
What is wrong with me ?
Why are we still sitting here ?
Let's go. We can still make last call.
What do you say, Lil ?
Yo-ho-ho and a bottle of rum ?
'Cause you're a pirate.
Okay, eye patch, gone.
And we can't just abandon Ted.
If it doesn't go well up there, he's gonna need some support.
It's been, like, 20 minutes.
You think they're doin' it ?
You think they're doin' it in front of the dogs ?
Doggy style.
Hey, there was a girl in college, she had this golden retriever...
Okay, we can go to the bar.
Just stop talking.
Hit it, Ranjit.
So, when you tell this story to your friends,
could you avoid the word "psycho ?"
I'd prefer. "eccentric."
Good night... psycho.
Great.
Um, how do I get to the F train ?
Oh, um, two blocks that way and take a right.
You know what ?
I'm done being single.
I'm not good at it.
Look, obviously, you can't tell a woman you just met you love her.
But... it sucks that you can't.
I'll tell you something, though.
If a woman... not you, just some hypothetical woman...
were to bear with me through all this,
I think I'd make a damn good husband.
Because, that's the stuff I'd be good at,
stuff like making her laugh and being a good father.
And walking her five hypothetical dogs.
Being a good kisser.
Everyone thinks they're a good kisser.
Oh, I've got references.
Good night, Ted.
And I'm a good handshaker.
That's a pretty great handshake.
And that was it.
I'll probably never see her again.
What ?
That was the signal.
That long, lingering handshake ?
You should have kissed her.
There's no such thing as "the signal."
But, yeah, that was the signal.
Signal.
Ah, Carl, thank you.
Something I gotta do.
By the way, you should have kissed her.
Carl ! You guys weren't there.
I am so turned on right now.
Guys, trust me.
I've seen the signal.
That was not the signal.
Yeah, Ted, we're not on you anymore.
- To my fiance.
- To the future.
To one hell of a night !
That was not the signal.
I asked her about it years later.
And, yeah, that was the signal.
I could have kissed her.
But that's the funny thing about destiny.
It happens whether you plan it or not.
I mean, I never thought I'd see that girl again,
but it turns out I was just too close to the puzzle
to see the picture that was forming.
Because, that, kids, is the true story of how I met your Aunt Robin.
Aunt Robin ?
I thought this was how you met mom !
Will you relax ?
I'm getting to it.
Like I said, it's a long story.
Transcripts : Raceman
Subtitles : Willow's Team
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net