Previously on Mom:
- Are you okay?
- No. Something's wrong.
Call 911.
Don't you die, you son of a bitch.
We're not done with this.
Hey, uh,
my ex is having a heart attack,
or my prayers are being answered.
All depends how quick you get here.
Christy, come here.
- What's he saying?
- I'd rather not repeat it.
- So, he'll be okay?
- Yeah. I should think so.
You'll probably
be able to take him home tomorrow.
Oh, thank God. That's great news.
For you.
He's gonna need to take it easy
for a couple of weeks.
Is there somebody
available to provide care?
What are you looking at me for?
I've got a full-time job,
and I'm gonna have to deal with Violet.
No. I am not doing it.
No, no, no.
No.
Oh, my God. She still loves him.
You have no idea how funny this is.
- What?
- Just thinking about God.
- What about him?
- He is just such a scamp.
He puts Alvin back into our lives.
That's good.
Gives him a heart attack.
That's bad.
But makes you realize
you still love him.
- What?
- And that's good.
I don't love him.
I despise him.
Uh-huh.
Keep telling yourself that.
I have no feelings for your father.
- God begs to differ.
- Leave God out of this.
- Woe unto thee who denieth his will.
- Stop that!
Thy kingdom come, et cetera.
Your father abandoned
me after you were born.
- How could I ever love that bastard?
- Don't ask me.
Ask the scamp.
Seems to me the moment Alvin's
heart stopped beating...
yours started.
That's it.
Get out.
You're walking home.
- The house is right there.
- Okay. Stay in.
I'm gonna drive you further away.
1x22 - Smokey Taylor
and a Deathbed Confession
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~
So what's the plan?
You working tonight?
Oh, don't remind me.
Would you keep Roscoe quiet
while I grab a quick nap?
- I am exhausted.
- Sure.
And I do not love your father.
Oh, my God.
Where have you been?
- My water broke.
- Okay. Okay. Uh, stay calm.
- Here we go.
- We need a new bathroom rug.
- How was your nap?
- Bite me.
- Roscoe?!
- What?
- Why aren't you wearing pants?
- I was relaxing.
Damn it. Come on.
Hey. How's she doing?
Son of a bitch!
That's the nicest thing
she's said in the last hour.
- The doctor's in with her now.
- Cool.
Oh. Hey, buddy. You want to
go hang out with your old dad?
I want to stay and see the baby.
Roscoe, we talked about this.
I don't care.
I want to see the baby.
Let me explain it to him.
Look up at me and nod like
I'm saying something smart.
How we doing, Doc?
She's three centimeters,
so we still have a little time.
Okay.
Why don't you go check on
Alvin and I'll hang with Violet.
Why don't YOU go check on Alvin
and I'll hang with Violet.
'Cause she's my daughter
and he's your long-lost lover.
Do you want to go to ICU?
Because it's right there.
Ah. Bring it!
Come on. Show me what you got!
Okay. I have rounds.
- But I was gonna be an uncle.
- Hey. I was gonna be the voice
of an animated character
in a Pixar movie.
But things don't always work out.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about waking
up one day and realizing
that you've wasted your
life chasing stupid dreams.
You got to get ready for that.
Somehow we forgot to
bring your toothbrush,
but I can run downst...
- What are you doing?
- I'm going home.
- You're kidding, right?
- Mm-mm. I'm not doing this.
Now, where are my freaking shoes?
I don't understand.
Is this about the adoption?
No. I don't want to have the baby.
It's gonna hurt!
You're just figuring that out now?
Okay. Breathe. Breathe.
I can breathe at home!
Now, let's roll!
Hmm.
Morphine.
Now I want a heart attack.
- Hey.
Did you come back to finish the job?
Don't be silly.
I like seeing you weak and diminished.
- Still, thanks for coming to visit.
- Eh... don't flatter yourself.
I'm only here 'cause Violet's upstairs
having the baby.
Oh... right. How's she doing?
She's fine.
She's surrounded by loved ones.
Speaking of which,
where's your wife and children?
I haven't told them yet.
- Why not?
- I don't want them to worry.
Well, don't expect me to, either.
You wouldn't be here
if you weren't.
Shh...
go to the light.
You shouldn't be sad.
You have lots of reasons to live.
- Like what?
- Um...
give me a second.
- Damn it, Violet. Get back in bed!
- No! I want to go home!
Sweetie, even if you leave the hospital,
that baby is still coming out.
Not if I hold it in.
Now, get out of my way!
I will not!
Now, you need to get in bed
- and just let things happen.
- That's how I got here.
Okay. Well, that's a
conversation for another time.
Come on. Lay down.
It's not fair.
My friend Rachel had
sex with her boyfriend,
and she didn't get pregnant.
She even had sex with Alissa's
boyfriend and didn't get pregnant.
My only takeaway from all
that is that Rachel's a slut.
Oh. Okay. All right.
Just breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
Ooh. I have an idea.
What are you doing?
I'm making a video for you to watch
the next time you think
about having unprotected sex.
That's not funny.
Look at the camera.
- Enough?
- Yeah. Thanks.
So, ever think in a million years
you and I'd be together like this?
First of all, we're not together.
And secondly, I have
dreamed of standing over
your dying body for decades.
So, you dream about me?
Listen, the doctor said this
was a small heart attack,
but if the big one's coming...
I need you to know how sorry I am.
Oh, please. Spare me
the deathbed confession.
I can't. Running out on
you when Christy was born
was the stupidest thing I've ever done.
And... I'll never forgive myself.
- That was a long time ago, Alvin.
- So, you forgive me?
- Would that give you peace?
- Yeah.
Then I'm gonna say...
...suck it.
If it matters at all, I...
had my will rewritten
to include you and Christy and the kids.
Really?
Signed and filed?
Yeah.
Shh...
go to the light.
You know, when your mom
kicked me out, I thought,
"Okay. I'm free.
I can party.
I can date lots of girls.
It's all good, right?"
Sounds good.
It's not.
It's lonely out there, kiddo.
And I am not getting any younger.
Living in my van is
getting less cute everyday.
You're still cute, Dad.
Thanks.
But we both know I'm borderline creepy.
Would ice cream make you feel better?
Couldn't hurt.
Come on. Let's go.
You got any money?
Shouldn't Luke be here by now?
He was too high to
drive, so he took the bus.
He smokes pot on the day
you're having the baby?
Don't make a big deal about it.
He smokes pot every day.
- Violet?
- There he is.
- Luke?
- Where are you?
I'm in here.
- I'm coming, baby.
- Luke!
In here!
Violet?
You just walked past me.
Violet...!
Luke!
"Every day," you say?
All right, Mr. Biletnikoff,
- everything's looking good.
- Thanks, Doc.
Be back to check on you in the morning.
- Mrs. Biletnikoff.
- I'm not Mrs. Biletnikoff.
Mrs. Biletnikoff left him
for a a guy on Facebook.
Okay.
Try to stay calm.
Hey. I push this button,
and the nurse is here in a second!
Relax. I'm just fluffing.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Mmm.
And I've decided...
to accept your apology.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It's time to move on.
Thank you, Bonnie.
That means a lot to me.
Forget about it.
Mm-mm.
You know, my heart's not
strong enough for sex.
Don't tempt me.
- Hi.
- Hi. Oh.
- Thanks for getting here so fast.
- Of course.
- Hi.
- Hey.
How's Violet?
Oh, you know,
a little crazy, a little mean.
But nothing that'll be passed down.
We brought some gifts for her.
I found a couple nice tops
and some cool earrings.
Yes, the earrings are cool.
That's very thoughtful.
- Is there anything we can do?
- I think we got it covered.
Unless you know how to do an episiotomy.
I-I don't.
- She's kidding.
- Oh.
Christy, something
amazing just happened.
- Is the baby born?
- Is the baby here?
Oh, no. Hi, hi.
Good to see you.
No, I was just making
out with Christy's father.
You scamp.
Please, uh, excuse me for a second.
What happened to hating his guts?
Oh, no, I don't think
I ever said "hate."
You said it, you sang it, you
bought an unregistered handgun.
Violet!
- Hey.
So...
how you feeling?
- Much better.
- Yeah.
That's what I hear.
- She told you.
- Yep.
I don't know what to
say. It just happened.
You... have any thoughts as
to where this goes from here?
You got me.
Right before we kissed,
she tried to kill me.
Twice.
All right, well,
you're both grown-ups.
I'm not gonna tell you
how to live your lives.
- Thanks.
- But here's the thing.
She's just a few months sober
and still pretty raw.
- You know, emotionally.
- I get it.
- Very fragile.
- Right.
Five-eleven in flats
and crazy as a bag of rats.
That's the girl I fell in love with.
Oh, my God, we're at nine centimeters.
- I got to go.
- Go, go, go.
I'm really glad you're okay.
Violet, this isn't funny anymore!
You're doing very well.
Let's try another push.
- I changed my mind.
- I told you,
you can't go home.
You're having the baby.
No, I want to keep it.
You want to keep the baby?
I'm never going through this pain again,
so I have to keep this one.
Well, what about the Taylors?
Tell them I am sorry,
but I changed my mind.
Violet, you're in a
lot of pain right now,
so you might want to wait till after...
This is my baby.
I am keeping it!
Okay. Um...
- What do I do?
- No idea.
- Do I go tell the Taylors?
- I think you got to.
- You want to do it?
- Hell no.
- Please?
- No.
You suck.
Oh, hey.
You guys can't find her, either?
- No, she's right down the hall.
- Oh. Weird.
Excuse me.
If you don't mind,
I'm gonna hang with you.
- Please.
- Thanks.
Oh, listen, now that I got you here,
I want to run a couple
baby names by you.
- Oh, okay. Sure.
- If it's a boy...
Smokey.
Smokey?
Smokey Taylor. Who doesn't
want to be Smokey Taylor?
- You know, it's not that bad.
- Oh, no.
Now, if it's a girl...
Smokey.
- Hey.
- Is it here?
No, no, no baby yet.
Um...
there has been a development, though.
Here, uh, why don't you sit down.
- Is she okay?
- She's fine. Um, the thing is...
- Where the heck did you go to?!
- What?
She changed her mind again.
- Really?
- Really.
Uh...
looked like a breech birth,
but then the baby did
a little somersault,
stuck the landing.
You need to start thinking gymnastics.
- Olympics 2032.
- USA! USA! USA!
Smokey Taylor for the gold.
- What the hell happened?
- The minute you walked out, she freaked
and started yelling that she
wasn't ready to be a mother.
How do we know she's not gonna
freak and change her mind again?
- We don't.
- I just hate this.
Hey, Bonnie.
- Oh, hi.
- Oh, God.
- How's Violet?
- She's doing okay. How are you doing?
- I'm cool, I'm cool.
- Yeah, you are.
I hate to break this up, kids,
but your great-grandchild
is about to be born.
- I'll be up to check on you later.
- Right on.
- Oh, God, his gown is open.
- Yeah, he's showing off.
You did great, honey.
Thanks.
You were so brave.
How come my stomach's not smaller?
Didn't anyone tell you?
You're gonna be fat forever.
It just... takes some time.
Would you like to hold your daughter?
You don't have to, honey.
No.
I want to say good-bye.
Hey there, little girl.
I just want you to know
that I'm doing this for you
and that you are gonna
have a wonderful life
with your new mom and dad.
And they are gonna love you so much.
- I don't know what else to say.
- You said it.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Hi. I'm Christy,
and I'm an alcoholic.
Hi, Christy.
Today I'm one year sober.
And I'd like to say it was
the best year of my life.
But the truth is it was
a 365-day crap storm,
starting with the woman
I hated most in the world
coming back into my life.
Mom, take a bow.
But I didn't drink.
My teenage daughter got pregnant,
and I still didn't drink.
And then I met two
incredible women here,
both of whom I truly love
and look up to.
One got cancer, and...
the other one went to jail.
Marjorie?
Cancer.
Jail sends her love.
And then I tracked down
my Dad, who I'd never met.
And we actually started
to build a relationship.
Aw.
He just had a heart attack.
Oh.
And my Mom made out
with him in the hospital.
Ooh.
And then yesterday,
my daughter gave her
baby up for adoption.
And that had
to be the hardest thing
I've experienced in my life.
But I didn't drink.
Didn't even think about it.
Okay, I thought about it, but...
I didn't want to.
Okay, I wanted to.
But I didn't do it.
It's funny. I thought...
I got sober and my life fell apart.
But what really happened was
I got sober just in time.
So... thank you.
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~
www.tvsubtitles.net
I'm thinking about going vegan.
Really? Why?
Diet, health,
compassion for animals.
I am not happy with
how my urine smells.
Then stop smelling it!
Oh! Don't look!
Don't smell, don't look...
you're bossy today!
- Isn't that the chef from your restaurant?
- Yeah.
- He's kind of cute.
- No! He's not!
Everyone at work
is terrified of him.
How scary can he be?
He's carrying a purse.
Hey! Hello there.
Damn!
Hi!
Chef Rudy, good to see you.
Good to see you, too...
I wanna say... Meredith?
- Christy.
- Right. And your mother Bonnie.
I work with you every day,
and her you remember?
Does a thirsty man forget
a tall glass of water?
May I join you?
Sure.
So, my daughter tells
me everyone at work
is frightened of you.
Ooh, that's very sweet.
Thank you.
So, what kind of naughtiness
is the mother-daughter
team up to today?
Don't go there.
Mmm, too late.
Mental snapshot. Click.
We've just come back
from the drugstore,
where we bought some, you know...
- girl stuff.
- Click.
What are you up to today?
Oh, just blowing
the dust off my spyder.
- Beg pardon?
- I have a vintage Porsche Spyder.
She's high-strung, impulsive,
and if I don't ride her hard
at least once a day,
she misbehaves.
I'm the same way.
Click.
Aw, all out of film.
Yeah. I will bid you adieu.
A la prochaine.
Yeah, I just know "adieu."
Tell me you haven't tapped that.
- Of course not.
- Good.
1x12 - Corned Beef and Handcuffs
sync by YesCool, corrections by f1nc0
- - www.addic7ed.com - -
Can I ask you a little friendly advice
vis-à-vis my personal affairs?
Oh. Yeah. Sure.
Great. What are my chances
of bedding your mother?
What?
I felt there was chemistry between us.
But I feel that with a
lot of women, often with
disastrous results.
Fun fact: Pepper spray
tastes nothing like pepper.
All right, look...
I don't want to get
involved here, but...
I will tell you she was
quite taken with you.
Oh, I knew it.
When I walked out of that coffee
shop, my testicles were on fire.
You might want to get those looked at.
That's what I'm trying to do.
Be a dear, get her on the phone for me.
Okay, but I got to warn
you about my mother.
There's a little crazy
up in them thar hills.
Mm-hmm.
Well, you know what they say,
"nothing soils the sheets like crazy."
How are you allowed to touch food?
Hi, Mom, it's me.
I'm probably going
to regret this, but...
He's right here.
Hey, you.
Been ridden hard yet, today?
Aah, clickety-click, click, click.
Is Grandma having dinner with us?
- No, she's got a date.
- Cool. You know the guy?
- I do.
- So, do you think they'll hit it off?
I'm thinking murder-suicide.
It's so weird to think
of your Grandma dating.
My Grandma weighs 300
pounds and has one leg.
Well, doesn't mean there's
not someone
- out there for her.
- That's true.
My Grandfather would sure
love it if she met somebody.
Oh, I'll get it.
Well, Grandma will be easy
to spot at the wedding.
- Well, you must be Violet.
- No, I-I'm Luke.
Well, you're very pretty, nonetheless.
Bonnie here?
Uh, she's getting ready.
Come on in.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
Well, I had you pegged
for a house on wheels.
That's the dream.
Can I get you something to drink?
I wouldn't mind a glass of Pinot Grigio.
I wouldn't mind a bucket of Gin.
But, uh, all we've got
is tap water and milk.
Mmm. I'll pass.
What am I smelling?
- I made dinner.
- No, that can't be it.
Do you have pets?
It's corned beef and cabbage.
Oh, yes, poor people food.
My apologies.
It smells delicious.
Ready to go?
Oh, well, there's a tasty morsel.
Yum, yum.
- Thank you.
- He's gonna eat her?
- Shall we?
- Did you bring the Spyder?
- Freshly lubed for your pleasure.
- Ooh! Bye, family.
- Have fun.
- Are we poor people?
Of course not.
Now, eat your boiled meat.
Wow, that was quite an education,
watching a master Chef
shop for groceries.
Well, I think it's
important to feel and smell
the things we put inside us.
I got to tell you, if I'm smelling it,
I'm not feeling it.
So, um, what are we having?
Well, it's a tasting menu that I call
"seven small explosions in your mouth."
Seven, huh?
Let's see.
Salty, sweet, savory, sour...
- help me.
- Crunchy, creamy and Rudy.
Ooh.
What's Rudy taste like?
Pistachios, I've been told.
Mm.
But the real magic happens
when we start to combine flavors.
For example,
take a simple cherry tomato.
Squirt a little aged balsamic
vinegar into its fleshy center.
"Cherry," "squirt," "fleshy."
- You can't help yourself, can you?
- It's very hard.
Mmm!
That's not sweet like a
tomato or sour like vinegar.
Exactly.
It's a third thing that didn't exist
until one was driven
deep inside the other.
And yes, I know what I just said.
Where'd you go to culinary school?
- Can you keep a secret?
- Of course.
A Denny's in Boston.
I worked the late shift;
there's a lot of time to screw around.
- Where's the Boston accent?
- I dropped it.
Hard to charge 60 bucks
for lobster chowder with capers.
Ah. Yeah.
Well, where are my manners?
Can I get you a glass of wine?
- No, thank you. I don't drink.
- Never?
- Never.
- Impressive.
How is it that you have
not killed yourself?
I'm more of a homicide girl.
Well, then, as a good host,
I won't drink, either.
Ah, who am I kidding?
- So, why do you abstain?
- I'm allergic to alcohol.
Every time I drink,
I break out in handcuffs.
Mm.
Pity.
I have a rather remarkable collection
of wine and handcuffs.
You know, next to great food,
beautiful women and vintage cars,
wine is what brings
me the most happiness.
No, actually, it's women, then food...
No, wine, women...
ah, I left out pills.
- It's pills, wine...
- I get the point.
Let's see how sophisticated
your palate is. Hmm?
Put on this blindfold.
Well, I usually charge 50
bucks extra for that, but okay.
I knew I liked you.
- And... you ready?
- Do it.
- What do you taste?
- Mmm. Fig?
Very good.
Now, try this.
Mmm.
Eel?
And here comes the pistachios.
Morning.
- Walk of shame?
- Stride of pride.
Did you consider, for even a minute,
to go slow with this guy?
See a movie,
shop at the flea market,
text him a picture of your boobs.
You know, like a lady.
- I did think about it.
- And?
I chose instead to do him
on the floor of his kitchen.
What is wrong with you?
Don't you have any self-respect?
Oh, please. Self-respect is for
women who spend Saturday night
alone with their
showerhead set on pulse.
That's a terrible thing to say.
And I happen to have
a stiff neck from work.
Did it ever occur to you
that what happened last night
between me and Rudolph was the
start of something wonderful?
Oh, wake up!
It's a one-night stand
between a middle-aged alcoholic
- and a sex addict.
- How dare you call me middle-aged?
And it was not a one-night stand.
Rudy and I are two ingredients,
which, when combined,
create a third thing which...
never existed before.
What the hell are you talking about?
I don't know!
It's a tomato thing!
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go take a shower.
To clean myself.
You'll never be clean!
So, are we gonna talk about it?
Well, I was gonna be a gentleman
and spare you the details,
but as you wish.
Your mother is sleek yet powerful,
like an enormous greyhound.
Yeah, great.
Not what I want to talk about.
I... I just want to put it out there
that no matter where your
relationship goes with her,
you and I maintain
a professional relationship here.
Okay, two things wrong
with that, Meredith.
First of all, you and I don't have
a professional relationship.
I'm a world-class Chef,
and you are a waitress.
And no offense, but I would
be just as happy to put my food
on a tiny toy train that
choo-choos into the dining room.
And secondly,
I have absolutely no plans
to pursue a relationship
with your mommy.
What?
I thought the two of
you made "a third thing".
With a tomato.
No, that's just my rap when I'm
trying to filet some panties.
Oh.
So, you're not planning
on seeing her again?
Oh, god, no.
Well, never say never.
Can't have a Russian hooker every night.
I don't believe this.
What kind of a man are you?
Well, selfish, narcissistic,
emotionally crippled by
a cold and distant mother.
You know, the usual.
She's gonna be devastated.
Well, then you better
break it to her gently.
I'm not gonna tell her.
Wow, that seems cruel.
But your call.
- What's going on?
- That pig slept with my mother.
Welcome to the club.
- Hey.
- Roscoe asleep?
- Yup.
- What'd you do tonight?
- What do you care?
Oh, come on.
I'm sorry about this morning.
Really?
So, you admit that Rudy and I
are capable of having
a meaningful relationship?
Well...
I admit that I love you.
All right, what's going on?
Rudy's done with you.
Well, why are you
telling me instead of him?
Because...
he was emotionally
crippled by his mother.
And, you know...
he's a giant douche.
- Wow, so I completely misread him.
- I'm so sorry.
No, you warned me.
I'm a big girl.
I should have known better.
Look at me, giving myself a pedicure
so that jerk could suckle
on a pretty red toe.
Is that his thing?
Oh, yeah, he's got a mouth
like a Chinese finger trap.
My fault, I asked.
All right, I'm gonna
take a quick shower.
Say hi to your "boyfriend."
I would, but after he saw
you naked, we broke up.
- Are you gonna be all right?
- Oh, yeah.
Not gonna do anything crazy?
Oh, come on, go take a shower.
Okay.
It's like she doesn't know me at all.
Yes, I want a medium meat lover's
pizza with cheese in the crust.
Yes, and some crazy bread.
- Hello, Rudolph.
- Bonnie.
How'd you get in my house?
Oh, please. Who sleeps with a man
and doesn't steal his spare keys?
- Okay. What do you want?
- What I want is to hurt you.
But not physically, because...
you might like that.
But on an emotional level,
like you hurt me.
No, you are barking up
the wrong tree, sister,
because I stopped feeling years ago.
Really?
We'll see.
Hmm.
"1957 Château Latour."
Ooh, sounds fancy.
Thank you.
And for my next trick,
I will attempt to juggle
three bottles of...
ooh, Montrachet.
Oh, ooh, ooh.
Aw.
I'm not very good.
Okay, I lied.
I didn't just get clean.
Mom?
Oh, damn it!
No.
And this Mouton Rothschild
is for little Jimmy,
who's sick in the hospital.
Please, no more.
And this Château Montelena
is for all the wine snobs
and their nutty top notes.
Enough! Stop!
I can't take it anymore.
Good.
Come to me.
Oh, my god, you're magnificent.
Now what?
Suckle.
Hello?
Oh, my god, I'm too late.
Ah, ah, oh, yeah, Bonnie,
right there, wicked hard!
Who the hell is that?
- Mmm.
- Oh, my god.
This duck pâté is so much
better than corned beef.
Yeah, and the house won't
smell like a thousand egg farts.
Hello.
Oh, hi, Chef Rudy.
Thanks for the picnic basket.
Yeah, I know it's not for me.
What's up?
Hang on, let me see if she's here.
She's not here.
Can I take a message?
Oh, s-slow down, let me grab a pen.
Go ahead.
"The... the dark, violent turn
our love play took
last night haunts me""
Wait, say again?
"The wine cork will remain where it is
as a sign of my commitment".
All right, I'll be sure
she gets the message.
Of course I won't tell
anyone at the restaurant.
Bye-bye.
I think someone's sweet on you.
sync by YesCool, corrections by f1nc0
- - www.addic7ed.com - -
www.tvsubtitles.net
I think you'll find our...
Napa Chardonnay to have
hints of vanilla and caramel
with a velvety smooth finish.
Are you all right?
Some days are better
than others.
Thanks for asking.
It's very good.
Yeah, 2004 was a great
year for this wine.
Not so much for me.
Enjoy.
So, did I talk you into that soufflé?
- Uh, yeah, two.
- Good call.
You won't want to share.
Oh, God.
♪ Happy birthday to you  ♪
♪ Happy birthday
to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear... ♪
♪ Ethel ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you. ♪
♪ And many more.  ♪
Hm...
More butter and salt.
They only need to live long
enough to pay the check.
Beat those egg whites gently...
as if they were a small, annoying child.
Paul, you're on fire again.
Um, Christy, you got a second?
I can't talk now, Gabriel.
I'm working.
Yeah, I know, but, uh, here's the thing.
I-I'm getting a lot of complaints.
Really?
About what?
Well, apparently, one of my waitresses
- is having a nervous breakdown.
- Is it Jennifer?
- No.
- Is it Carol?
It's you!
Gabriel, what does
this taste like to you?
- Uh, mushrooms?
- The correct answer was "ass."
Listen, uh, maybe you should
take the rest of the night off.
I can't afford to do that.
I have children to feed.
Not a problem. Grab a couple
steaks, head home and feed 'em.
You don't understand.
The guy at table 4 said
something horrible to me
when I was telling him about the salmon.
- What's wrong with the salmon?
- Nothing, the salmon's great!
- The guy insulted me.
- Oh, that's fine.
- What did he say?
- He said I was...
"a good waitress."
That's not bad.
Or true.
I didn't grow up to
be a "good waitress""
That was never the plan.
The plan was to be a psychologist.
Okay.
You're a young woman.
- You can still do that.
- Yeah, maybe.
I'd probably have to
graduate high school first.
Now all I've got to look
forward to is serving $60 risotto
to a bunch of smug food Nazis.
I mean, who are we kidding?
It's a big, steaming
pile of gooey rice!
- What did you say?
- Get over yourself, Rudy.
I saw you at McDonald's
going down on a Big Mac.
First of all,
it was a Filet-O-Fish.
- And for you?
- Um, I'd like the, uh...
I'd like the, uh,
the pounded capon with,
uh, lemongrass and thyme.
Excellent choice.
You know...
that's a castrated chicken
they beat with a hammer.
1x01 - Pilot
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ addic7ed.com ~
Daily affirmations.
I open my heart and
allow wonderful things
to flow into my life.
I open my heart
and allow wonderful things
to flow into my life.
Forgiving those who have wronged me
is a gift I give myself.
My daughter's an easy lay
and it's not my fault.
- Hi.
- I'm sorry. Did I wake you?
That's okay.
How was work?
Oh, fun.
I feel guilty taking the money.
What'd you do tonight?
Not much.
Did my homework, watched TV.
Mmm.
Is there a TV on your ceiling?
What?
Sit down.
We need to talk.
What's up?
Violet, I can't tell you...
not to have sex at your age,
because I had sex at your age.
Mom, I'm not having sex.
Don't lie to the woman
who washes your sheets.
And in case you've forgotten,
I got pregnant with you
when I was a teenager.
And please don't take
this the wrong way:
- It ruined my life.
- I love you, too, Mom...?
And I can't tell you not
to drink and smoke pot,
because my senior yearbook quote was:
"Let's drink and smoke pot""
- Can this please be over?
- You don't know how lucky you are.
My mother never bothered to
talk to me about this stuff.
- Yeah, this is over.
- Honey, I just don't want you
to wake up one day and feel bad
'cause you're not a psychologist!
Okay, good talk!
Let's get you back in your own bed.
- Hi, Mom.
- Hi, sweetie.
- I waited up for you.
- Thank you.
- Violet's boyfriend was over.
- I know.
They were kissing.
I'm sure they were.
They took a shower together.
Terrific.
Are you coming to my
talent show tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
What time?
11:00.
Oh, honey, I have to
work the lunch shift.
It's okay.
I'm not good anyway.
Listen, maybe I can get
someone to cover my shift.
Don't worry about it.
No, I-I want you to be able
to look out into the audience
and see me, because that
way you'll know how much I...
Shh!
Mommy, I'm sleeping.
Good talk.
Hi.
You feeling better?
Oh, yeah.
My home is a real oasis.
- So, am I in trouble with Chef Rudy?
- He'll be fine.
He bought an eight ball and
took home the pastry chef.
Sleeping with your boss.
Who does that?
Mom...?
- Yeah, honey?
- I had a bad dream.
Oh, no, well, um...
why don't you go back to bed
and I'll come lay down
with you in a second?
I'm so sorry.
I owe you one.
Don't lay there too long.
The sprinklers come on in ten minutes.
- What the hell?
- Can I help you?
- What time is the talent show?
- What talent show?
- There's no talent show today?
- I don't think so.
Are you freaking kidding me?!
- I lost a day's pay for no reason?
- Maybe we were destined to meet.
It would definitely be
the high point of my day.
Psst! Roscoe!
Hi, Mom.
What are you doing here?
- The talent show?
- That's not today.
- But you said it was!
- Guess I was wrong.
I guess you were.
Don't you kids tease him about this.
Son of a bitch!
Oh, God, I need a drink.
Hi, I'm Christy and I'm an alcoholic.
Hi, Christy.
I've been sober 118 days.
Oh, don't applaud for that.
They've been the worst
118 days of my life.
Um...
The only reason I'm here is because, uh,
I didn't want to turn into my mother.
And I did anyway.
Yeah, I drank like her.
I went through men like her.
Um, I was selfish to my kids
just like she was.
And I didn't know how
to live any other way
because she was my only role model.
I mean, some mothers teach
their daughters how to bake.
Mine taught me how to
beat a cavity search
and still feel like a lady.
Anyway, thanks for letting me share.
And I cannot tell you
how comforting it is
to be in a room with people
who are just as screwed
up as I am, so...
Oh, stop it.
Hi, I'm Jim and I'm an alcoholic.
Hi, Jim.
Aren't you a little old
to be blaming all your
problems on your mother?
Hi, Mom.
Hi, I'm Greg.
May I take your order?
Hi, Greg. I'm Bonnie and
this is my daughter, Christy.
- Hi.
- She and I haven't spoken
in a couple of years, so this
is kind of a big moment for us.
Oh, for God's sake.
What can you recommend
for a mother and daughter
who are reconnecting after
a long, angry silence?
Um... pie?
- Mom, please, just order.
- Um, is the mint tea decaffeinated?
- Yes.
- Do you promise?
If I have caffeine after
2:00, my sleep in ruined.
- I promise.
- Okay, Greg, but if I wake up
in the middle of the
night, I'm calling you.
Well, I'll-I'll give you my number.
Um, and for you?
We have a lovely
selection of local wines.
I'll have a bottle of each
and a funnel.
She's kidding. We're both
in Alcoholics Anonymous.
Mom, it's Alcoholics Anonymous,
not Alcoholics Tell Your Waiter.
Water is fine. Here, take
this knife away from me.
So, when were you going to
tell me you quit drinking?
Well, I was afraid if I called you,
I'd just start again.
Not that you care,
but I have two years
clean and sober myself.
You're right; I don't care.
Well, regardless,
it has really changed my life.
I have a steady job.
I exercise.
I'm in a book club!
I have become the kind of
woman I've always hated.
It is nice to see you
wearing underwear.
And not on your head.
Here we go.
Oh, Greg, honey,
can I trouble you for
some water without ice?
Ice isn't good for my digestive system.
- Yeah, of course.
- Really? Ice?
I think your digestive system
has seen worse than ice.
Excuse me?
Mom, I've watched you
lick cocaine crumbs
out of a shag carpet.
It's not a sin to be thrifty, dear.
Okay, here we go.
Now, I hope that you're
being nice to your mother.
- Go away, Greg!
- Right.
Whoa, whoa.
You know, just because you're sober
doesn't mean you can't take a Xanax.
Actually, Mom, it sort of does.
Really?
Maybe I don't have two years.
And I don't need a Xanax;
I'm doing great.
Well, that's funny, 'cause
your daughter says you're
hanging on by your fingernails
and sleeping with your boss.
Wait, when do you talk to Violet?
We talk all the time, and
we're Facebook friends.
I don't want her talking to you.
Well, she has to talk to somebody.
She's sexually active,
drinking, smoking grass.
Sound familiar?
You're making this about me?
No, it's okay.
I have come to understand
that you were the best
daughter you could be.
My job is to forgive you,
which I do.
Oh, my God!
- You forgive me?
- I've come a long way.
Excuse me, but if anybody
needs to be forgiven,
it's you, and I don't,
and I never will.
There's hardly a day I can remember
that I didn't come
home to an empty house.
Oh, don't be so dramatic.
While other mothers were cooking
dinner, you were cooking meth.
Otherwise known as "working."
I don't want you in my life.
And while you're at it,
stay away from my daughter!
She may need a better
role model than me,
but it's certainly not you.
- Is, uh, everything okay?
- My daughter doesn't get me.
Oh. I'm sorry.
What time do you get off work?
I could use a lap to cry on.
Oh.
Stop crying.
It wasn't an important finger.
This doesn't concern you.
Oh, good, you're still here.
Hey, hi.
This is a surprise.
Yeah, I just really
needed to talk to you.
I am having the worst day.
- Hey, you ready to go?
- Yes, dear.
Um, Christy,
you know my, uh, wife.
Yeah, hi, Claudia.
Nice to see you again.
It's "Clowdia""
FYI, the ladies' room
needs some attention.
I don't know if that's you, Christy.
It's not,
and it's "Christ-y."
Okay, dear, let's go.
- Bye.
- Yeah.
Don't serve the soup.
- Hey, Mom. Dad's here!
- Yo, yo, baby mama.
What do you want, Baxter?
A father can't visit his son?
Not when he's six months
behind on child support,
but you're welcome to wave
at him through the window.
Be right back, Roscoe.
Don't be afraid to hit
the hookers with a bat.
I think I may have found a way
to pay you your child support.
Trust me, Baxter,
you can't sell that much semen.
I know. I tried.
So, here's the deal:
I know a guy who can hook me up
with a couple of kilos
of premium Sonoma Kush.
All I need is $2,000...
...from you.
Just so I'm clear:
You want to pay child support
by borrowing money from
me so you can buy pot?
No. So I can sell pot.
There's no money in buying pot.
I know. I tried.
Oh.
Hey. Hello.
- What are you doing here?
- Um...
studying...?
You let Violet have boys
over while you're gone?
No, I do not, and don't worry
about her, she's not your kid.
I know, but this sets
a bad example for Roscoe.
Oh, you're worried
about setting a bad example?
You had Roscoe pee into a sippy cup
so you could pass a drug test.
And it worked.
I like bananas.
They have their own carrying case.
You know I can't divorce Claudia.
Her father owns the restaurant;
I'm pretty sure he'd
fire me, and then what?
I was an English major.
I can't believe you're
sleeping with that loser.
sleeping with this loser!
Hey, we were mostly studying.
Shut up, Luke.
I love him.
- Please, I used to love him!
- She did.
Mom, Luke and I have been
together for, like, a year.
You only started noticing
when you stopped drinking.
You're right.
I-I haven't been a very good mother,
- and I'm sorry, but...
- But what?
You want me to forgive you?
Oh, God, would you?
That'd be awesome!
Why should I forgive you
when you can't even
forgive your own mother?
- That's different.
- How?
Okay.
Okay...
Hello, Mom, it's Christy.
Yeah, yeah,
today was a blast.
Listen...
I just want you to know
that I forgive you
for everything you did
when I was growing up.
I get, now, that
you did the best you could...
...just like I'm doing.
And...
I hope that you and I can
wipe the slate clean
and start over.
No, I did not take
a Xanax from your purse!
Listen, I gotta go.
Yeah, talk soon.
There.
I've forgiven my mother.
- Are we good?
- It's not that easy.
Oh, come on!
Like me!
Hey, Dad!
If you hit the hookers enough times,
they give you your money back!
Smart kid.
That's my semen at work.
- You still living in that red van?
- Yep.
Looks like your house is being towed.
Oh, no,
my cleaning lady's in there.
What a day, huh?
Hello...?
- Oh, hi, Mom.
- Hello, sweetie.
What are you doing here?
I just thought I'd help
out while you were at work.
You know, clean slate.
- You didn't have to do that.
- Yeah, she did.
Bonnie made Roscoe
and me hot dinner.
- Yeah, but I...
- It was hot, Mom!
Like on TV.
Night, Bonnie.
- She calls you Bonnie?
- We're like sisters.
You hungry?
No, thanks. I ate at the restaurant.
How about some tea?
Okay.
I'm so glad
you and I have a chance to
start over.
Forgive me,
but I'm not quite there yet.
Of course I forgive you.
You know...
I apologized for beeing
a crappy daughter.
- So, anything you wanna say to me...
- I love you with all my heart.
And?
And... from now on, I'm going
to be the kind of mother you deserve.
This is the start of a new chapter.
Oh, it's my date!
New chapter, same book.
- Ready to go?
- Let me just get my bag.
You remember our waiter Greg?
Hi, new dad!
Please stop.
He's way to young for me.
And he's... married.
Married?
What a whore.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Your daughter think
she might be pregnant.
Call me, if you need me.
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ addic7ed.com ~
www.tvsubtitles.net