To understand what I'm about to tell you,
you need to do something first.
You need to believe in the impossible.
Can you do that? Good.
You see that red blur?
That's me.
That too.
There I am again.
My name is Barry Allen.
I am the fastest man alive.
My story is pretty simple.
My whole life, I have been running.
Usually from bullies.
Sometimes I escaped.
Sometimes I did not.
Tell me what happened.
Those guys were picking on kids
just 'cause they thought they weren't cool.
- It wasn't right.
- I know.
- I guess I wasn't fast enough.
- No.
You have such a good heart, Barry.
And it's better to have
a good heart than fast legs.
Hello. I'm home.
- Barry got into a fight.
- Oh, yeah?
And he won.
Ah, way to go, slugger.
Oh, and uh, no more fighting.
Mm-mm.
But after that night,
I was running from something much scarier.
- Something I could never explain.
- Henry! Henry!
Something impossible.
Help!
- Mom! Mom!
- Barry, don't!
- Mom!
- Don't let him touch you!
Mom!
- Nora!
- Stay back!
Nora, hold on!
Run, Barry, run!
Mom?
Dad?
Sorry.
Second robbery this week.
The teller I.D.'d Clyde
Mardon as the shooter.
What?
Oh, jeez, the Mardon Brothers are back?
What do we got?
Perps took the bank, shot out the cameras,
and as a chaser, killed
the security guard over there.
I've got unis kicking in doors
of known Mardon Brothers associates.
CSI been over it?
Uh, no.
Where's Allen?
Sorry, sorry.
You can't keep covering for him.
- CSI, CSI coming through.
- If he's not here now,
I'm gonna have to carry on this
investigation without him.
Sorry I'm late, Captain Singh.
What was it this time, Mr. Allen?
Did you forget to set your alarm clock?
Before you answer, I should remind you
the excuse you gave last time
was car trouble.
Want to know why that one
was particularly memorable?
I do not own a car.
He was running an errand for me.
Barry, did you get me what I asked for?
Yeah, yeah. I did.
I have it right...
Here.
I had a few bites of it.
Getaway car's a mustang shelby gt500.
Shelby's have a rear super-wide tire
specific to that model.
12 inches with an asymmetrical tread.
And there's something else.
Thanks.
Fecal excrement.
Animal, I'd guess.
My dad gave me that pen...
Before he died.
Sorry.
Okay, I am ready to see
this atom smasher smashing.
There was a shooting today.
Your dad needs me to process some evidence,
which means I don't know if we're going
to be able to make it to S.T.A.R. Labs.
But seeing this thing turn on
is like your dream.
Your sad, little nerdy dream.
Besides, I canceled a date for this.
Hands off my fries.
Unbelievable.
I'm stress eating over my dissertation.
We started selling cronuts at Jitters.
I ate two today. If I don't graduate soon,
I'm gonna be more muffin top than woman.
You look amazing.
What is so important
about this particle accelerator anyway?
Harrison Wells' work in quantum theory
is light-years ahead of anything
they're doing at Cern.
You're doing that thing where
you're not speaking English.
Okay.
Just imagine
that that dot is everything the human race
has ever learned until this moment.
Does that include "twerking"?
That is everything we could learn
from the particle accelerator.
It's a whole new way of looking at physics.
It will literally change the way
that we think about everything.
You got to get yourself a girlfriend.
Hey, leave him alone. He's working.
Hi, dad.
- Your test thingy is done.
- Yeah.
I think the Mardon Brothers
are hiding on a farm.
The fecal matter I found on
the street, it was cow manure,
which contained traces of oxytetracycline.
It's an antibiotic.
There are only four farms in the area
that still use it in their feed.
Bet you find a really sweet
shelby parked at one of them.
Dad, seeing as how Barry
solved your poop problem,
how about letting him go to S.T.A.R. Labs?
- Fine, go.
- Yes!
Thank you, Joe.
So, Barry, how was your trip?
Did you find proof of the
impossible in Starling City,
or did you just make my dad
mad for no reason?
Actually, while I was away,
I had a chance to think about...
You know, relationships.
And, well, I'm not in one.
And you're not in one, either.
And you're my best friend, Iris.
You're mine too.
Why else would I be here?
That's not what I meant. What I...
I know what you're gonna say, Barry.
I'm not sure you do.
Even though we pretty much grew up
in the same house together,
and we're kind of like brother and sister,
because we're not brother and sister,
it can get really weird and awkward
to talk to me about girls.
But I just want you to know
that it shouldn't be awkward.
There is nothing that I want more
than for you to meet the right person
that totally loves and adores you
for the amazing guy that you are.
Took the words right out of my mouth.
Aw, aren't you glad I know you so well?
Thank you.
My name is Harrison Wells.
Tonight, the future begins.
The work my team and I will do here
will change our understanding of physics.
We'll bring about advancements in power,
advancements in medicine,
and trust me, that future
will be here faster than you think.
Oh, hey, my laptop!
It's got my dissertation.
I'm sorry.
All right, kid, you don't have
to do this, all right?
Just give me back my friend's bag,
and we'll call it even.
Okay?
Barry!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Freeze! Police!
Or do you want to find out the hard way
you're not faster than a bullet?
Who is that guy,
and what is he so proud of?
So he caught a mugger?
He's a transfer from keystone.
Started a few weeks ago. Eddie Thawne.
Oh, that's Detective Pretty Boy.
That's what my dad calls him.
Says he actually keeps score
when it comes to arrests.
He is pretty though.
This is the last farm on Barry's list.
Look, I know the kid's smart,
but you said it yourself.
Sometimes he's chasing flying pigs.
Well, let's check it out anyway.
I'm Linda park, and we're live
outside S.T.A.R. Labs
despite the inclement weather,
which is only going to get worse.
The torrential downpour
has in no way affected
the particle accelerator,
which is up and running smoothly
according to S.T.A.R.
Labs CEO Harrison Wells.
The weather has also...
- Whoa.
- Mardon.
Ah!
I've got a plane to catch!
What the hell?
Ah!
Chyre, hang in there.
Wait, we're now being told
to evacuate the facility.
The storm may have caused a malfunction
to the primary cooling system.
Officials are now trying to shut down
the particle accelerator, but so far,
have been unable to regain
control of the system...
What the hell happened to him?
He was hit by lightning.
How is he still alive?
Go.
No heartbeat. CBC, chem 24,
type and cross four.
- Bag him.
- He's coding.
- You can't be in here.
- I'm family.
- Charge the paddles to 200.
- Barry!
Clear.
What are you doing?
He likes this song.
How could you possibly know that?
I checked his Facebook page.
I mean, he can hear everything, right?
Auditory functions are the last
sensory faculties to degenerate.
♪ Can't read my no
he can't read my poker... ♪
Oh, my God!
- Where am I?
- He's up.
Dr. Wells, get down
to the cortex, like, right now.
Pulse 120, pupils equally
reactive to light.
Look at me, look at me.
Hey, hey, whoa, whoa, relax.
Everything's okay, man.
You're at S.T.A.R. Labs.
S.T.A.R. Labs? Who are you?
I'm cisco Ramon. She's Caitlin... Dr. Snow.
I need you to urinate in this.
Not this second.
What is... what is happening?
What is going on?
You were struck by lightning, dude.
What?
Lightning gave me abs?
Your muscles should be atrophied,
but instead they're in a chronic
and unexplained state
of cellular regeneration.
Come here. Have a seat.
You were in a coma.
For how long?
Nine months.
Welcome back, Mr. Allen.
We have a lot to discuss.
It's hard to believe I'm here.
I have always wanted
to meet you face to face.
Yeah?
Well, you certainly went to
great lengths to do it.
S.T.A.R. Labs has not been operational
since FEMA categorized us
as a class four hazardous location.
17 people died that night.
Many more were injured.
Myself amongst them.
Jeez.
What happened?
Nine months ago, the particle accelerator
went online exactly as planned.
For 45 minutes, I had
achieved my life's dream.
And then... Then there was an anomaly.
The electron volts became unmeasurable,
the ring under us popped.
Energy from that detonation
was thrown into the sky
and that, in turn, seeded a storm cloud...
That created a lightning bolt
that struck me.
That's right.
I was recovering myself...
When I heard about you.
The hospital was undergoing
unexplainable power outages
every time you were going
into cardiac arrest,
which was actually a misdiagnosis
because you see,
you weren't flatlining, Barry.
Your heartbeat was moving too fast
for the EKG to register it.
Now, I'm not the most popular
person in town these days,
but Detective West and his daughter
gave me permission to bring you here,
where we were able to stabilize you.
- Iris?
- Iris, yes.
She came to see you quite often.
She talks a lot.
Also, she's hot.
- I need to go.
- No, you can't.
No, no. No, Caitlin's right.
No, now that you're awake,
we need to do more tests.
You're still going through changes.
There's so much that we don't know.
I'm fine. Really, I feel normal.
Thank you for saving my life.
Really?
Can I keep the sweatshirt?
- Yeah, keep the sweatshirt.
- Okay.
Sure.
- Fill 'er up?
- Thanks.
Oh, my God.
You're awake.
Why didn't S.T.A.R. Labs call us?
I just woke up.
Should you even be on your feet?
Iris, I... I'm okay.
I watched you die, Barry.
You kept dying. Your heart kept stopping.
It's still beating.
- Feels really fast.
- Oops.
Are you okay, Tracy?
Yeah, I got it.
My dad is gonna be so happy to see you.
Let me get my stuff, okay? Be right back.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
How can I help you today?
"This is a robbery."
Is this supposed to be a joke?
You tell me.
Oh, you scared the hell out of us, kid.
Yeah, that was quite the nap
you took there, baby face,
and you still look 12.
You look okay.
Are you really?
- Yeah.
- Detective West,
we've got a 5.15 in progress
at gold city bank, two dead.
Storm's really picking up
on the South side.
I'd grab your rain gear.
I'm sorry, Barry. I got to run.
- Do you need my help?
- No, you take it easy.
There'll be plenty for you to do
once you settle in.
Let's go, partner.
Hey, Allen. Glad to see you.
- Thanks, Eddie.
- Hey, Iris.
Detective, you should go.
My dad doesn't like to be kept waiting.
Glad you're back.
The night of the explosion,
Clyde Mardon shot and killed Chyre.
Mardon and his brother
died trying to escape.
Their plane crashed.
Iris, got a minute?
Hey, Barry. Good to see you.
Screw you!
You okay?
I... I'm fine.
I... I just need some air.
But I'll call you tonight, all right?
What's happening to me?
Oh, oh!
Awesome.
You don't really believe he
can run that fast, do you?
Well, I believe anything is possible,
and in a few minutes,
maybe you will too.
How does it fit?
It's a little snug.
At least you will be moving so fast
no one will see you.
See, you thought the
world was slowing down.
It wasn't.
You were moving so fast
it only looked like everyone
else was standing still.
Dr. Wells will be monitoring
your energy output,
and Caitlin, your vitals.
What do you do?
I make the toys, my man. Check it.
This is a two-way headset
with a camera I modified.
Typically designed to combat
battlefield impulse noise,
or in your case, potential sonic booms,
which would be awesome.
- What?
- Nothing.
I just noticed you don't smile too much.
My once promising career
in bioengineering is over,
my boss is in a wheelchair for life,
the explosion that put you in a coma
also killed my fiance.
So this blank expression kind of
feels like the way to go.
Mr. Allen, while I am extremely eager
to determine your full range of abilities,
I do caution restraint.
Yeah.
Woo-hoo!
He just passed 200 Miles per hour.
It's not possible.
Mom!
- No, Barry!
- Mom!
No! Don't let him touch you!
Aah!
What is all this?
Witnesses from the robbery
at Gold City Bank.
Perp made off with 200 grand, more or less.
- Catch these guys.
- The windows blew in.
It was like a hurricane.
Everyone ran for cover.
We're going to have
a sketch artist work with you,
if you feel up to it.
Third robbery in a month
where a freak storm precedes it.
Sounds like one of those
"wide world of weird" cases
- Barry's obsessed with.
- He's not obsessed.
Guess you haven't read his blog.
The security cameras at the bank.
Apparently it all shorted out.
We got a bunch of witnesses here.
They all have cell phones.
The sky went black and then, boom.
Outside was inside.
Man, it was like there was a thunderstorm
in the bank.
Vukuvich, suspect is driving
a black Mustang.
Partial plate six-kilo-Charlie-three.
- Put out an APB.
- Copy that.
It looks like you had
a distal radius fracture.
Had?
It's healed... In three hours.
How is that even possible?
We don't know... yet.
You really need to learn how to stop.
What happened out there today?
You were moving pretty well,
and then something
caused you to lose focus.
I started remembering something.
When I was 11, my mother was murdered.
It was late.
A sound woke me up.
I came downstairs and...
I saw what looked like a ball of lightning.
Inside the lightning,
there was a man.
He killed my mom.
They arrested my dad.
He's still sitting
in Iron Heights for her murder.
Everyone, the cops, the shrinks,
they all told me what I saw was impossible.
But what if the man who killed my mom
was like me?
Well, I think I can say unequivocally
you are one of a kind.
Can I help you, detective?
You can stop acting like you can't stand me
when your dad's around.
Aww.
And I like having a boyfriend
who isn't shot to death.
You can't tell my dad.
He doesn't know about me and Eddie.
Doesn't seem like anyone's
in on the secret.
I was gonna tell you.
When you were in the hospital,
Eddie covered my father's shifts
so that we could both be with you.
I thanked him with a cup of coffee,
and things just kind of happened.
And it's good.
Dating your partner's daughter...
Isn't that against department regulations?
Why are you so upset?
I just don't like having
to lie to your dad, you know?
Barry?
Hey! Mardon!
That poor man.
The way that fog came in,
I have never seen anything like it.
Barry! Iris.
I'm all right, dad.
What the hell were you thinking
- having her out here?
- No, no, no...
And I told you, when you see danger,
you run the other way. You're not a cop.
- Because you wouldn't let me.
- You're damn right.
Joe, I need to talk to you.
- It can wait.
- No, now.
I know who did this.
It's Clyde Mardon.
I know everybody thinks
he died in a plane crash
after the S.T.A.R. Labs explosion,
but he is alive.
All right, something
happened to him that night.
I... I think he can control the weather.
The recent robberies,
they all happened during
freak meteorological events.
And when I just confronted Mardon,
the street was instantly enveloped in fog.
Of course you don't believe me.
- You never believe me.
- Okay.
You want to do this now?
Out here? Fine.
Mardon is dead.
There is no controlling the weather, Barry.
Just like there was no lightning storm
in your house that night.
It was your brain
helping a scared little boy
accept what he saw.
My dad did not murder my mother.
Yes, he did! Your dad killed
your mother, Barry!
I am sorry, son!
But I knew it, the jury knew it,
and now he's paying for what he did.
- Dad, enough!
- Unh-uh, Iris.
I have done my best to take care of you
since that night, and I have never asked
for anything in return,
not even a thank you,
but what I do ask now is that you
for once in your life
see things as they are.
You're not going to believe this.
We got the eyewitness sketch
of the robber from the bank job.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say that's Clyde Mardon.
But that's impossible.
He's dead, right?
I wasn't the only one affected
by the particle accelerator
explosion, was I?
We don't know for sure.
You said the city was safe,
that there was no residual danger.
But that's not true, so what
really happened that night?
Well...
The accelerator went active.
We all felt like heroes, and then...
It all went wrong.
The dimensional barrier ruptured,
unleashing unknown energies into our world.
Antimatter, dark energy, x-elements...
Those are all theoretical.
And how theoretical are you?
We mapped the dispersion
throughout and around Central City.
Though we have no way of knowing
exactly what or... Who was exposed,
we've been searching for other
- meta-humans like yourself.
- "Meta-humans"?
That's what we're calling them.
I saw one today.
He's a bank robber, and he
can control the weather.
This just keeps getting cooler.
This is not cool.
All right? A man died.
Mardon must have gotten his
powers the same way I did.
From the storm cloud.
He's still out there.
We have to stop him
before he hurts anyone else.
Barry!
That's a job for the police.
I work for the police.
As a forensic assistant.
You're responsible for this.
For him.
What's important is you!
Not me. I lost everything.
I lost my company.
I lost my reputation.
I lost my freedom.
And then you broke your arm,
and it healed in three hours.
Inside your body could be a map
to a whole new world... Genetic therapies,
vaccines, medicines, treasures buried deep
within your cells and we cannot
risk losing everything
because you want to go out and play hero!
You're not a hero.
You are just a young man
who was struck by lightning.
I didn't do this.
I swear to God, I didn't do this.
Dad, why are they taking you?
- Barry, don't go in the house.
- Where's mom?
What's gonna happen to my son?
- Dad!
- Barry!
- Stay out of the house!
Barry!
Joe, you know these people?
My daughter's best friends with their kid.
- I'm sorry.
- Mm.
- Mom.
- Barry.
Mom!
So that's my story.
I've spent my whole life
searching for the impossible,
never imagining that I would
become the impossible.
So why come to me?
Something tells me you
didn't just run 600 Miles
to say "hi" to a friend.
All my life, I've wanted to just do more...
Be more.
And now I am.
And the first chance I get to help someone,
I screw up.
What if Wells is right?
What if I'm not a hero?
What if I'm just some guy
who was struck by lightning?
I don't think that bolt of lightning
struck you, Barry.
I think it chose you.
I'm just not sure I'm like you, Oliver.
I don't know if I can be some... vigilante.
You can be better.
Because you can inspire people
in a way that I never could...
Watching over your city
like a guardian angel...
Making a difference...
Saving people...
In a flash.
Take your own advice.
Wear a mask.
Cool.
I've been going over unsolved cases
from the past nine months,
and there's been a sharp increase
in unexplained deaths and missing people.
Your meta-humans have been busy.
Now, I'm not blaming you.
I know you didn't mean
for any of this to happen.
I know you all lost something.
But I need your help to catch Mardon
and anyone else out there like him.
But I can't do it without you.
If we're gonna do this,
I have something that might help.
Something I've been playing with.
Designed to replace the turnouts
firefighters traditionally wear.
I thought if S.T.A.R. Labs
could do something nice
for the community, maybe people wouldn't
be so angry at Dr. Wells anymore.
How is it going to help me?
It's made of a reinforced tri-polymer.
It's heat and abrasive resistant,
so it should withstand your moving
at high-velocity speeds.
And the aerodynamic design
should help you maintain control.
Plus, it has built-in sensors
so we can track your vitals
and stay in contact with you from here.
Thanks.
Now how do we find Mardon?
I retasked S.T.A.R. Labs satellite
to track meteorological abnormalities
over Central City.
We just got a ping.
Atmospheric pressure dropped 20 millibars
in a matter of seconds.
I've tracked it to a farm
just west of the city.
I'm not saying Mardon is alive.
But if he was, this is the last place
him and his brother hid out.
Let's go.
Mardon?
On your feet.
Hands on your head.
You got me.
The night of the storm,
after S.T.A.R. Labs blew,
after our plane went down,
and I woke up on the ground alive,
when I saw what I can do, I understood.
I am God.
Shut the hell up.
Turn around.
Do you think that your guns can stop God?
Why in the hell would God
need to rob banks?
You're right.
I've been thinking too small.
Barry! Barry!
This thing's getting closer.
Wind speeds are 200
Miles-per-hour and increasing.
Barry, can you hear me?
Yeah. Loud and clear.
If it keeps up, this could
become an F-5 tornado.
But it's headed towards the city.
How do I stop it? Guys?
What if I unravel it?
How the hell are you going to do that?
I'll run around it
in the opposite direction,
cut off its legs.
He'd have to clock
700 Miles-per-hour to do that.
Your body may not
be able to handle those speeds.
You'll die.
I have to try.
The suit's holding up.
- But he's not.
- He can do it.
I know he can do it.
It's too strong!
It's time to think big.
You can do this, Barry.
You were right.
I am responsible for all of this.
So many people have been hurt
because of me, and when I looked at you,
all I saw was another potential
victim of my hubris.
And yes, I created this madness,
but you, Barry, you can stop it.
You can do this.
Now run, Barry, run!
Barry?
Hey.
I didn't think there was
anyone else like me.
I'm not like you.
You're a murderer.
- Barry?
- It's over.
I'm okay.
What you can do...
It was the lightning bolt?
More or less.
I'm sorry, Barry.
I'm sorry I didn't believe you.
And I called you crazy
for chasing the impossible.
But you really did see something
that night your mom died.
And your dad is innocent.
I need you to promise me something.
I don't want you telling Iris
about anything you can do, any of it.
I want her safe.
Promise me.
Yeah.
Hey, slugger.
You've been calling me that since I was 11.
Funny thing is, I finally got
into a fight today.
You just got out of a coma.
I'm not sure you should be picking fights.
Hey...
Did you win?
Yeah, I did.
You didn't kill mom.
You know I know that, right?
You believing me is all I need.
You're not gonna be in here much longer.
Whoever killed mom...
Whatever killed her...
I think I finally have a way to find them.
To stop them.
Barry, we've talked about this.
It's time to let it go.
You have got to stop worrying about me,
and live your life.
For the first time,
I feel like I finally can.
The truth is,
ever since the night mom died,
I've been stuck in one place,
missed out on a lot of things.
But I'm different now.
I've made some new friends.
They're helping me find my way...
Why is it shaped like a lightning bolt?
So it's not boring.
To finally move forward.
You remember when you
wanted me to change my name
so I wouldn't have to deal with
people knowing you're my dad?
I'm glad they know.
I'm so proud to be your son.
I love you, son.
I love you too, dad.
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
A friend recently gave me
the idea for a new name.
And something tells me,
it's gonna catch on.
Greg, move your head!
www.tvsubtitles.net
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother killed
- by something impossible.
- Run, Barry, run!
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensics scientist,
but secretly,
I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
Mom!
And get justice for my father.
I am... The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
Cisco, if you don't
seal off the blast,
everyone in this building
will die, including Caitlin.
Don't look for me again.
Ronnie's alive,
and he's out there,
alone and scared.
Hartley Rathaway
Possesses one of the finest
scientific minds
I've ever encountered.
I can't imagine
how you're gonna feel
when you open up these doors
and let me out of here.
Why would I ever do that?
Because I know
where Ronnie Raymond is.
Honey... honey...
Dana.
Oh, God.
Someone!
- Help!
- Somebody help us.
See if you can get the power
of that line shut down.
You guys lay down the hose line.
- Please help!
- Help us!
- Hold on!
Stay here, all right?
I gotcha.
Dana!
How did...
I love you.
Thank you,
Flash.
Dude.
That was insane.
I mean,
even I'm having a hard time
getting mad at you
for dirtying up my suit.
Okay, when are we going to
start considering it my suit?
I'd be comfortable calling it
our suit.
"Our suit."
Tonight was the fastest
you've ever run.
Yes, your training is
paying off.
That couple is alive tonight
because of you.
I can still get faster.
I know I can.
And you will one day, I'm sure.
But for today,
I'd say you've fulfilled
your save quota.
Proper rest is what you need,
as do we all.
Better yet, what we all need is
a proper drink.
Who's up for a round?
Oh, dude, it's...
it's movie night with Joe.
I can't.
But I'll see you guys tomorrow,
all right?
- Bye.
- Night.
What about you?
Drinks on me?
I think I'll pass.
You okay?
I was looking for my tablet
at your work station,
and I found this.
I can explain.
I know you said we should
stop looking for Ronnie,
so I...
didn't stop looking for Ronnie.
Why?
Hartley.
He said he knew
what happened to Ronnie.
Oh, Hartley Rathaway,
who is currently locked up in
our super-villain basement jail
for going psycho
with sound waves?
Yeah.
He's made some poor choices.
There's no argument there.
But I looked into
what he was saying and...
Cisco.
Ronnie's gone,
and it's time for me to
move on with my life.
Doesn't seem like it.
What's that supposed to mean?
Look, I'm not an expert
on love,
but I think in order to
move on from Ronnie,
you actually have to move on.
♪ Don't pull your pants ♪
♪ Before I go down ♪
♪ Don't turn away ♪
♪ This is my time ♪
♪ Like a shotgun ♪
♪ Needs an outcome ♪
♪ You gonna get some ♪
- ♪ Go ahead go way low ♪
- ...Level 2!
♪ Where I can do no harm ♪
♪ Go ahead go way low ♪
Hold it right there!
♪ In my honey-loving arms ♪
♪ Go ahead go way low ♪
♪ Where I can do no wrong ♪
Shawna?
Hey, there she is!
Crazy cool, right?
How did you do that?
Grab my hand.
♪ And 'cause I can ♪
♪ I'm gonna go west ♪
How the hell, Shawna?
So, you like?
Oh, I love.
♪ Like a shotgun ♪
♪ I can't be outdone ♪
Whoo!
♪ You gonna get some ♪
Hey.
The security cameras in
half the prison are shut down.
Then Clay Parker,
according to this data log,
who was still
locked in his cell,
somehow vanishes.
Not completely.
What's that?
It's some kind of
organic particulate residual.
I found it on the floor
in here,
just outside the cell,
out in the hallway.
Trail led me
all the way outside.
Dad.
So...
Word around here is,
Parker pulled a Shawshank?
Yep, and none of
the other prisoners
heard or saw anything.
Well, they wouldn't talk to you
about it.
Leaves us with
not a lot to go on.
Well, if there's anyone
who can figure out
how Parker got out of here,
it's you, Son.
Come on, Allen, let's go.
Duty calls.
So, my dad just happened
to come by?
The guard owed me a favor.
Thank you.
Thanks for...
getting me
out of that hellhole.
You'd have done the same
for me, right?
So...
How the hell did this
happen to you?
Don't know.
After you got locked up,
I started not feeling right.
I was passing out for
no reason,
waking up in odd places.
It took me a while before
I could control it.
Soon as I could...
I came for you.
What, so you can just
jump wherever you want?
If I can see where
I'm going.
We got a second chance, Clay.
We can leave Central City.
Do... do all the things
we talked about.
I can't leave yet, baby.
I owe Marcus a lot of money.
I skipped town
before paying him back.
He'll find us.
Hey, but with what you can do,
we can pay off that debt.
Then we'll be free, and
we can go anywhere in the world.
Together.
Not even Barry's cells
move this fast.
I've never seen
anything like it.
So Clay Parker is a meta-human?
Not so fast.
The particulate residue
Barry gathered
at Iron Heights does contain
Clay Parker's DNA,
but also DNA of a woman.
Run her DNA against
the CCPD criminal database.
See if you get a match.
Yahtzee.
Her name's Shawna Baez.
Mostly petty crimes,
and this girl likes to party,
apparently.
Long list of disorderly conducts
at local bars.
So I'm guessing we find her,
we find Clay Parker.
- Barry?
- Yeah.
In the meantime,
let's track these particulates
and see how they work.
I'll be right with you guys.
I've had the biggest craving
for Thai food.
You said you knew
what happened to Ronnie
and how he was still alive.
And you said Professor Stein
was at S.T.A.R. Labs
the night of the explosion.
Yes.
He was.
Why?
The mystery isn't why Stein went
to S.T.A.R. Labs that night.
It's why he didn't leave.
Tell me.
Can't.
I have to show you.
You are not getting out
of this cell.
Fair enough,
but I know you, Cisco.
I know how much
you looked up to Ronnie.
He was like family.
A family
you built for yourself here.
I know how much you want
to see that family healed.
Let me help you.
I don't believe you.
Well, I'm telling you
the truth, Cisco.
When you are ready,
you know where to find me.
What's that smile about?
I saw my dad today.
No glass, no phones.
Just me and him, face-to-face.
Joe arranged it.
That must have been amazing,
Barry.
Yeah.
I really needed it.
I'm sure he needed it, too.
Were you there
investigating the breakout?
- Mm-hmm.
- That is a big story.
Which I am not a part of.
My editor wants me writing about
The Flash, and only The Flash.
Is that a bad thing?
I don't know.
I would just like
to be thought of
as more than The Flash PR flack.
I mean,
if I don't write something soon,
I think I might lose my job.
Hey, no.
We will find you
a great story to write about.
Together.
Okay?
You know
I'm always here for you.
I know.
Didn't know you enjoyed yourself
a little rough trade.
If I'm gonna let you out,
I'm not taking any chances.
Curiosity's a maddening thing,
is it not?
What do you mean
you've been asking around?
Do you know
a Marcus Stockheimer?
Sure,
he's some mid-level gangster.
He works mainly on
the south side.
Word is, Clay Parker was
a runner for Marcus.
When Clay got pinched,
Marcus lost a lot of money.
Apparently Marcus doesn't like
losing money.
So, what?
So Parker can't leave
Central City
until he's paid off his debt?
From what I'm told,
if you're a member of
the Stockheimer crew,
you get out,
first thing you do is
pay him a visit
or suffer the consequences.
All right.
No more playing cop.
Promise me.
I hear you.
All right.
You said you were gonna show me
what happened to Ronnie.
Ronnie died inside the building.
What are we doing out here?
What do you see?
I don't know.
Buildings, walls, dirt.
Wells would be so disappointed
in your observational skills.
Look again.
It's Japanese.
How can you speak six languages
and sound like a dick
in every one of them?
It means "bomb shadow."
They found these
all over Hiroshima
after the first atomic bomb
was dropped.
This shadow belonged to
Martin Stein.
The accelerator explosion
did this to him?
You really don't see it,
do you?
You're gonna kick yourself
when you figure it out.
Oh, man.
You were full of it then,
and you're full of it now.
This is just another one of
your lame-ass tricks.
Come on.
We're going back
into the Pipeline.
Oh!
Aah!
You're not the only one who
understands vibrations, Hartley.
Those cochlear devises
you're wearing?
I made a few adjustments.
No, please don't!
Aah.
If you know how to find Ronnie,
then you better tell me.
Right now.
Please, make it stop.
Please.
I'll show you.
I'll show...
ah... aah!
Try that again,
and I won't make it stop.
Ever.
I'm impressed.
Didn't think
you had that in you.
But you have to
take these off me
if you want to
find out the truth.
And why's that?
It'll look a little conspicuous
where we're going next.
Mm.
I was analyzing the particulates
that Clay Parker and Shawna Baez
left behind,
and I found
something very interesting.
When Clay's cells come into
contact with Shawna's,
they adopt her properties.
Something bothering you?
Why would you ask that?
You're doing that
biting-your-lower-lip thing
that you do
when something's bothering you.
I'm fine.
Okay.
Cisco says
I don't have a life.
You don't, do you?
I do!
I cook and I eat
and I read
and I help you.
So, what you're saying is,
you do everything
that has nothing to do with
having a life.
You don't have to be
rude about it.
Hey, I'm not doing any better
than you.
My social life consists of
running at superhuman speed
and Netflix.
We are quite the pair,
Mr. Allen.
Yes we are, Dr. Snow.
There's an armed robbery
in progress.
Two suspects,
male and female in their 20s.
Sounds like our meta-human
Bonnie and Clyde are
at it again.
Time to ruin
their social life.
Just a few bags, baby,
is enough to pay back Marcus.
These things are heavier
than they look.
Oh, I've read about you.
You're The Flash.
I've heard you're real fast.
Let's see if it's true.
Catch me if you can.
I can.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
Not too many men can
keep up with me.
This is a bullet wound.
You're lucky it just barely
broke the skin.
Guess I'm a lot faster than
a speeding bullet.
Shawna Baez.
She can teleport.
As in, "Beam me up, Shawna?"
Yes, of course.
Quantum entanglement.
The ability to manipulate
interconnected particles
over an infinite distance.
Or, as Einstein put it,
"spooky action at a distance."
Every time I got close,
she'd disappear.
It was like we were playing
a game of...
Peek-a-boo.
Come on.
Can't I name one?
How am I supposed to catch her
if I don't know
where she's gonna be?
Everybody has limits,
Mr. Allen.
Now that we know
Shawna's powers,
we'll focus on those limits.
All right.
Let me know.
I'm gonna change.
I gotta go help Iris.
Hey, Barry.
- Hey, Eddie.
- Hey, what are you doing here?
I thought I'd see if
you wanted help
writing your story
for the paper.
Oh, that is so sweet.
I would love to,
but we were about to have dinner
with Eddie's mom tonight.
And we're late.
Can we do it another time?
Yeah, yeah... yeah.
Okay.
- All right.
- Bye.
- See ya.
Hey.
What bars did
Shawna and Clay frequent?
Uh, mostly south side
dive bars.
Why?
I was just gonna check 'em out.
See if they fall into
any old habits.
That's a good idea.
I'll join you.
♪ Everyone's wondering ♪
♪ Will you come out tonight ♪
♪ Everyone's trying
to get it right ♪
♪ Get it right ♪
Hey.
What?
Nothing.
Uh, well, you look...
really nice.
I don't always dress like
a high school principal.
So, this is where
Shawna Baez and Clay Parker
used to hang out?
It is,
according to the files.
I thought we could
kill two birds with one stone.
Look for them and
get ourselves back out there.
I keep making
the same mistake.
Every time Iris falls,
I race to pick her up
thinking that one of these times
things are gonna change,
but I... things are never
gonna change.
I am just destined to be
just the friend.
At least you're not pining for
someone who bursts into flames
and wants nothing
to do with you.
What is wrong with us?
I mean, we're in our 20s.
We should be having fun.
We should meet people,
go on lots of dates.
Well,
here's to liquid courage.
♪ Everybody's working for
The weekend ♪
Uh... that is... very fast.
Drank all of it.
Excuse me?
I would like to start a tab.
CCPD confiscated everything
from S.T.A.R. Labs
after the explosion.
Video, audio,
traffic cam footage.
Okay, so?
I saw Martin Stein the night
S.T.A.R. Labs went boom.
He walked right past me.
You see, Stein specialized in
transmutation.
Molecular transmography.
Quantum splicing.
Taking two things
and making them one.
Let's go to the videotape,
shall we?
Okay, stop.
Now zoom in a few clicks.
Now advance it,
frame-by-frame.
His eyes.
They turned white,
just like Ronnie's.
Now, stop there.
In the mass of energy.
- Looks like...
- Ronnie.
And Professor Stein.
The dark matter
merged them together.
Explains why Ronnie hasn't
seemed quite himself lately.
It's because he's not.
He's Martin Stein.
Aah!
You can't say I didn't keep up
my end of the bargain.
I figure that makes us
even Stephen.
Adios.
Excuse me,
could I get some water?
Yo.
Excuse me?
- For real?
- Mr. Barry Allen!
Come on down!
- Or up.
- I'm not doing it.
Come up here with me.
Oh, come show 'em what you got.
Come on.
Barry!
Barry! Barry! Barry! Barry!
Barry! Barry! Barry!
Ooh, look at him go.
He's so fast!
Ooh, shh!
You know I'm not
much of a singer.
And you're not
much of a drinker.
We are gonna
bring this place down.
Okay, just... good girl.
Get ready.
♪ Summer lovin' ♪
♪ Had me a blast ♪
♪ Summer lovin'
Happened so fast ♪
♪ I met a girl ♪
♪ Crazy for me ♪
♪ I met a boy
Cute as can be ♪
♪ Summer days
driftin' away ♪
♪ To uh-oh
Those summer nights ♪
♪ Uh well-a
well-a well-a uh ♪
You're fast and you can sing?
What can't you do?
Stop you from drinking,
apparently.
I'm not even sure
that was mine.
I have to go
to the bathroom.
Okay.
Can I close out my tab,
please?
Hey, Stevie.
Can my friend here tap out?
Sure thing, Linda.
Uh, thank you, Linda.
You're welcome, Barry.
How do you know my name?
"Barry. Barry. Barry."
Yeah...
Sorry about us up there.
That's...
Are you kidding?
No, that was some of
the best singing that I've heard
come from that stage.
You definitely
made my ears happy.
Don't worry.
Thanks.
So... was that
your girlfriend up there?
Oh... no, no.
She's a friend.
Okay.
Hey. Have you heard of
this new phone app?
It's so cool.
Check it out.
You just touch someone's phone
with your phone,
and it automatically
downloads your contact info.
Wow.
That is cool.
See?
You have my number.
What you do with it now is
up to you.
Okay.
- Barry?
- Yeah?
I don't feel good.
Okay.
Come on.
Okay?
80 grand.
What I owe.
So we square now?
Almost.
Ohh.
Holy crap.
I'm glad you're impressed.
So we cool now?
Absolutely.
Couldn't be cooler.
Which is why I think we need to
keep working together.
With what I know,
and what you can do,
oh, we can be looking at
a very lucrative future.
Police!
Everybody down!
Aah!
- Oh, baby!
Hold it right there.
Damn.
Are we still running?
No, we are here.
Vodka and super-speed...
not a good combination.
Come on.
So, are you gonna call her?
Who?
That girl.
The one who gave you
her number.
I hadn't really
thought about it.
Yes, you have.
But I know you.
You won't.
You'll let her slip
right through your fingers
because you think
you don't deserve happiness.
But what you don't realize is,
you need a little saving, too.
Little help, please.
W... yeah.
Okay.
There you go again.
Saving me from that
evil dress.
Get in bed.
Did you sneak a peek?
At my goods?
I wouldn't be much of a hero
if I did.
Yeah, but it's okay
if you peeked a little.
You deserve a peek for
all the good stuff you do.
Drink lots of water.
Thank you for tonight.
I sang.
Any time.
Hey, Barry?
Will you stay with me
until I fall asleep?
Sure, yeah.
Hi.
So loud.
Oh, ho-ho.
I just wanted to make sure
you're okay.
Let's just say I envy
your inability to get drunk.
I don't remember
much from last night.
Yeah,
that's probably for the best.
♪ Summer lovin' ♪
Oh, God.
That I do remember.
What's wrong?
Cisco... has something
he needs to tell you.
Hartley's gone.
He escaped
from the Pipeline?
How is that even possible?
I let him out.
Are you mad?
I can't tell with
those glasses on.
I'd like to yell
and wave my arms,
but I'm afraid I'd throw up.
Why?
What were you thinking?
You know how dangerous he is.
Hartley said he knew
what happened to Ronnie.
I told you to let it go.
I didn't want you
looking into that for me.
I wasn't doing it for you.
I...
I sealed Ronnie into the
accelerator before it blew.
He told me to wait
two minutes,
and I waited,
but he didn't come back.
And I can't stop thinking,
10, 20 seconds and...
Ronnie wouldn't be like
he is right now.
I've wanted to tell you
so many times.
I'm so sorry.
So you carried that around
this whole time?
Do you know what
Ronnie would say if he was here?
He would say that
you did the right thing.
It wasn't your fault.
What happened that night
wasn't anybody's fault.
Come on.
Don't we have
a teleporter to catch?
We do have
a teleporter to catch.
And fortunately,
we do have a promising theory.
Take a look at this.
Now, this is the normal behavior
of the particulate
that Shawna left behind.
Watch what happens
when we remove light.
Shawna can only become entangled
with something she can see.
Take away her ability
to do that...
She can't teleport.
Exactly.
So, we just need to get her
into a dark space.
How do we do that?
It's a valid question.
Hello?
What?
Yeah, I'll be right there.
All right.
What's wrong?
M-my dad.
He's been stabbed.
Dad... what happened?
A rather stern reminder,
I'd say,
not to poke around
Marcus Stockheimer's business.
Dad, I told you to stop.
Your dad called me
with more intel.
It helped us track down Clay and
Shawna and arrest Stockheimer.
I managed to screw up
Marcus's big heist, too, so...
You two kept working together,
and you didn't tell me?
It isn't his fault.
I did it to help you.
You getting stabbed and beaten
is not helping me.
Look, I-I-I-I don't get to
feel useful very much in here.
So if I can help you
for a change,
I'm gonna want to
be there for you.
Just like you've been there
for me all these years.
Yep.
You said Marcus had
a big heist coming up?
Mm.
Do you know anything else
about it?
Dad, tell me
who did this to you.
No, it doesn't matter,
slugger.
But you said
you want to help me.
So help me.
One of Marcus's boys.
Julius.
What the hell?
Evening, Julius.
How'd I get out here?
You escaped.
They catch me trying to escape,
they're gonna add five years
to my sentence.
Ten, actually.
Unless you tell me where
Marcus Stockheimer's next
job is gonna be.
Oh! Guards will be here
any second.
I'd start blabbing.
Okay!
Okay.
It's a TDK
and money transfer truck
coming from the federal reserve
bank in St. Louis.
Supposed to be millions.
Delivery's around 8:00.
That's all I know.
I swear.
That's right now.
Hey!
Hey, what about me?
I think we got company.
What the...
Okay.
Let's go.
I got this.
Why the hell
do you care what we do?
Are you a cop or something?
Something.
Come on!
Barry, remember: she cannot
teleport if she cannot see.
Limit her field of vision.
No.
He left me.
Is there any way she can
teleport out of this?
It's impossible.
It's one-way glass.
It's mirrored on the inside.
No one dangerous is ever gonna
get out of this thing again.
Shawna.
Clay left you.
He's out there,
and you're in here.
You know what
the crazy thing is?
I still love him.
Cisco.
Crazy is right.
Some people are worth
being crazy for.
I'm sorry if I was a bit of
a drunken mess the other night.
Actually, it was pretty fun.
Yeah, it was.
You know what?
I think everybody's been right
about you and me.
Both of us have been hung up
on people for way too long.
If what Cisco says is true,
that Ronnie merged
with Martin Stein,
then he's not alive anymore.
Time for me to move on.
Find someone new
to be crazy about.
All right, well.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Yes, sure.
Bye.
That's for you.
I thought maybe
you could help me out,
if you're willing.
This is about
the breakout at Iron Heights.
Clay Parker.
He's still on the loose,
and we need to catch him.
Why are you giving this to me?
'Cause you're a good reporter.
And the only one I know.
You're not the only one
who's fast.
Hey, what are you doing here?
- Hey.
- If you came to check on me,
that is really sweet,
but I think
everything's gonna be okay.
I'm glad.
Uh...
I actually am not here
to see you.
No?
No, I have a lunch date.
With who?
- Ready.
- Hey.
Oh, hey,
you're our new stringer, right?
Yeah.
I'm Linda Park.
Sports.
Iris West.
How did you two meet?
Well, it's actually
kind of a funny story.
Yeah, I'll tell you later,
all right?
- You ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- See ya.
Have fun.
So an actual date this time.
Good for you.
You didn't tell her
your dad's in the slammer?
No, I read in a magazine that
that's a big turnoff.
Smart.
Hey.
You see this?
No.
I haven't.
The Flash.
I saw him once.
In here.
Watched him save
Joe's life.
Joe told me about that.
I guess he was lucky.
Hm.
Lucky Joe.
The strangest thing.
I get roughed up by Julius,
end up in here.
Next thing I know, Julius is
caught trying to escape,
claims The Flash
broke him out.
Won't be seeing Julius for
a long time now.
Guess I'm lucky too, huh?
Dad.
If I was The Flash,
don't you think that you'd be
the first to know about it?
Yeah.
Well, if The Flash were my son,
I'd tell him a few things.
First off, I'd tell him
it's a dangerous world,
so be careful.
Then I'd tell him he's a hero.
And he's saving a lot of lives.
But the most important thing
for him to know, I feel,
is that
his father's proud of him.
Power grid's been going haywire
in this sector.
The system's so antiquated.
Whoa.
What was that?
Aah!
Greg, move your head.
www.tvsubtitles.net
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident made me
the impossible.
To the outside world, I am
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly,
I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day,
I'll find who killed my mother
and get justice for my father.
That day is today.
What?
No Big Belly Burger?
It's one of the few perks
of living in this time.
We're out of cows
where I come from.
You don't care about that.
You have questions. Go ahead.
Not sure where to start...
Thawne.
That is your real name...
Eobard Thawne.
- Since the day I was born.
- And when was that?
136 years from now.
That's not what
you want to know.
Go ahead, Barry.
Ask it.
Why did you kill
my mother?
Because I hate you.
Not you now.
You years from now.
- In the future.
- In a future. Yes.
We're enemies, rivals,
opposites,
reverses of one another.
Why?
Wh-why were we enemies?
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't...
matter anymore.
What matters is that
neither of us was strong enough
to defeat the other.
Until I learned your secret.
I learned your name.
Barry Allen.
And finally, I knew how
to defeat you once and for all.
Travel back in time,
kill you as a child.
Wipe you
from the face of the earth.
But then you, future you,
that is, followed me back,
and we fought.
We both landed
some pretty solid shots.
And then you, future you, got
your younger self out of there.
I was so mad.
But then I thought...
what if you were
to suffer a tragedy?
What if you were to suffer
something so horrible,
so traumatic that your child
self could never recover?
Then you would not become
The Flash.
And so I stabbed your mother
in the heart,
and I was free.
Finally able to return
to a future without The Flash,
only to realize
that in traveling back
I'd lost my way home.
Lost my ability to harness
the speed force.
And without it,
I was stuck here.
Stranded in this time,
unable to return to my own.
And the only way back
was The Flash.
But The Flash was gone,
and so I created him.
Why train me?
Why help me save
so many people?
Because I needed you
to get fast.
Fast enough to rupture
the space-time barrier
and create
a stable wormhole
through which
I could return home.
Why would I
ever do that?
Because...
Barry Allen,
if you give me what I want,
I'm gonna give you
what you want.
You can go back
and save your mother.
You can prevent your father
from going to prison.
You can reunite
the Allen family.
No.
No, I don't
believe you.
I want to kill you
right now.
I know that rage.
I used to feel that rage
every time I looked upon you.
And now, somehow,
I know
what Joe and Henry feel
when they look on you
with pride.
With love.
No. No.
Don't you
ever say that to me!
I know you're upset,
but I'm giving you
a chance.
I'm giving you a chance to undo
all the evil I've done.
Don't you want that chance?
The rare opportunity to go
back in time and right a wrong
and save your mother's life...
Quite the paradox Harrison has
presented you with, Mr. Allen.
The chance to be
with someone you love?
Seems pretty cut and dry
to me.
At first blush, Dr. Snow,
it would appear so,
but this gift
has unparalleled risk.
Barry, the night
your mother died,
the night you saved yourself
from being killed,
that event altered the timeline
you were already on
and changed
the course of history.
So what you're saying is we're
living in a parallel universe?
Just like when
I time travelled before.
But he... he only changed
one day that time.
Exactly. Now imagine 15 years
of compounded experiences.
One different decision,
no matter how big or small,
impacts everything that follows.
Moments upon moments,
choices upon choices.
No relationships,
nothing would be as it is today,
and you'd never know
the difference
because you'd never
remember any of it.
So if I go back
and save my mom,
my dad doesn't go to prison.
I never live
with Joe and Iris.
You might never meet me.
Or Caitlin or Ronnie.
Truth is,
there's no real way
of knowing what
your life will be.
There's no choice here, Barry.
You have to do this.
You gotta change the past.
Joe?
So what...
What, that's it?
You think I should
just do it?
Yeah, I do.
Which means I will never
come to live with you, and...
you're okay with that?
Barry, you get the chance
to grow up with both parents.
You don't have to grow up
without a mother.
What about growing up
without a father?
You will have a father...
Your real father.
Wells has messed with our lives
long enough.
This is why you became
The Flash, Barry.
To put things right.
You saved a lot of
people's lives this past year.
Now it's time
to save yours.
Dad, look.
I know this sounds crazy.
I think
we're way past crazy, slugger.
Look, you're fast, I get it.
But turning back time...
No, I wouldn't be
turning time back.
I would be...
going back
to that night
to save her.
And what does Joe think
about all this?
He thinks
I should do it.
No.
You can't.
Dad...
I can make it so that night
will never have happened.
We'll be a family again.
We are a family.
Not like this.
Not without Mom.
Barry, there's a natural order
to things, okay?
Things happen the way they do.
We may not know why
at the time,
but there must always be
a reason.
Now, I believe that.
I've had to believe it.
I... I can save Mom.
At what cost?
You said time would change.
What if it changes you?
- I don't care.
- I do.
I am in awe
of the remarkable man
that you are becoming...
All the things you've achieved,
and not just as The Flash,
but you, Barry.
Your honesty.
Your heart.
You were always a hero.
And your mom would be
just as proud.
And if she had a say in this,
if she thought for one second
that you going back to save her
would mean you losing
what makes you so special,
she would never want that.
Barry, what I hope for you,
maybe the greatest thing that
a father can hope for his son
is that one day, you will become
a father yourself.
And then you will know...
How much I truly love you.
98.6. Normal.
I don't even know
what that word means anymore.
Me neither.
I know Barry
really appreciates you
coming back to help him
stop Wells.
That's not the only reason
I'm back, Cait.
I'm here now.
For good.
But I thought...
I thought too...
I thought too much
about what might happen if
the government tracked us down.
If we couldn't control
our powers and we hurt someone.
If we hurt you.
But I realized that although
sometimes I'm more than one man,
I'm not whole
unless I'm with you.
I love you, Cait.
- Are you sure?
- I am.
Once upon a time and a
Particle Accelerator or so ago,
you agreed to marry me.
Yes, I did.
What do you say
we do that?
Thought I might find you here.
I needed to get
out of the lab.
I thought this would be
a good place to think.
Oh, it is.
Trust me.
I've done a lot
of thinking up here.
When I wasn't having
clandestine meetings
with the mysterious
"streak."
Yeah, not mad
we lost that name.
Hey, I thought that
had pizzazz.
- No.
- Uh-uh.
So are you gonna do it?
It's just so... huge.
It's the biggest decision
of my life,
and if I'm wrong,
I can't undo it.
Why would you
want to?
I mean, you'd get to see
your mom again, your dad,
have a great career,
even get married.
Iris West-Allen, huh?
I never really thought of myself
as a hyphenator.
Must be a 2024 thing.
We don't know that
that's going to happen.
Do you think that because you
didn't live with us,
that's why things
are different there?
Growing up together and...
knowing so much
about each other...
it made it hard for me to admit
how I felt about you.
And I waited too long, and you
fell in love with Eddie.
But living with you
and Joe...
I've had a great life,
Iris.
Come here,
Barry.
What do you think
I should do?
I need someone to tell me.
I think...
that for once in your life,
Barry Allen,
you should stop thinking
about other people.
I think you should do
what's in your heart.
Do what you need to do
for yourself.
Ah!
Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
it took you a whole hour
longer to decide
than I thought it would.
So how does this work?
Your grand plan?
Well, it's really not
that grand at all, Barry.
In fact, it's rather simple.
We use
the Particle Accelerator.
The Particle Accelerator.
The last time that happened,
you caused an explosion
that hurt a lot of people.
This time, the accelerator
will operate exactly
the way it was designed to.
Except, instead of two particles
moving in opposite directions,
colliding at the speed of light
in the inner ring,
we're only going
to inject one particle
into the accelerator.
And I'm what
it collides with.
And if you can go fast enough,
Barry,
if you can hit that particle
with enough speed,
you will punch a hole right
though the fabric of reality.
And you will create a portal
connecting this time
to infinite times.
A wormhole.
Through which one might travel
back to the past, say,
to the night your mother died or
forward to the future, to, say,
my time.
You said if I run fast enough.
What happens if I don't?
If you don't achieve
the desired velocity barrier,
you'll die.
According to
Wells' calculations,
Barry super-speeds
inside the accelerator ring.
Once Barry
reaches optimum speed,
we then launch a hydrogen proton
into the accelerator.
Once the collision happens,
a wormhole forms,
opening a gateway
into time itself.
It's at that moment
I plan on shouting something
along the lines of "Eureka"
or possibly "Excelsior."
I'm uncommitted.
What do you think?
I mean, on the one hand,
it does make a kind of sense.
On the other hand,
why?
Why, why would you ever
consider doing this?
You know why.
So, for this to actually work,
how fast would Barry have to go?
By my estimates,
Mach Two at a minimum.
You've never gone that fast.
So what happens if Barry
doesn't reach that speed?
I mean, I'm imagining a bug
hitting a windshield.
How far off am I?
Not very far,
I'm afraid.
Let me worry about
how fast I have to go.
We're gonna need
something else too.
Really?
And what's that?
'Cause I don't know
about you guys,
but I'm not at all interested in
helping you get yourself killed.
I need you to build
a time machine.
Go on.
So, if Wells is as fast as you,
what's he need
a time machine for?
Apparently he lost his speed
when he killed my mom.
He gets it back sometimes
but only in spurts.
He can't fully
control it.
So I was right
about the wheelchair.
He was using it
to charge himself.
So after I open the wormhole,
he's gonna need the ship
to travel back
to the future.
He's been squirreling away
the parts.
Now we just need
to put it together.
Ronnie, I love you,
but this is a time machine,
not a bookcase from IKEA.
We got a problem.
These tiles...
They're made of tungsten.
Well, tungsten does have
the highest melting point
of any other element.
Yeah, but the dust
it generates is flammable.
The pressure exerted
from the wormhole...
Yeah. Yeah.
It could cause a hole to be
melted into the exterior.
It could explode.
Any ideas?
Let me ask Dr. Evil.
Which used to be
a name that made me smile.
Something on your mind,
Cisco?
No.
Yes.
How did you fit
your Reverse-Flash suit
into that little ring?
Is it some sort
of compressed micro tech?
Or actually, forget it.
I don't care.
Maybe a little.
Ronnie's right.
I should have accounted
for the temporal shearing.
Glad we're still good
for something.
I never underestimated
your contribution, Cisco.
Or Ronnie's.
As a matter of fact,
do you know how many times
I wished you were there with me
as I rebuilt the accelerator?
It would have been
a lot more fun.
Yeah?
Well, doesn't change the fact
that your nifty little
Time Sphere...
Is that what you're calling it?
Whatever it's called.
It's gonna blow.
Not if you cement the tiles
with a cobalt resin.
That'll prevent degradation
in conditions of extreme heat.
Okay. Fine.
We'll try that.
That's it? That's all?
Well, what do you
want me to say?
I don't know, Cisco.
I thought that of anyone, you'd
be a little more understanding
of my predicament.
I don't belong here.
These barbaric times.
It's like
living amongst the dead.
Is that what you told yourself?
When you killed me?
What?
What did you say?
It was an alternate timeline.
One that Barry reset.
But I never forgot it.
It just kept
coming back to me.
And I can still picture
the way you looked at me
when you called me a son
and you crushed my heart
with your fist.
Cisco...
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
It sucked.
Not for killing you.
I'm sure I had a good reason.
I'm sorry for the fact that
you're able to retain traces
of another timeline.
You're able to see through
the vibrations of the universe.
It means...
I wasn't sure
until just now.
Sure of what?
The night the Particle
Accelerator exploded...
You were affected too.
What are you talking about?
No.
I wasn't.
Don't be afraid, Cisco.
A great and honorable destiny
awaits you now.
I only hope that as you're
living your great adventure,
that you remember
who gave you that life.
And that it was given
out of love.
I'm sorry, but I'm told
this is the only station
with enough power
to run these calculations.
If we make the slightest error
creating the wormhole...
Say no more.
Joe told me to stick around
in case I was needed,
but it seems
I'm only in the way.
Everyone has
a contribution to make.
Perhaps you just haven't
discovered yours yet.
No, Dr. Wells made it
pretty clear when he told me
about the future.
I don't matter.
As far as history's concerned,
I don't save the day
or get the girl.
And you believed him?
He had a newspaper
from the year 2024.
And I have a mug that says
"World's Best Boss."
I doubt my teaching assistant
would testify
to its authenticity.
We're dealing with a lot
of big scientific ideas today.
But you, Mr. Thawne, might be
the most interesting thing here
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Me?
What are the odds that Dr. Wells
would travel back in time
and get stuck
in the exact same city
as his great-great-great-
great-grandfather?
Working in the same profession,
the same building?
And that part of his plan
to get home would mean
that he'd have to preserve
and protect your life.
That makes you this rare thing
that no scientist can plan for.
Which is?
Coincidence.
There is no science
to coincidence.
You, sir, are an anomaly.
A wild card, as it were.
You are the only person
in this whole story
who gets to choose
his own future.
At least, that's my opinion.
Wait, that can't be right.
Oh, dear.
- We have a problem.
- What?
The calculations.
There is a danger.
I know.
I'm ready to take the risk.
No, not just to you
but to everyone.
Wells didn't tell us everything.
Barry, even if you do reach
the right speed,
colliding
with the hydrogen particle,
there is a chance that explosion
could create a singularity.
What's a singularity?
It's a black hole.
We could destroy
Central City.
For starters.
If we create a singularity here
and then cannot control it,
we could be looking
at a global catastrophe.
So long and thanks
for all the fish.
Well, sure,
there's a bit of a risk.
I would hardly refer
to possibly causing
an extinction-level event as
"a bit of a risk."
Yeah, and your accelerator's
been about as reliable as the
beater I drove in high school.
Let me ask you a question.
How many meta-humans...
How many dangers...
Have we faced
this year together?
Or did you forget
that was me
fighting alongside
each and every one of you?
I have been planning this
for almost two decades.
It will work.
And how do we make sure
we don't open a black hole
in the middle
of Central City?
So, once the wormhole
stabilizes,
Barry will have 1 minute
and 52 seconds to alter the past
and return to this time.
If and when he does that,
you can close the wormhole,
and we can all live
happily ever after.
Almost two minutes.
More than enough time
to save Nora.
But not enough time
to stop you from going home?
Everything's a choice.
And what if I'm late?
You won't be.
I believe in you, Barry.
Always have.
So I guess the question is,
do your friends and family
believe in you as much as I do?
So, if I don't run fast enough
to collide with the particle,
then I'm dust,
and if I do run fast enough
but I'm not back here in time,
then a black hole will form,
swallow up the city
and possibly the world.
You're sure you still want to
look me in the eyes and tell me
this is for the best?
I'd be lying
if I told you I did.
Truth is, I don't...
I don't know what to think.
I thought
you were the sure one.
I...
was kind of banking on that
when I made my decision
the first time.
I was faking it.
Sometimes parents do that.
Most of the time,
parents do that.
Look, of course I'm scared.
But I didn't want you to not
help your mother
because you were worried
about me.
Well, I'll always worry
about you, Joe,
just like you'll always worry
about me.
Sorry,
but you can't stop that.
Do you think I can do this?
You think
I can save my mom?
I mean, do you think
I'm fast enough?
Yes.
I know you are.
You know, I've... I've dreamed
my whole life about...
saving her,
freeing my dad, and...
I never thought I'd have to lose
another parent to do that.
Barry...
Joe, it's true.
It's true.
I've always been
so focused on everything
that I lost that night,
but I gained so much too.
I was born with one father,
and that tragedy gave me...
another.
And I don't think
I can lose you.
You won't ever
lose me.
Ever, you hear me?
Ever.
Wow, slow news day?
If they only knew, right?
I thought you would be
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
I was.
Then I got hungry,
so I went to Mama Chows.
For dim sum?
Your favorite.
And to remind myself
of something.
What?
A coincidence. A pretty big
coincidence, actually.
About a year and a half ago,
I had a date with this girl.
Katie Rogers.
She was a dancer.
We had plans to meet
at Mama Chows,
but she texted me.
She pulled a hamstring
and had to cancel.
Oh, those fragile dancers.
I was bummed 'cause I was
looking forward to it.
So I had dinner by myself,
and I was walking home
when I saw a mugger
running with a stolen backpack.
Your backpack.
And I arrested him.
That's how you and I met.
I remember.
Someone just told me how
powerful a coincidence can be,
and it made me realize how many
coincidences had to happen
for you and I to get together...
in this time.
We've all been so focused on
Barry's destiny,
I forgot that I have one too.
And it's you.
Iris West,
every moment of my life
led to meeting you.
Screw the future.
Is this actually binding?
My father made me become a rabbi
before he would send me to MIT.
This will be "legit,"
as the kids say.
No kids say that.
Let's not fight
on our wedding day.
♪ There is freedom within ♪
♪ There is freedom without ♪
If it's all right with everyone,
I'd like to skip all the Hebrew.
I've learned a lot
about merging one's life
with another this past year.
Yet, for all the incredible
advancements in science
we've all been party to,
the mystery that brings
two people together through love
is still the province of magic.
Mr. Ramon,
the rings please.
♪ When the world comes in ♪
♪ They come, they come ♪
♪ To build a wall between us ♪
♪ We know they won't win ♪
I owe you a real ring.
I don't need one.
I have everything
and everyone
that I could ever need
right here.
And...
if all the events
of the past year
have led us
to this moment,
it was worth it.
I love you, Ronnie.
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Stop telling me
what to do.
♪ Don't dream it's over ♪
♪ Hey now, hey now ♪
♪ When the world comes in ♪
Congratulations.
♪ They come, they come ♪
Okay.
There are gonna be three yous
back there...
The you from the future
who saved younger you
from the Reverse-Flash
and now you you.
Remember, wait until future you
gets younger you out of there,
and then you can go
and save your mom.
Piece of cake.
May the Speed Force
be with you.
Good-bye, Dad.
Good-bye, Son.
Iris...
You don't have
to say anything.
I already know.
I hope whatever life you get,
it's enough for you.
That it makes
you happy.
You too.
Remember, Mr. Allen,
assuming you achieve the proper
velocity and open the wormhole,
you will only have
1 minute and 52 seconds
to save your mother
and return.
Or else...
I know.
Well...
you hold both our futures
in your hands now, Mr. Allen.
And I know you can do it.
Now...
Run...
Barry.
Run.
The accelerator's structural
integrity is holding.
What was that?
Is Barry okay?
Yeah.
He just passed Mach Two.
I was waiting for you
to bring Barry home.
Looks like he's going to be
staying with us for a while.
Barry, what you're seeing is
the Speed Force:
your past, you present,
your future
all at once.
So you need to focus
on where you want to go.
So think about...
that night.
Think about your mother.
Time for bed.
Good night, slugger.
Mom!
It's working.
Inject the hydrogen particle
now.
What's that?
What happened?
Barry... he's gone.
- Look.
- The wormhole.
And it's stable.
Start the clock.
Mom!
Barry!
Nora! Hold on!
Run, Barry, run!
Barry, no!
No, no, no!
Hey. It's okay.
It's okay. You're okay.
Please. My husband,
my son, are they...
They're okay.
They're both safe.
I promise.
Who are you?
I'm...
I'm The Flash.
I don't understand.
You look
just like my father.
This won't make
any sense,
but it's me, Mom.
It's Barry.
Barry?
Your Barry.
Oh, my beautiful boy.
I got a second chance
to come back here and...
Tell you that I'm okay.
Dad and I are
both okay.
And we love you, Mom.
I love you.
Oh, my sweet boy.
Bye. Good-bye.
Good-bye, Barry.
Mom.
I believe it's time to
say good-bye to Harrison Wells.
It's beautiful.
Rip Hunter would
be impressed.
He built
the first one of these.
Interesting man.
Now what the hell
is that?
That's my cue to leave.
Thank you, Cisco.
Don't ever come back.
30 seconds.
Home.
- Oh, my God.
- Barry.
We have to shut down
the wormhole quickly!
Caitlin!
You didn't save her.
Why?
You could have had
the life you wanted.
everything you ever wanted!
I already do.
Not for long.
Cut the internal generators.
Ten seconds, hurry.
Three, two, one.
Ronnie, are you okay?
Did you do it?
Yes, I turned them
all off.
They did it.
They cut the generator.
Just so we're clear,
after I kill you,
I'm going to kill them.
And then I'm going
to kill your father.
I always win, Flash.
Eddie! Oh, my...
Eddie!
What did you do?
No such thing
as a coincidence.
What's happening?
Cisco, help me.
Eddie's his ancestor.
If Eddie dies,
he'll never be born, and...
He's being erased
from existence.
No! No!
Eddie.
Eddie, no, no.
Stay with me, okay?
Stay.
He was wrong,
it turns out.
I'm a hero after all.
You are, Eddie.
You are my hero.
That's all
I ever wanted to be.
Your hero.
No!
I've controlled your life
for so long, Barry.
How will you get along
without me?
Guys, that's not good.
Professor, I shut down
the wormhole.
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
You did close it,
but it seems to be reopening.
We got to go.
You okay?
Iris, we have to go.
I'm not leaving him.
We have to go now, honey.
I'm sorry.
So that's what
we didn't want to happen.
- What's it doing?
- Feeding.
A singularity won't stop, not
even after the earth is gone.
I'm afraid the accretion disc
has already assembled.
What?
The diffuse material
that's in orbital motion
around the singularity.
What does that mean?
We have to disrupt the motion.
Basically it's just like
the tornado, only upside down.
And bigger.
And scarier.
Barry, that event
has an energy level
of at least
6.7 Tera Electron Volts.
It cannot be stopped.
I have to try.
Oh, God.
Barry.
Move your head.
www.tvsubtitles.net